Chapter 1: Fox Girl

It was a vast and barren wilderness with not a single person in sight.

Aside from weeds and shrubs, the only things that were visible on the barren, yellow landscape were countless gray rocks, all of different shapes and sizes.

A scorching sun was hanging in the sky, baking the earth with its heat, and the air was filled with yellow dust.

A petite and frail figure gradually came into focus on the bleak, yellow landscape, and she was running forward as fast as she could.

It was a little girl who was roughly six or seven years of age, and she was wearing a light yellow robe that was embroidered with pink plum blossoms. Her black hair was arranged into a pair of buns, and she possessed a set of intricate features, consisting of a pair of large eyes with bright, black pupils, a petite little nose, and a pair of red cherry lips.

The little girl was holding a palm-sized pellet drum tightly in her right hand.

The pellet drum seemed to be quite old, with the skin on either side of the drum already yellow with age, and there were several azure snake designs on its surface. The pair of pellets attached to the drum by short cords occasionally clattered audibly into the drum head as she ran along.

Despite her young age, the little girl was very fast and agile, and after just a few long strides, she arrived at a clearing in front of a patch of long grass that was as tall as the average adult person.

She seemed to be in a great hurry as her fair forehead was already beaded with sweat, and a trail of sweat was flowing along her left cheek down onto her delicate neck.

She wiped the sweat away with her left hand, and her round cheeks were as red as a pair of ripe apples, but she didn't slow down in the slightest.

Right at this moment, a harsh male voice suddenly rang out in the distance. "Stop, you little witch!"

The little girl shuddered upon hearing this, and she was so frightened that her face instantly turned pale. She raised the pellet drum in her right hand before giving it a vigorous turn, and her lips fluttered slightly, upon which a layer of faint azure light immediately appeared over the surface of the drum.

As the pellets clattered onto the surface of the drum, a burst of azure light erupted forth, landing on a patch of tall grass right in front of her.

A layer of azure light immediately appeared over the surface of the tall grass, but the light vanished in a flash, having seemingly accomplished nothing.

The little girl turned the pellet drum a few more times, and one burst of azure light shot forth after another with each strike of the drum, landing on the tall grass around her, which also flashed momentarily with azure light before returning to normal.

After doing all of that, the little girl's face had paled even further, but she had no time to rest as she dove headfirst into the tall grass.

Not long after the little girl concealed herself within the tall grass, a dust cloud rose up over 100 feet away, and a figure sped forth at an incredible speed before arriving in front of the patch of tall grass.

The figure was a tall and burly man with a coarse beard who appeared to be in his forties. He was holding a shimmering podao in one hand, presenting a menacing sight to behold. [1]

His gaze fell upon the trail of petite footprints in front of the tall grass, and he immediately rushed toward the tall grass with his podao raised, but right at this moment, a burst of azure light flashed up ahead, and five or six long azure snakes shot out at once, opening their serpentine mouths to expose their sharp fangs as they pounced at the burly man.

The man faltered slightly upon seeing this, then quickly pulled out a talisman with his left hand before slapping it onto his own body. A white light barrier instantly emerged, and at the same time, he slashed the podao in his right hand through the air amid a loud buzzing sound.

A burst of light that was several feet in length swept forth from the podao, and three of the oncoming azure snakes were instantly sliced into two by the attack. As for the remaining azure snakes, they were repelled by the white light barrier around the burly man, following which they were also sliced in half by the man's podao.

In the blink of an eye, all of the azure snakes had been vanquished by the burly man, and their true forms were revealed to be several bunches of tall grass.

The burly man harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and he was just about to continue rushing into the tall grass when his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he stopped in his tracks as he withdrew his podao.

A burst of rustling rang out from behind him, and two figures quickly arrived on the scene.

One of them was a tall and thin daoist priest who was wearing a slightly tattered gray robe and holding a white horsetail whisk in his hand, while the other was a short and well-built man with a long face that was carrying several bruises, and a head of disheveled hair.

"Are you alright, fellow daoists?" the burly man asked as he turned to the two men.

"As expected of the daughter of a demonic fox, she's truly a cunning little witch. Fellow Daoist Qi and I were a little too impatient to chase her down, and we almost fell into her trap, but thankfully, we managed to escape relatively unharmed. Why have you stopped here, Fellow Daoist Yan? And where is that witch right now?" the long-faced man asked with a puzzled expression.

The burly man offered no reply as he pointed at the tall grass up ahead, and the trail of petite footprints in front of the tall grass was still clearly visible.

"Then what are we waiting for? Let's capture her and end this!" The long-faced man stepped forward to enter the tall grass as he spoke.

"She's been on the run for a day and a night, so I'm sure she's close to completely spent at this point, but she's very adept at using wood-attribute illusion techniques, which means this patch of tall grass to her will be like water to a fish. I fear that it would be unwise to rush in after her recklessly," the daoist priest mused as his eyes narrowed slightly.

The long-faced man hesitated slightly upon hearing this, then stopped in his tracks as he said in an indignant manner, "Then are we just going to let her get away? She's already this cunning at such a young age, if we allow her to grow to full maturity, who knows how much of a menace she could become?"

"We are enforcers of justice, so we naturally can't shirk our duty and allow this demon to escape. There's no way we'll just let her slip away right under our noses!" the burly man declared in a righteous voice.

"It sounds like you've already worked out a strategy, Fellow Daoist Yan," the daoist priest remarked.

"This patch of tall grass covers quite a large area. If we enter it blindly, we'll still be able to capture that demon in the end, but it's most likely going to be a huge hassle. I heard that Fellow Daoist Feng recently purchased a Firecloud Talisman, and as we all know, Fellow Daoist Qi's mastery of the Windlure Technique is unmatched.

“ With those two things working together, we'll be able to incinerate all of the tall grass in no time, and that demon will have nowhere to hide then," the burly man said.

The long-faced man was silent for a moment, then said, "Using my Firecloud Talisman is not out of the question, but after we capture that demonic fox, I'm taking its hide, you two can share everything else. What do you say?"

"No, that demonic fox must be captured alive," the burly man immediately refused with a shake of his head.

The long-faced man's expression darkened slightly upon hearing this, and he asked in a cold voice, "So you're asking me to sacrifice my Firecloud Talisman for nothing? This is a mid-tier elementary talisman that cost me a good chunk of my fortune!"

"No need to get agitated, Fellow Daoist Feng. If I'm not mistaken, Fellow Daoist Yan should be an outer sect disciple of the Blood Sword Sect. The Blood Sword Sect recently released a mission for the demonic fox to be captured alive, and the one who completes the mission will not only become an inner sect disciple , they'll also receive a reward of one Bloodcry Pill and 1,000 spirit stones, isn't that right?" the daoist priest said as he turned to the burly man with a meaningful look in his eyes.

The burly man's expression remained unchanged as he said, "I didn't think you'd know so much about our Blood Sword Sect, Fellow Daoist Qi. Let's not waste any time by talking in circles. If you two can help me capture this demonic fox alive, you can share the spirit stone reward evenly among the two of you. What do you say?"

"I have no objections to that proposal," the daoist priest replied as he casually laid his horsetail whisk over his own arm.

"In that case, let's not delay any further." The long-faced man pulled out a talisman as he spoke, and he took a wistful glance at it before tossing it forward and chanting an incantation.

A layer of red light immediately appeared over the surface of the talisman, following which it exploded into a cloud of crimson flames. It was like a fiery force of nature as it descended from the sky toward the tall grass down below.

As soon as the tall grass came into contact with the cloud of fire, it immediately erupted into flames.

At the same time, the daoist priest uttered a daoist prayer before abruptly sweeping his horsetail whisk through the air.

A loud howling sound immediately rang out as several gusts of fierce wind appeared out of thin air before proliferating outward in a fan-shaped wave.

The flames were fanned by the wind, rapidly spreading through the tall grass like an unstoppable wave, and dense black smoke rose up into the air while ashes flew in all directions.

The trio stared intently into the sea of fire in an unblinking manner, and all of a sudden, the daoist priest declared, "Over there!"

At the same time, he shot forth toward a certain direction like a speeding arrow, and with a flick of his horsetail whisk, faint azure light began to glow on the surface of its hairs.

The burly man and the long-faced man were both spurred into action upon hearing this, and they followed along closely behind the daoist priest.

Around 200 to 300 feet in front of them, a petite figure suddenly sprang out of the tall grass, which was quickly being eaten away by the sea of fire, and it was none other than the little girl from before.

At this moment, there were already many holes in her light yellow robe, and her face had also been blackened by the dense smoke.

The field of tall grass that she had been hiding in had previously covered quite a large area, and in order to not make any sound that would draw attention to herself, she had been carefully advancing through the tall grass while occasionally changing directions. There was no sound coming from behind her, so she had thought that she was in the clear, but never did she think that her pursuers would use fire to force her out.

A horrified look appeared on the little girl's face, and she rushed away as quickly as she could in a bind panic, coughing incessantly all the while.

However, she wasn't able to get very far at all before she felt a gust of cold wind sweep toward her from behind, following which countless azure threads emerged all around her.

Almost at the exact same moment, a whistling sound rang out overhead, and a black net that was around 10 feet in size descended upon her from above.

The panic in the little girl's eyes turned into despair, but all of a sudden, she caught sight of a small and withered tree that was over 100 feet in front of her. Her eyes immediately lit up, and she bit down forcefully onto the tip of her own tongue.

"We've got her now!"

The long-faced man was the slowest of the three, but he could see that the burly man and the daoist priest had worked together to trap the little girl, and he was naturally ecstatic.

The large swathe of azure threads swept over a distance of several dozen feet before surging back to ensnare the little girl, and at the same time, the black net in the sky also fell upon her.

However, right at this moment, the body of the immobilized little girl suddenly disintegrated into azure light before transforming into a small tree.

"She used a Wood Substitution Technique!"

The expressions of the burly man and the daoist priest immediately darkened upon witnessing this development, and they both descended from above.

"Over there!" The long-faced man hurriedly pointed at a spot up ahead.

The small and withered tree that had been standing there just a second ago suddenly blurred before transforming into the pellet-drum-wielding little girl, and she turned to take a glance behind her before continuing to flee the scene.

"Don't let her get away!"

Perhaps it was due to the fact that she had just unleashed a Wood Substitution Technique, but the little girl's face was now completely devoid of color, and her footsteps were also becoming heavier and more laborious. As a result, she was beginning to stumble regularly, so her speed was naturally severely impacted, and her three pursuers were quickly closing down the gap between them.

"Ah!"

All of a sudden, the little girl yelped as she was tripped over by a rock, and she flew forward before crashing into a huge gray rock that was around 10 feet tall before falling heavily onto the ground.

"Why don't you keep running?" the long-faced man goaded with a gleeful expression.

The three men slowed down, and they formed a triangle before slowly approaching her from three different directions, cutting off all avenues for escape.

At this point, the three men had already been chasing the little girl for a day and a night, and along the way, they had fallen for many of her cunning tricks, so they were naturally feeling very resentful and indignant. Out of the three, the long-faced man was feeling particularly vindictive, having just lost a Firecloud Talisman to the cause.

As the three men approached the little girl, she pressed her back tightly against the huge rock behind her before curling up into a ball, but her eyes were filled with resentment.

The three men were naturally completely unfazed by her hateful expression, and the long-faced man took a step forward as he raised a hand with a sinister expression.

"I can't kill you, but I'm going to teach you a good lesson for making a fool out of us!"

Right at this moment, an unexpected turn of events unfolded.

A loud crack rang out, and countless thin cracks appeared over the surface of the huge rock that the little girl was pressed up tightly against.

Many small rock shards came cascading down onto the little girl's head, causing her to flinch involuntarily.

The long-faced man was quite taken aback to see this, and he stopped what he was doing, keeping his right hand suspended in mid-air. The attention of the other two men was also temporarily drawn away from the little girl as they turned to inspect the giant rock behind her.

The three men watched as the cracks on the surface of the huge quickly spread like a system of cobwebs, and many shards of rock began to split off before falling onto the ground.

The little girl clearly wasn't expecting this strange turn of events, either, and she immediately closed her eyes in f e ar as she threw her arms over her own head, not daring to move even a single inch.

Finally, the giant rock completely shattered amid a rumbling boom, and large chunks of stone flew in all directions before landing on the ground, raising up large clouds of yellow dust.

The three men were all quite startled by this, and they retreated a few steps with wary expressions, but their eyes remained firmly fixed on what remained of the huge rock.

"Wh... What's that supposed to be?" the long-faced man stuttered with a stunned expression.

As the dust gradually settled, it became clear that the giant rock was already gone, and it had been replaced by a male figure who was remarkably tall and broad .

The man was wearing an azure robe, and his face and hair were coated in a layer of gray powdered rock, indicating that he seemed to have been residing within the giant rock. Even through the gray powder, it was still possible to make out a set of unremarkable facial features and a complexion that was slightly on the darker side.

The man was staring forward with a blank expression, seemingly a little slow and dull, but he was significantly taller than even the burly man.

The little girl and the three men were all astonished by this sudden turn of events.

[1]. A podao is a Chinese single-edged infantry weapon that is basically a Chinese broadsword attached to a long wooden handle.

[Back]

Chapter 2: Brother Rock

"Brother Rock!"

Right as the three men were looking on with stunned expressions, an elated voice suddenly rang out.

The little girl had already clambered up from the ground, and she immediately threw her arms around the imposing young man who had just emerged from the massive rock.

Given her short stature, the little girl's head only reached the young man's waist, and her delicate little arms were wrapped tightly around one of the young man's legs. Most of her body was concealed behind the young man, and she was looking up at him with her large, watery eyes.

The three men faltered slightly upon hearing this, then exchanged a bewildered glance before turning their attention back to the young man, only to find that he was displaying no reaction whatsoever to the little girl's voice, and he was still staring blankly at the three of them, much to their confusion.

A sense of unease welled up in the little girl's heart upon seeing this, and she frantically tugged on the young man's leg as she sobbed, "Brother Rock, I've finally found you! Those bad people are trying to capture Le'er! You have to help me beat them, Brother Rock!"

This time, the young man seemed to have heard the little girl, and he lowered his head slightly.

The little girl looked into the young man's eyes, only to find that they were still completely blank and vacant, and her heart sank even further.

In contrast, this was a very encouraging sight for the three men.

They had already released their spiritual sen se over the young man, only to find that there were no signs of magic power in his body whatsoever. There were only two possible explanations for this, the first of which was that the young man really was just a mortal who possessed no cultivation base at all, and the second possibility was that he was using a special secret technique or magic tool to conceal his magic power.

The strange circumstances leading up to the young man's emergence and the fact that the little girl was calling out to him for help made the three feel as if the latter possibility were more plausible, and there was a good chance that the man was perhaps also a demon.

The daoist priest rested his horsetail whisk on his arm as his gaze roamed back and forth between the young man and the little girl, and it was unclear what he was thinking.

At this point, the long-faced man had already lowered his right hand, and he had also taken a step backward to rejoin his two companions. At the same time, an object had fallen into his left hand, which was concealed up his sleeve, and he was still staring intently at the little girl.

The burly man gave his two companions a meaningful look, then declared, "May I ask your name, Fellow Daoist? I am Yan Cheng of the Blood Sword Sect, and I'm working with these two fellow daoists to capture this demonic fox. If this has nothing to do with you, then please be on your way."

The little girl was very alarmed to hear this, and she looked up at the young man with an imploring expression.

The young man slowly raised his head to face the burly man with a wooden expression, and he remained completely silent.

A hint of anger flashed through the burly man's eyes upon seeing this, but he suppressed it before repeating what he had just said, raising his voice a little on this occasion.

The little girl opened her mouth slightly, but didn't say anything. However, her palms were sweating profusely as she continued to hold tightly onto the leg of the young man's pants with her little hands.

The young man continued to offer no response.

The long-faced young man turned slightly to the side, then transmitted his voice to his companions as he said, "There appears to be something wrong with him. As opposed to wasting time here, why don't we..."

"In this area, the only people who would remain so calm after hearing the name of the Blood Sword Sect have to be complete idiots or unfathomably powerful. In any case, he's displaying an intention to protect that demon, so no one can say anything even if we kill him. Of course, the final decision is up to you, Fellow Daoist Yan," the daoist priest replied through voice transmission as his eyes narrowed slightly.

The burly man nodded in response, and a cold look appeared in his eyes as he tightened his grip around his podao. "Why do you not speak, Fellow Daoist? Are you looking down on us?"

His voice was like rumbling thunder, echoing incessantly across the barren plains, causing the nearby air to buzz incessantly.

A fearful look appeared on the little girl's face upon hearing this, and she reflexively let go of the young man's legs before tightening her grip on her pellet drum.

The young man continued to display no reaction, and it was as if he were deaf.

"Fine. If you insist on siding with the demonic girl, then we'll just have to take you down along with her!"

A fierce gleam flashed through the burly man's eyes, and his podao suddenly began to glow with blinding white light. At the same time, he raised his other hand, and a burst of black light shot forth in a flash, rising up into the air before descending as a huge black net.

The little girl was greatly alarmed by this, and she hurriedly tried to scurry away, but she was too close and it was already too late for her to get away.

The huge net descended like a dark cloud before rapidly closing in from all directions, encompassing the young man within it as well. At the same time, a flash of light emerged within the net, and a gleaming silver hook appeared on every single knot of the net, looking extremely sharp and menacing.

The little girl screamed as she opened her mouth to release a cloud of blood mist onto the pellet drum while turning it vigorously at the same time.

The sound of the pellet drum rang out, and azure light flashed over the little girl before her body abruptly disintegrated, transforming into a piece of dead wood.

The little girl then re-emerged out of thin air over 100 feet away before falling onto the ground. Around a dozen wounds had been inflicted onto her arms and legs from the hooked spikes on the black net, causing her to bleed profusely.

She rolled over before struggling laboriously to her feet, but she only managed to take a single step before she slumped feebly onto the ground again. Her face was deathly pale, and she was gasping for air.

At this point, the little girl was clearly a spent force, and the burly man didn't even bother to pay any attention to her. Instead, he made a hand seal with one hand, and the black net around the young man abruptly tightened.

At the same time, the daoist priest sprang up into the air, releasing around a dozen translucent flying needles with a flick of his wrist, and the needles shot forth like lightning toward various vital regions all over the young man's body.

"Look out!"

The little girl was unable to get up, so all she could do was yell frantically in the young man's direction.

A string of metallic clangs rang out, and as soon as the azure flying needles struck the young man's body, all of them were repelled away as if they had struck a rock.

"How is that possible?" the daoist priest exclaimed as he descended lightly onto the ground.

Even if the young man's body were actually made of stone, those flying arrows should've been able to easily pierce through him.

All of a sudden, a streak of golden light flew past the daoist priest before striking the young man's throat with vicious power.

"Hehe, what a fool! No one's ever taken a Golden Wasp Spike of mine and..." The long-faced man was slowly lowering his raised arm with a cruel smile on his face, but before he had a chance to finish what he was saying, the golden spike that had struck the young man's throat abruptly exploded into specks of golden light.

"Impossible!"

The long-faced man was left looking as if he had seen a ghost, and the burly man was also completely incredulous to see this.

The sharp hooks on the black net were capable of tearing through metal with ease, but they were unable to leave even the slightest scratch on the young man's body.

Right as the three men were looking on with disbelief in their eyes, the young man finally reacted to the string of attacks that had just been directed at him.

He slowly lowered his head to look at the net that was clinging to his body, and he seemed to find it a little cumbersome. He grabbed onto the net with both hands, and bursts of spiritual light erupted from its surface before it was torn apart with ease as if it were made from paper.

The two halves of the net gently drifted down onto the ground, and both the long-faced man and the daoist priest were so shocked to see this that their eyes were on the verge of popping out of their sockets.

Not far away, the little girl was also looking on with astonishment in her eyes, temporarily forgetting the excruciating pain that she was in.

"How dare you destroy my magic tool!" the burly man roared with fury, greatly anguished by the loss of the black net.

The black net was a powerful magic tool that he had borrowed from a good friend in the sect at a hefty price, so it was only natural that he was so furious to see it destroyed here.

The burly man gritted his teeth as he glowered at the young man with a livid expression, and he extended the index finger and middle finger of his right hand, upon which a purple talisman appeared between her fingertips out of thin air. He tossed the talisman forward as he chanted an incantation, and the talisman immediately flew through the air, arriving directly above the young man's head.

Immediately thereafter, the talisman exploded to form a dense black cloud.

The sound of rumbling thunderclaps rang out as light flashed within the black cloud, and a bolt of silver lightning that was thick as a bowl came crashing down.

The bolt of lightning struck the young man's body with a resounding boom, and countless arcs of lightning sprang forth in all directions, bombarding the ground around him to create a series of charred black craters.

The little girl closed her eyes in fear amid the rumbling thunderclaps, and somehow, she was able to muster up the strength to shift herself back slightly by pushing off against the ground with her hands, allowing her to just barely avoid being struck by the stray arcs of lightning by the tightest of margins.

She opened her eyes with lingering fear in her heart, and her mouth immediately sprang open in shock once again at the sight that she was greeted by.

The young man was standing in silence with countless black charred craters around him, but there was not even so much as a single scratch on his body.

The burly man was very alarmed to see this, but he didn't skip a beat as he continued to make hand seals while quickly chanting an incantation.

"Seal!"

Another bolt of silver lightning came crashing down above, but during its descent, it suddenly transformed into a series of intertwining lightning chains that wrapped themselves around the young man's body at an incredible speed, binding him firmly into place.

"What are you waiting for, fellow daoists?" the burly man roared as he raised his podao, and a layer of red light immediately appeared over its surface, following which he sprang forward with the tip of his podao aimed directly at the young man's face.

The long-faced man was initially also shocked by the fact that the young man was completely unharmed by the lightning, but he was ecstatic to see this, and he immediately made a hand seal before vanishing on the spot as a gentle breeze.

In the next instant, a gust of fierce wind was swept up beside the young man, and the long-faced man emerged out of thin air with a black metal ruler in his hand. There were several flashing white runes on the ruler's surface, and it was swung viciously toward the young man's shoulder, accompanied by a gust of ferocious wind.

Meanwhile, the daoist priest was looking on with a cautious expression, and instead of rushing forward like his two companions, he retreated a couple of steps before waving a hand through the air. A ball of crimson light flew out of his sleeve, then circled around in the air at an incredible speed before hurtling silently toward the back of the young man's head.

Even though the three of them had all unleashed their attacks at different times, their teamwork was flawless, and it was clear that this wasn't their first time working together.

The young man's eyes remained as vacant as ever, and he continued to remain completely still on the spot, seemingly unable to even detect the attacks that were being directed at him.

An elated look appeared in the burly man's eyes upon seeing this, and he injected even more power into his podao.

However, in the next instant, he suddenly felt something constrict around his wrist. As it turned out, he had been caught by the wrist by a large hand that felt as if it were made from steel, and not only was he unable to thrust his podao even an inch further, his entire body was also stopped cold in its tracks.

The young man had reached out to catch the burly man's podao-wielding arm by the wrist, and he had done so at such an unfathomable speed that no one was able to see his movements.

The burly man pulled back his arm with all his might, but it was completely locked into place, and it was as if he had been caught by an immovable mountain. His heart immediately sank upon seeing this, but a cruel smile then suddenly appeared on his face.

In the next instant, the long-faced man's metal ruler and the ball of crimson light unleashed by the daoist priest struck the young man's shoulder and the back of his head, respectively. Both blows landed almost at the exact same time, and piercing black light erupted from the metal ruler, while the ball of crimson light exploded into a large cloud of dense blood mist that encompassed the young man's entire head within it, giving off a nauseating stench.

The long-faced man burst into triumphant laughter upon seeing this, but in the next instant, he felt a rush of heat travel through his hand, and a burst of inexplicably immense power erupted out of the young man's body, traveling directly into his body along the metal ruler.

"No!"

A horrified expression appeared in the long-faced man's eyes, and he was involuntarily sent flying into the distance. A string of gruesome cracks rang out as he tumbled down onto the ground like a ragdoll, and countless bones had been shattered in his body.

Blood was also gushing incessantly out of his mouth along with fragments of internal organs, and by the time he drew to a rest, his entire body resembled a tattered rucksack that was riddled with holes, and he was as dead as dead could be.

"Impossible! How... Argh!"

The burly man was astonished to see this, yet before he had a chance to do anything, the hand that was locked around his wrist suddenly moved ever so slightly. Immediately thereafter, a burst of strange tremors rang through his body, instantly shattering every single one of his bones. The pain was so excruciating that it was like having his skin and flesh torn away by 1,000 cuts, and he couldn't help but let loose a bloodcurdling howl.

In the next instant, his body was sent flying involuntarily into the air, having been hurled viciously toward a large rock nearby.

Another bloodcurdling scream rang out as the burly man's body exploded into a pile of mincemeat against the huge rock.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the daoist priest was horrified to see this.

He immediately turned around and frantically slapped five or six talismans of different colors onto his own body while fleeing with all his might.

However, he was only able to take a few steps before the air abruptly constricted around him, and the several types of protective spiritual light radiating from his body were snuffed out in a flash. Immediately thereafter, his entire body exploded into scraps of blood and flesh that came raining down from the sky , as if it had just been crushed by an invisible giant hand.

Meanwhile, the young man swallowed the cloud of dense black mist around his head, revealing his wooden features once again.

Chapter 3: Departure

The little girl was staring blankly at everything unfolding before her with her mouth gaped open, seemingly still yet to recover from the shock of what she had just seen.

She inspected the remains of her three tormentors with a dazed expression, and all of a sudden, she collapsed onto her backside as tears began to flow down her face.

Initially, she was only sobbing quietly, but she quickly began to cry louder and louder, as if she had thought of something tragic.

Soon, the floodgates completely broke down, and her bawling once again broke the silence in this once-peaceful area. It was like a heart-wrenching song of grief and tragedy, expressing to the heavens the tribulations and injustice in the human world.

After an indeterminate period of time, the bawling drew to an abrupt halt.

The little girl had already risen to her feet again, and her hands were balled up into tight fists. The soot and blood on her face had already been washed away by her tears, revealing her delicate features once again, but this time, there seemed to be something in her eyes that wasn't there before.

All of a sudden, she rushed toward another huge gray rock that was up ahead not far away.

At the foot of the large rock was a mangled body laying in a pool of blood, and one could just barely make out that the body belonged to the burly man. At this point, he was already long dead. Several dozen feet away from the giant rock was a male corpse that resembled a pile of sludge, and it belonged to the long-faced man from before.

As for the daoist priest, his entire body had exploded in the face of the punch that the young man had thrown from afar, so there was nothing left of his remains aside from scraps of flesh and blood in the nearby area.

The little girl leaped over to the foot of the huge rock, then raised both of her hands, and azure nails that were several inches in length abruptly grew out of her fingers, using which she viciously ravaged the burly man's remains.

Her nails whistled through the air, releasing one azure claw projection after another, all of which struck the man's already severely mangled body.

Blood splattered in all directions, and the man's remains were instantly reduced to a pile of broken flesh.

However, the little girl seemed to have been yet to vent all of her resentment, and she blasted a burst of green flames out of her mouth to incinerate the man's remains into ashes.

Immediately thereafter, she did the exact same thing to the long-faced man's body, and only after that did she finally relent.

After doing all of that, her knees gave out from under her, and she fell onto her backside again as she panted heavily, having just exhausted all of the slight amount of magic power her body had just recovered.

The little girl took a moment to compose herself, then knelt down toward a certain direction as she murmured, "Dada, Mama, Big Brother, Big Sister, one of these foul bandits from the Blood Sword Sect is finally dead.

“ I wasn't the one to kill him, but a tiny amount of justice has finally been served for what they did to you. Rest assured, so long as I still draw breath, there will come a day when I will go to Bloodlight Mountain and erase the Blood Sword Sect from the face of this world!"

Tears began to well up in her eyes again as she spoke, but she forced them back, not allowing herself to shed them.

"I won't cry anymore. Dada always says that crybabies never grow up. I have to grow up faster!"

Only after a long while was the little girl able to suppress the sobs that were fighting to break out of her chest, and she stood up again before taking a glance at the storage bags left behind by her three deceased pursuers.

A hint of disgust surfaced in her eyes, but after a brief hesitation, she still decided to pick up all of the storage bags.

As the sun moved westward, the sky began to dim, and the wind also grew stronger, howling incessantly as the air temperature began to drop.

Looking at her barren surroundings, the little girl was becoming a little afraid, and she curled up slightly before reflexively sidling up closer to the only other living person in the area, the young man.

After throwing that punch to put an end to the daoist priest's life, the young man fell still again, standing on the spot in a wooden manner as he looked down blankly at his own feet, seemingly completely oblivious to what the little girl had just done.

"Brother Rock..." the little girl called out in a slightly hesitant voice, and she didn't dare to get too close to him.

The young man displayed no reaction.

"Brother Rock, my name is Liu Le'er. Thank you for killing those three bad people just now. Even though you're also a human, Dada told me that there are good people even in the human race," the little girl said in a slightly fearful voice.

The young man finally displayed a slight reaction to her voice, and he raised his head slightly to take a glance at her.

The reflection of the little girl appeared in his pupils, and a faint gleam seemed to have flashed through his dazed eyes, but they quickly became glazed over again. However, his eyes were still fixed on Liu Le'er.

Liu Le'er was quite startled by this, and she hurriedly took a few steps backward.

However, all the young man did was stare blankly at her without doing anything else, remaining as still as a statue.

Liu Le'er heaved an internal sigh of relief, and she became even more convinced that there was something wrong with the young man's head. She then gradually mustered up some courage and drew closer to the young man, examining him with a curious expression.

She had been in a state of panic before, so she didn't get a chance to take a close look, and only after approaching the young man was she able to catch a clearer glimpse of him.

The young man was tall and broad with long and slim fingers. His body wasn't particularly muscular, but it struck the beholder with the sense that it contained limitless power.

Even though his eyes were dazed and soulless, his pupils were incredibly black, almost as if they were capable of sucking in one's soul if they were to look into his eyes for too long. His exposed skin was slightly dark in complexion and extremely smooth . Despite the fierce battle that he had just endured, not a single scratch had been inflicted onto his body.

His azure clothes appeared to be completely unremarkable, but they had also managed to remain unscathed in the wake of the attacks that he had been struck by.

All of this, in addition to the fact that the young man had just devoured that cloud of blood mist like it was nothing, indicated that he was definitely no ordinary person, and he certainly wasn't a mortal.

How could a mortal possibly have killed three cultivators wielding magic tools with such ridiculous ease?

The little girl sized up the young man with an absentminded expression, and she became more and more relaxed as the young man continued to display no reaction. Having just survived that grueling ordeal, her childish curiosity seemed to have returned, and she walked around the young man in a circle.

The young man's gaze remained fixed on Liu Le'er the entire time, as if there were something about her that attracted his attention.

Perhaps it was because the young man ha d saved her life and killed her three tormentors for her, but the more she looked at him, the closer and more intimate she felt with him.

All of a sudden, Liu Le'er caught sight of a small dark green accessory that was peeking out from behind the young man's collar. The accessory was glittering and translucent, and she couldn't figure out what it was.

She wanted to peel back his robe slightly to take a closer look, but she didn't dare to do so.

Right at this moment, the wind suddenly grew a lot stronger, and a thick blanket of dark clouds appeared in the sky, causing the surrounding area to become even darker.

A thick bolt of lightning tore through the dark clouds, illuminating the entire sky, and this was followed closely by a deafening thunderclap and the arrival of a heavy storm.

"Argh!"

Liu Le'er let loose an alarmed yelp as she reflexively sought shelter from the young man's body, throwing her arms around his leg as she trembled delicately.

She was a demonic fox, and she had an innate sense of fear toward natural lightning.

Another faint gleam surfaced in the young man's eyes, but once again, it quickly faded, he bent over slightly, using his large frame to cover Liu Le'er. It was unclear whether this was an intentional gesture or not, but in doing so, he was keeping out the rain and wind for her.

A hint of warmth welled up in the little girl's heart, and she no longer feared the rain, wind, and lightning. Instead, she was struck by a sense of warm serenity, much like the feeling of being in her father's arms.

The storm left just as quickly as it arrived, and it didn't take long before the dark clouds faded, and the refreshing scent of petrichor began to spread through the air.

Liu Le'er shook off the rain on her body, then giggled as she latched onto the young man's hand and brushed off the water that had gathered on his clothes.

She didn't know what material the young man's azure clothes were made from, but the rainwater that fell upon it formed a series of beads that were completely unable to seep into his clothes, much like one would expect to see on a lotus leaf.

As always, the young man displayed no reaction to what the little girl was doing, allowing her to do as she pleased with him.

"Brother Rock, you still haven't told me your name yet," Liu Le'er said as she tugged gently on his arm, trying to get him to sit down.

The young man slowly obliged and sat down, but he was still as silent as ever.

"Why are you here, Brother Rock?"

"Brother Rock, that punch you threw at the end was so strong! Can you teach me?"

"Brother Rock..."

Liu Le'er was determined to break the young man's silence, and she tried several different ways to communicate with him, but the young man displayed no reaction no matter what she said, and she was left feeling rather disappointed.

The little girl was silent for a moment before making up her mind, and she grabbed onto one of the young man's large hands as she implored, "Brother Rock, I don't know who you are, but you've killed someone from the Blood Sword Sect, so it's best for you to leave this place with me."

The young man was still as dazed and disoriented as ever, but with Liu Le'er making a series of gestures to illustrate what she was saying, he seemed to have understood what was being told, and he finally departed with the little girl.

Dusk slowly fell, and the dying sun basked the sky in a blood-red hue.

With the sun casting its final rays of light upon the landscape, the barren plains were bathed in resplendent golden light.

Two figures, one tall and one short, were making their way toward the setting sun, getting further and further away. The wind was picking up the sound of Liu Le'er's cheerful voice and carrying it into the distance.

"Brother Rock, I know you're really strong, but there are a lot more bad people in the Blood Sword Sect!"

"It's getting late, you must be hungry, right?"

"Once we get out of here, I'll catch a few wild birds and roast them for you. My cooking skills are pretty good!"

"Brother Rock, I'm going to treat you as my real brother from now on!"

Chapter 4: Interdependence

In a primitive forest on a mountain, glacial winds were howling incessantly, and the heavy snowfall had covered everything in a pristine white blanket.

Even though the sun hadn't completely set yet, the forest had already become extremely dim amid the heavy snow.

There was a winding mountain path in the forest that wasn't all that clear to begin with, and it was virtually unidentifiable under the thick blanket of snow. However, there was a fire that had been lit at the end of the mountain, providing a slight hint of warmth in this glacial landscape of ice and snow.

The flame had been lit in the only mountain god shrine in the entire forest.

Due to how inaccessible the shrine was, it had already been abandoned and unvisited for many years. The gatehouse and walls of the outer courtyard had already all collapsed, leaving only a dilapidated main hall standing in a lonesome fashion.

The gate of the main hall had long been absent, and there was only a tattered straw mat hanging on the doorframe to keep out some of the wind and snow.

Through the holes in the straw mat, one could see that aside from cluttered weeds and stones in the empty hall, there was a figure seated with his legs crossed.

This was a tall and broad young man in an azure robe, and even though he was sitting on the ground, his back was ramrod straight. However, his face was completely wooden and expressionless, much like the dilapidated mountain god statue behind him.

The young man's arms were hanging naturally down onto his lap, and Liu Le'er was laying in the cradle formed by his hanging arms.

Right at this moment, a faint moan suddenly rang out in front of the young man's chest.

Liu Le'er's rubbed her tiny head against the young man's arm, and her face, which was previously buried against his chest, peeked out slightly from the crook of his arm.

At this moment, her delicate features were tainted by an unnatural flush, and even though she was sound asleep, her brows were tightly knitted together, and tears were flowing incessantly down her face from her tightly shut eyelids. It seemed that she was having a terrible nightmare.

"No... Don't..."

Liu Le'er reflexively tightened her grip on the young man's arm as she moaned in her sleep.

One of her legs had also been kicked out from the young man's arms, and she was occasionally twisting around in a disturbed manner, clearly suffering greatly from whatever it was that she was seeing in her dream. Soon, she buried her face back into the young man's chest.

The young man was looking straight up ahead, but he seemed to have sensed the little girl's movement and lowered his head to check on her. A slight hint of confusion appeared in his vacant eyes, but they were still mostly vacant and dazed.

"Brother... Rock..."

The little girl continued to talk in her sleep in a barely audible voice.

Perhaps it was because the young man's face was being illuminated by the light of the fire, but at this moment, his features seemed to have become softer and more gentle, and there seemed to be an extra spark in his vacant eyes.

He remained seated on the ground, but slowly swiveled around on the spot until his back was facing the entrance of the hall, shielding the little girl from the cold wind. He then gently tucked the little girl's leg back into his arms before tightening his embrace around her slightly.

The little girl wiggled slightly in his arms and buried her head deeper into his chest, following which her movements gradually subsided, and her breathing returned to a slow and even rhythm.

At this point, it was already completely dark outside, and the wind and snow had gradually abated slightly.

……

Halfway up a lush mountain that was over 1,000 feet in height was a cave that stood at over 30 feet tall, and a tall and broad young man was standing with his back facing the cave.

Liu Le'er was standing behind the young man with one hand gripping onto the corner of his robe while the other arm was wrapped around his leg. Half of her face was peeking out from behind him as she cast her gaze forward, and her complexion was a little pale from fear and anxiety.

Several dozen feet in front of the two stood a giant gray bear that was over twice the height of an adult human, and it was standing on its hind legs with its front paws raised in a menacing display.

There was a single jagged horn on its head, and the lips around its cavernous mouth had been peeled back to reveal two rows of sharp fangs, while a trail of putrid and slightly viscous drool was dribbling down the corner of its mouth as it snarled in intimidation.

The young man was far taller and more imposing than the average person, but in the face of this giant bear, even he was made to look like a small child.

However, he was completely unfazed by this situation, and he was staring blankly at the massive bear with a pair of inky-black eyes that were almost completely devoid of luster.

After staring back at the young man for a while, a humanized look of fear suddenly appeared on the giant bear's face for some reason, and it let loose a low roar before taking a couple of steps backward, then fell onto its front limbs before fleeing as quickly as it could on all fours.

Liu Le'er's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and she heaved a sigh of relief, then scratched her own head with a rather perplexed expression. She stepped around the young man before raising her head to look up at his face, but even after staring at his blank and wooden face for a long while, she was rather disappointed to find that she couldn't spot any changes in his expression.

"Brother Rock, I know you're not an ordinary person. It's a pity that you can't speak. Otherwise, it would be great if you could talk to me."

Liu Le'er heaved a forlorn sigh that was rather unbefitting of someone of her age, then latched onto the young man's hand before leading him into the cave behind them.

The young man didn't say anything, but his gaze fell upon the little girl's delicate hand that was holding onto his own, and he allowed himself to be led into the cave.

……

On a vast grassland, spring was in full swing, and the area was teeming with life. New grass was already beginning to grow, and the unique, refreshing fragrance of grass was permeating across the entire grassland.

A little girl who appeared to be around eight or nine years of age was holding a bunch of thin vines that were riddled with small yellow flowers, and she was straddled atop the shoulders of a tall and broad young man as he made his way forward at a leisurely pace.

Compared with two years ago, the young man hadn't changed at all, and he was still wearing that same azure robe, but Liu Le'er had undergone some significant changes.

She had grown a lot taller, and her face had also lost some of its childish chubbiness. There was already a hint of gentle seduction in her eyes that was very rare to see in girls her age. It was clear that she was going to grow up to be a stunning beauty, perhaps the type that wars would be waged over.

Her fingers were moving rapidly as she wove the floral vines in her hands while humming a cheerful tune, and her voice was as crisp and alluring as the song of a yellow warbler.

"Done!"

Before she had a chance to finish her song, she had already finished weaving a beautiful floral wreath.

She held up the wreath with both hands, turning it to examine it from all angles, then nodded with a pleased expression before placing it onto the young man's head in a joyful manner.

The size of the wreath was perfect, and the part where the flowers were most concentrated was sitting directly above the young man's forehead.

The young man seemed to have detected what was happening, and he reached up to gently touch the floral wreath before slowly withdrawing his hand.

Liu Le'er was already accustomed to the young man's dull reactions, and she lowered her head to glance down at the thin green string around his neck. A mischievous grin appeared on her face as she quickly reached down to grab onto the string and lift it up, but the young man reflexively grabbed onto the dark green accessory attached to the string as if it were second nature for him, refusing to let it go.

"You do this every time, Brother Rock! Why are you so stingy? I just want to take a look at it!" Liu Le'er grumbled as she puffed out her cheeks in displeasure.

Despite what she was saying, she wasn't actually angry. Throughout the past two years, the young man hadn't spoken a single word to her, and aside from the very minor reactions he gave in response to external stimulus, the only times that he reacted in any meaningful way was when that accessory that he wore around his neck came under threat.

It was exactly because of this that Liu Le'er would occasionally goad a reaction out of him by playfully grabbing the string.

……

Time passed by quickly, and several years flew by in the blink of an eye.

A gorgeous young woman who appeared to be 13 to 14 years of age was walking energetically over an official road paved with yellow sand. She was wearing a white dress and a pair of light gray boots. Her black hair spilled all the way down to her waist, and her hands were tucked behind her back as she walked along.

Behind her was a tall and broad azure-robed man who was following her at a lethargic pace with a wooden expression on his face.

The little girl was walking along far quicker than the young man, but due to the stride length advantage that the young man had over her, not much distance was opened up between them.

In the distance, Liu Le'er spotted a mighty gray city at the end of the official road. There were many people traversing through the city gate, and from this distance, all of them appeared to be as tiny as sparrows.

Her brows furrowed slightly as she drew to a halt.

"Farbright City..." she mused after peering into the distance through narrowed eyes for a long while.

The young man made his way to her side before also stopping and casting his gaze toward the imposing city.

"Looks like it's a major city of the human race," Liu Le'er murmured to herself with a hesitant expression.

During these past five years, the two of them had visited some human cities and towns to try and find a cure for the young man's mysterious condition, but never had they visited such a large city.

"Brother Rock, if we can cure you, you'll be able to take revenge for me, right?" Liu Le'er asked as she looked up at the young man, but it was unclear whether she was directing the question at him or at herself.

The young man seemed to have displayed some reaction to her question, slowly withdrawing his gaze before turning to look at the little girl, but he remained silent.

What nonsense am I spouting? No matter how strong Brother Rock is, there's no way he can beat all those bad people in the Blood Sword Sect.

A depressing thought seemed to have occurred to Liu Le'er, and she lowered her head with a dejected expression. Tears began to flow down her face before falling onto the yellow sand beneath her feet.

Right at this moment, she felt a warm sensation on the top of her head.

She raised her head slightly to find the young man gently stroking her head with a warm look in his eyes.

For some reason, this simple gesture made Liu Le'er feel incredibly at ease, and an indescribable sense of courage welled up in her heart, as if no hardships or obstacles would be able to strike fear into her heart anymore.

She wiped away her tears with the back of her hand while latching onto the young man's hand with her other hand, then strode toward the city gate in the distance with a determined expression.

Chapter 5: Horse Beast

Farbright City was the third largest city in the Prosperous Nation.

The city was situated on a plain and took up an area in excess of 100 kilometers. To the south of the city was a large river, and transport via both land and water was very convenient, thereby giving rise to the flourishing city.

At this moment, there was a long line of people outside the city gate, and it was a very noisy and bustling scene.

Liu Le'er led the young man through the crowd, feeling rather anxious as she occasionally looked up above the city gate, which was several dozen feet tall.

An octagonal copper mirror was hanging there, and it was directly facing the city gate.

The sun was hanging high up in the sky, and the eight trigram diagram engraved onto the surface of the copper mirror was glowing under the light of the sun, giving off a sense of righteous energy.

All that was required for entry to be granted into the city was for a fee to be issued. The examination process wasn't very strict, and soon, it was Liu Le'er and the young man's turn.

The two of them arrived at the foot of the city gate, directly facing the octagonal copper mirror up above, and both of them were enshrouded in a burst of indescribable power.

Liu Le'er seemed to be quite stiff and anxious as she lowered her head, while the young man was staring directly at the copper mirror with a dazed expression.

Everyone failed to notice the faint glimmer of blue light that flashed through his eyes for an instant, and it didn't seem to have any effect on the mirror anyway.

A middle-aged city guard took a glance at the two of them, then asked in a lazy voice, "Where are you from, and why are you visiting our city?"

Liu Le'er immediately put on a bright smile as she replied, "We are from the Liu Clan Village located around 150 kilometers northwest of here. My name is Liu Le'er, and this is my brother, Liu Shi. We have come to Farbright City to visit some relatives and to treat my brother's condition."

Even though she and the young man had been living on their own for the majority of the past five years, occasional interaction with other people was unavoidable, so she had assigned the young man with the name of "Liu Shi" for the sake of convenience.

Liu Le'er pulled out some copper coins before handing them to the guard as she spoke, issuing a sum that was slightly more than the fee required to enter the city.

A pleased look appeared on the middle-aged guard's face upon seeing this, and he discreetly put the excess copper coins into his own pocket. He then took an extra glance at the dazed Liu Shi before waving them through.

"You two don't look like bad people. Go in now."

Liu Le'er gave a grateful response, then quickly led Liu Shi into the city. They walked for quite a distance, and only after reaching a secluded corner far away from the city gate did Liu Le'er slow down and heave a sigh of relief.

After making sure that no one was around, Liu Le'er pulled out an azure jade talisman as she murmured to herself, "It's a good thing that Dada gave me this Aura Concealment Talisman that can conceal my demonic aura so I wasn't exposed by the Demon Spotting Mirror."

The jade talisman was two inches in length and around two centimeters wide, with azure designs engraved all over its surface to form a complex array. Bursts of gentle azure light were surging over its surface like flowing water.

A hint of sorrow flashed through her eyes at the sight of the jade talisman, and she carefully stowed it away again.

After turning past two alleyways, the two of them arrived on the main street of Farbright City.

The street was wide enough to fit three horse-drawn carriages side by side with one another, and it was lined with countless large shops that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

However, there were very few brick and tile buildings in the city. Most of the buildings were constructed from wood instead, and even though the buildings weren't very tall or large, with very few of them exceeding even 100 feet in height, they were extremely intricate, and it was clear that there was great attention to detail in the craftsmanship.

This was the first time that Liu Le'er had ever visited such a large city, and she was pressed up tightly against Liu Shi as the dense crowds of people around her made her feel rather uneasy.

However, even though there were many people around them, they were all focused on their own business, and none of them bothered to interact with her and Liu Shi. As a result, she gradually became more at ease and began to have her attention drawn to all of the new things that she was seeing in the city. Soon, she was strolling along the street in tow with an intrigued expression.

"Look over there, Brother Rock! I've heard of that thing before, and it really does look as delicious as the stories I've heard!" Liu Le'er exclaimed while staring at a nearby stall that was selling sugar-coated haws.

The bustling scene in the city was reflected in Liu Shi's inky-black eyes, but he remained completely expressionless, seemingly unmoved by what he was seeing.

Liu Le'er was just about to drag Liu Shi over to the stall, but a hint of dejection suddenly welled up in her heart at the sight of his vacant eyes. She was immediately reminded of their objective for visiting the city in the first place, and she hurriedly tightened her ground on Liu Shi's hand as she said in an earnest voice, "Don't worry, Brother Rock. This is a massive city, there's definitely going to be a doctor here who can cure your condition."

Liu Shi's eyes flashed ever so slightly upon hearing this.

Liu Le'er led Liu Shi to a streetside food stall for a quick meal, then asked around and quickly secured the addresses for the two nearest medical clinics.

To the west of the city was the Li Family's medical clinic.

This medical clinic had already been around for over 100 years, making it a truly time-honored establishment in the city.

A middle-aged man in a long azure robe was seated atop a wooden chair with three of his fingers resting on Liu Shi's wrist to examine his pulse, while Liu Le'er was looking on from the side with an anxious expression.

The man's name was Li Changqing, and he was the current heir to the Li Family's medical clinic. He had already been practicing medicine for over 20 years and had earned quite a reputation for himself in the area.

After feeling Liu Shi's pulse for some time, Li Changqing withdrew his hand.

"Your brother's pulse is very strong and stable, and his energy is very abundant and well-balanced. It's clear that he's in exceptional physical condition. How did he sustain this condition? When did the symptoms first appear, and were there any external factors at play?" Li Changqing asked as he turned to Liu Le'er with furrowed brows.

"My brother and I have been apart for many years, so I don't know when he suffered this condition or the root cause," Liu Le'er replied with a shake of her head.

"That's rather problematic then. If I don't know the cause, then there's no way for me to administer treatment. My apologies, but with my limited skills, I am unable to help you," Li Changqing said as he stroked his long beard with an apologetic expression.

"Is there really no way at all?" Liu Le'er asked in an urgent voice.

"I'm afraid not," Li Changqing reaffirmed with a shake of his head.

Liu Le'er was very disappointed to hear this, and she extended a curtsey toward Li Changqing before departing from the clinic with Liu Shi.

She hung her head in dejection for a while, but then quickly turned to Liu Shi as she encouraged, "There are many more medical clinics in Farbright City. We'll visit them one by one, I'm sure one of the doctors will be able to cure you."

Liu Shi smiled in response, but it was unclear whether he understood Liu Le'er or not.

The two of them made their way in the same direction, passing through two streets before arriving in front of another medical clinic.

This clinic had gray outer walls with black roof tiles and a wide entrance, presenting a lavish sight to behold. The clinic was far more spectacular than the Li Family's medical clinic, and there were many people here for its services as well.

"Given how good this clinic looks, I'm sure the doctors here will be more skilled as well."

Liu Le'er led Liu Shi into the clinic with a hopeful expression, but Liu Le'er was left disappointed once again as the two of them re-emerged around an hour later.

"It's alright, there are still other clinics in the city." Liu Le'er quickly pulled herself together again.

Throughout the rest of the day, the two of them made their way through the entire city, visiting virtually all of the medical clinics, but none of the doctors were able to treat Liu Shi's condition.

……

To the north of the city was a clinic by the name of Wild Chrysanthemum Clinic, and Liu Le'er and Liu Shi emerged slowly from inside.

Liu Le'er wore a dejected expression as she hung her head while fiddling with the corner of her dress.

The Wild Chrysanthemum Clinic wasn't the largest medical clinic in Farbright City, but it was said that the doctors there were quite adept at treating some rare and complex conditions. Unfortunately, even they were unable to diagnose Liu Shi's condition.

"Please wait a moment, little girl." Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out from behind them, and an azure-robed elderly man with a head of gray hair quickly rushed out of the clinic.

Liu Le'er was rather taken aback by this, and she stopped in her tracks before asking, "What is it, Doctor Liu?"

The azure-robed elderly man was none other than the doctor of the Wild Chrysanthemum Clinic who had just examined Liu Shi's pulse.

A hint of hope welled up in Liu Le'er's heart, and she hurriedly asked, "Could it be that you've thought of something related to my brother's condition?"

"Indeed, I have. After examining your brother's condition just now, I went to the back to do some reading, and I just so happened to stumble across a case that is rather similar to your brother's symptoms," the elderly man replied with a nod.

Liu Le'er was ecstatic to hear this. "That's fantastic! Could I ask you to elaborate, Doctor Liu?"

"According to the records in the book, your brother's symptoms are different from what is normally seen in patients suffering from a debilitating mental condition. Instead, it seems more like he's been cursed or had a restriction planted on him that's harmed his soul. This is not something that the average doctor will be able to treat.

“Only immortal doctors who are adept in this field will perhaps be able to administer the correct treatment. As for your brother's inability to speak, that's not a concern. I can see that there's nothing physically wrong with him, so he'll naturally recover his ability to speak once his soul is restored to normal," the elderly man replied.

Liu Le'er fell silent upon hearing this, and after a while, she forced a smile onto her own face as she said, "Thank you for your advice, Doctor Liu."

"You're welcome, little girl. Doctors like us have an obligation to do everything we can for our patients," the elderly man replied before returning to the clinic.

Liu Le'er and Liu Shi continued on their way, and the former was feeling rather dejected.

"So Brother Rock really has had his soul harmed by someone," she murmured to herself.

As a demonic fox, even though she was still very young, she had a certain level of understanding of matters related to cultivation, and judging from Liu Shi's symptoms, she had already deduced that there was a chance that his soul had been harmed.

In order to treat him, she had to seek out the assistance of a cultivator adept in the way of the soul.

However, cultivators who fit that description were all extremely powerful, and she wasn't confident that her Aura Concealment Talisman would be able to keep her identity a secret in the presence of such a cultivator.

She had come to Farbright City to seek out medical treatment on the slim hope that she was incorrect in her assessment, but her worst fears had been confirmed.

Liu Le'er was rather hesitant about how to proceed.

Right as she was walking along the street in an absentminded manner with her brows furrowed, a commotion suddenly rang out up ahead, and everyone immediately erupted into a panic.

"Look out! There's a horse beast on a rampage!"

A cry of alarm rang out up ahead, and everyone frantically dove to the sides of the street to avoid the oncoming danger.

Not far away, there was a silver carriage being drawn by an azure horse-like beast with scales all over its entire body. It was galloping along the street as if it had gone insane, and it just so happened to be charging directly toward Liu Le'er and Liu Shi.

The horse-like beast neighed in a deranged manner, while the carriage behind it was swaying violently from side to side. The coach driver's face was as pale as a sheet, and he was pulling on the reins with all his might, but to no avail.

Liu Le'er was greatly alarmed by this, and she immediately tried to drag Liu Shi away to avoid the rampaging beast, but it was already too late.

A putrid stench wafted through the air as the horse-like beast reached within 10 feet of Liu Le'er and Liu Shi in the blink of an eye. It was so close that Liu Le'er could even see the globules of white froth that were flying in all directions from the sharp fangs in the beast's mouth.

Chapter 6: White-robed Young Man

"Argh!"

Liu Le'er wanted to unleash an ability to stop the horse-like beast, but in her panicked state, the magic power in her body wasn't circulating correctly, and she couldn't help but let loose a cry of alarm.

In this dire situation, she suddenly felt a shadow being cast over her. As it turned out, Liu Shi had abruptly stepped forward to shield her with his body, and at the same time, he had reached out with one hand like lightning, grabbing onto the horse-like beast's thick neck before turning his body to the side to collide head-on with the beast.

A loud thump rang out as the horse-like beast let loose an almighty neigh, and its enormous body was stopped cold in its tracks as if it had crashed into an immovable mountain.

Due to the excessive momentum that it had built up, a few of the hard stone slabs that the street was paved with were shattered under its thundering hooves.

At the same time, the carriage was propelled forward by its momentum and crashed into the beast's backside before flying several feet away to the side, then fell onto the ground with a heavy thump.

The carriage wasn't completely tipped over, but it had been significantly warped from the collision, and many pieces of its frame had come flying off before clattering onto the ground.

The coach driver was almost thrown off the carriage from the impact, but Liu Shi was standing completely still on the spot as if he had been nailed into place.

All of the nearby bystanders were astonished to see this, and a faint exclamation of surprise rang out from a certain teahouse.

Liu Le'er patted her own chest with a hint of lingering fear in her eyes, and a rush of warmth surged through her heart at the sight of the reliable figure standing before her.

During the past few years, whenever she encountered any danger, Liu Shi would always instinctively step in to protect her. Even though they weren't related by blood, they were just as close as blood relatives.

After being stopped cold in its tracks by Liu Shi, the azure horse beast became even more agitated, and it neighed furiously as it lowered its head before charging directly at Liu Shi's chest at full speed.

"Look out, Brother Rock!" Liu Le'er exclaimed in alarm.

Liu Shi remained completely expressionless as he locked his hand around the beast's neck, then exerted downward force with his arm.

The horse-like beast's legs buckled beneath it, and its enormous body was instantly flattened, causing it to fall to its knees, shattering all of the stone slabs on the ground around it in the process.

It felt as if its entire body were being crushed under a mountain that was threatening to shatter all of its bones, and the deranged look in its eyes immediately faded, replaced by a sense of fear.

In the face of Liu Shi, who possessed far superior strength to itself, the horse-like beast finally calmed down, sitting on its haunches in a docile manner, not daring to move.

"What incredible strength! With the momentum it built up, that horse beast had to have crashed into him with no less than two tons of force, yet he was able to stop it with ease!"

"Incredible, indeed!"

"Whose manor does this carriage belong to? How dare you drive it through a busy market so recklessly? If that man hadn't stepped in, who knows how many people could've been hurt or killed?"

Only after hearing this did everyone come to realize the severity of the situation, and they all erupted into spirited discussion.

Meanwhile, Liu Shi released the beast's neck in a wooden manner and fell still again.

Even though the horse-like beast had been released, it was still panting heavily and didn't dare to stand up.

"Are you alright, Brother Rock?" Liu Le'er hurriedly approached Liu Shi to examine his body, and she was very relieved to see that he was unharmed.

The coach driver had already turned as pale as a sheet, and now that the beast had been tamed, all of the energy seemed to have been drained from his body at once as he collapsed feebly onto the carriage.

Right at this moment, the door of the carriage was flung open, and two pale-faced young men emerged from within.

The first of the two men appeared to be around 20 years of age. He was quite handsome, and was wearing a white scholarly robe.

The other man appeared to only be 17 to 18 years of age with a complexion that was as fair as jade. The black pupils and whites of his eyes formed a very distinct contrast, as did his pearly white teeth and red lips. He was wearing a long white robe with a jade belt around his waist and a jade hat on his head. A pigeon-egg-sized jewel was embedded onto the hat, and he possessed far more style and flair than his companion.

"What the hell's wrong with you, you useless piece of trash? I almost died in there!"

The young man in the scholarly robe had a look of lingering fear in his eyes, and he snatched the horsewhip away from the coach driver before giving him a vicious beating with it.

With each strike of the whip, a bleeding gash appeared on the coach driver's body, but he didn't dare to evade the punishment and could only kowtow incessantly while begging for forgiveness.

The young man became even more incensed upon seeing this, and the whip fell with increased venom.

"Shush! They're from the Yu Manor!"

"This is none of our business, so let's all stop talking about it."

……

Once the two young men who had emerged from the carriage were identified, the discussions ringing out nearby immediately subsided. Everyone was looking at the two men with timid expressions, and it was clear that they all knew who the two men were.

"Let it go, Brother. Azure Wind Horses are low-grade demon beasts that are very wild in nature and difficult to tame, so he can't be blamed for this."

A hand suddenly reached out before grabbing the young man by the wrist, preventing the whip from falling again. It was the younger of the two men who had stepped in, and his voice was as pleasant to the ears as flowing spring water.

The whip-wielding young man took a glance at his companion, and his lips twitched slightly, following which he gave a cold harrumph before tossing the whip away.

"Thank you, Young Master!" The coach driver hurriedly began to kowtow toward the white-robed young man.

"Here, take this silver and compensate all of the people and shops that have been harmed by our carriage. If you can do a good job of that, you'll be spared harsh punishment," the white-robed young man said as he pulled out a bag before handing it over to the coach driver.

"Yes, Young Master." The coach driver hurriedly nodded in response as he took the bag of silver, then made his way toward the people who had been injured during the Azure Wind Horse's rampage.

"Thank heavens you were here to tame this Azure Wind Horse. It wouldn't be a big deal if my brother and I were injured, but it would be a travesty if we were to bring misfortune upon others," the white-robed young man said as he turned to Liu Shi with a smile, then cupped his fist in a salute.

The young man in the scholarly robe also turned to Liu Shi, only to find that he was completely unremarkable in appearance with a slightly dark complex and was wearing a simple azure robe that was rather shabby in appearance. A hint of disdain appeared in his eyes upon seeing this, and he cupped his fist in a rather half-hearted salute.

Liu Shi remained completely silent as he stared blankly at the two young men.

The scholarly-robed young man had never been ignored like this before, and he was just about to flare up with rage again, only to be stopped by the white-robed young man.

The young man took a closer look at Liu Shi, and his heart stirred slightly upon noticing the strangely vacant look in Liu Shi's eyes.

More and more people began to gather in the surrounding area, and Liu Le'er was beginning to feel rather uneasy. She gently tugged on Liu Shi's arm as she said in a quiet voice, "Let's go, Brother Rock."

Only then did the white-robed young man notice Liu Le'er, and his eyes immediately lit up at the sight of her gorgeous doll-like features. He hurriedly stepped forward to stop them as he said, "Please wait a moment."

"What do you want?" Liu Le'er asked as her brows furrowed tightly in her best attempt at a menacing expression.

"My name is Yu Qi. The carriage from just now belongs to our manor, and I sincerely apologize for putting you through such an ordeal," the white-robed young man said with a warm smile. [1]

"It's fine. Get out of our way so we can leave," Liu Le'er said with a hostile expression.

"If your brother hadn't stepped in, the consequences could've been catastrophic, so I would feel very guilty if I couldn't repay you somehow. The Yu Manor is not far away from here. Would you be open to paying our manor a visit so we can repay you with some hospitality?" Yu Qi asked.

"There's no need for that. It was the least that we could do in that situation. We still have other important matters to attend to, so we'll be on our way now." Liu Le'er shook her head without any hesitation, then began to skirt around the white-robed young man with Liu Shi in tow.

However, Yu Qi immediately positioned himself in front of the two of them again, then took a glance at Liu Shi before asking with an earnest expression, "Hold on. Could it be that by important matters, you're referring to seeking treatment for your brother?"

Liu Le'er was quite taken aback to hear this, and she asked with a surprised expression, "H... How did you know about that?"

"I was born with a very sensitive nose. Judging from the medicinal scent on your bodies, I presume you just came out of the nearby Wild Chrysanthemum Clinic. Your brother possesses incredible strength, but it looks like he's suffering from some type of mental ailment, and that's what led to my assumption. It looks like I was correct in my guess," Yu Qi explained as he cast his gaze toward the nearby Wild Chrysanthemum Clinic with a smile.

Even though he was a man, there was an indescribable hint of seduction in his smile.

As a young girl in her early teens, Liu Le'er was momentarily entranced by his smile, but she then immediately turned to Liu Shi to gauge his reaction. Liu Shi was still as expressionless as ever, and for some reason, that instilled her with a sense of reassurance.

The white-robed young man's smile faded as he continued, "Our Yu Family is a decently influential family in Farbright City with connections to many renowned doctors, so if it's medical services that you seek, then perhaps we can be of help to you."

"We did come to Farbright City to seek out medical services, but my brother's condition isn't something that can be cured by the average doctor," Liu Le'er said with a shake of her head.

Yu Qi's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but after some contemplation, he smiled as he said, "It sounds like your brother is suffering from a rather unusual ailment. However, we should still be able to help. Our Yu Family has an immortal guest elder who's very adept in the way of medicine, far more so than the average doctor. How about we get him to take a look at your brother's condition?"

Liu Le'er's eyes immediately lit up at the prospect of seeing an immortal doctor, and she was rather hesitant about how to proceed.

"Please don't turn down my offer. Just allow me to repay you for your efforts. I don't wish to come across as arrogant or boastful, but even though there are other immortal doctors in Farbright City, no one would dare to claim superiority in the way of medicine over our guest elder," Yu Qi proclaimed in a proud manner.

In the end, Liu Le'er was lured in by the white-robed young man's offer, and she reluctantly agreed, "Alright, we'll go with you, but we're leaving right away if that immortal doctor can't cure my brother's condition."

Yu Qi was ecstatic to hear this, and he said, "Of course. By the way, I still haven't had a chance to ask your names."

Liu Le'er hesitated momentarily before introducing herself and Liu Shi.

The scholarly-robed young man had been ignored for quite some time now, and he was clearly feeling rather disgruntled. Finally, he couldn't help but interject, "Brother, we've only just met these two and have no idea about their past, how can you just offer to bring them to our manor? Are you really going to get someone to treat him?"

"No need to worry, Brother. I know what I'm doing," Yu Qi replied in a casual voice with a dismissive wave of his hand.

The scholarly-robed young man seemed to be rather fearful of Yu Qi, and he seemed to want to say something further, but refrained from doing so in the end.

Right at this moment, several well-dressed guards equipped with swords and blades hurriedly rushed over from afar.

All of the surrounding bystanders immediately scattered upon seeing this, seemingly quite fearful of these guards.

The guards paid no heed to the bystanders as they hurriedly extended a collective respectful bow toward Yu Qi's duo.

"Please forgive us for arriving so late, young masters." [2]

"We're fine, there's no need to make such a big fuss. Take the carriage back to the manor, and don't make a big deal out of this," Yu Qi instructed in an indifferent voice.

"Yes, Young Master."

The guards immediately did as they were told, quickly tugging the Azure Wind Horse to its feet before departing.

After that, the white-robed young man turned to Liu Le'er and Liu Shi with a smile as he said, "Please come with me."

He then turned to lead the way, and Liu Le'er took another glance at Liu Shi, then tightened her grip on his hand before following along behind Yu Qi.

The scholarly-robed young man looked on as the three of them departed, and his expression became darker and darker. After remaining on the spot for a while longer, he gave a cold harrumph before also following along.

……

"Interesting! Isn't she the one who the prime minister of the Prosperous Nation is doing everything in his power to send to the Cold Flame Sect? I've heard she possesses decent cultivation aptitude."

All of a sudden, two people emerged from a discrete corner of a street not far away. They were led by a black-robed young man with a pair of long and narrow eyes, and he watched with a sinister expression as Yu Qi and the others departed into the distance.

The black-robed young man was accompanied by a man in gray who was as thin as a stick, and there were several bulging beasthide bags hanging from his waist. He was also looking in the same direction as he cautioned, "Be careful, Junior Martial Brother. I've heard that the Yu Manor houses multiple vagrant cultivators, so we can't take them too lightly."

The black-robed young man brushed off his concerns as he said, "I know what to do, Senior Martial Brother Fan. This is my first training mission, and you've only been sent to assist me. Unless any special circumstances arise, there's no need for you to step in. I'll take care of everything on my own."

The man in gray could only fall silent with a wry smile upon hearing this.

He knew this junior martial brother of his very well. Even though his cultivation base was nothing exceptional, he was directly related to one of the elders of the sect, thereby giving him a powerful backer, so he was always looking down on his fellow martial brothers.

All of a sudden, the two of them blurred before vanishing on the spot.

[1]. The "Qi" in Yu Qi's name is the Chinese character for 7. Earlier, he was referred to as the "seventh young master" when the coach driver said: "Thank you, Young Master!", so the accurate translation is actually "Thank you, Seventh Young Master", but that's not very idiomatic, so I decided against it. Hence, we can deduce that Yu Qi is the seventh young master of the Yu Family.

[Back]

[2]. Here, the two men are being referred to as "seventh young master" and "second young master", but once again, translating that literally wouldn't be very idiomatic, so I've just used young masters here to refer to both. From this, we can extrapolate that they are the second and seventh young masters of the Yu Family.

[Back]

Chapter 7: Yu Manor

The white-robed young man was quite talkative, and on the way back to the manor, he told Liu Le'er many interesting stories about the city, but Liu Le'er was rather distracted and only gave half-hearted responses.

The group passed through several streets and quickly arrived at the central area of Farbright City.

It was a rather quiet area with clean streets that were lined with barely any shops. Instead, the area was home to many large courtyards, and it was clear that this was where the wealthiest families in the city resided.

After making their way forward for a while longer, the group arrived outside a red manor.

In contrast with the other buildings in the city, this manor took up a massive area, and the bright red gates, which were around 20 feet tall, gave off a very majestic and imposing appearance. On either side of the gates were a pair of stone lions that were each around 10 feet tall, and the large gates were riddled with shiny copper nails that glistened under the light of the sun.

There was a guard wearing a suit of resplendent armor standing on each side of the gate. These guards were dressed the same way as the guards from before, but they were equipped with spears as opposed to swords.

All of this was a reflection of the status of the manor's owner.

There was a large golden plaque hanging above the gates, upon which the words "Yu Manor" were inscribed in large golden characters.

Liu Shi raised his head to take a glance at the manor before him, but then quickly withdrew his gaze.

Meanwhile, Liu Le'er was inspecting the manor with a slightly awestruck expression and a hint of unease in her heart.

She had never seen such a massive manor before, and it was clear from this manor that the Yu Family had to be a family of extremely high standing in Farbright City. In fact, there was a very good chance that they had ties with the Prosperous Nation's imperial court.

The white-robed young man could see that Liu Le'er was rather uneasy, and he asked in a gentle voice, "What is it, Sister Liu?"

Liu Le'er forced a smile onto her face as she said, "This place is huge, and it has so many guards! I'm sure your family is no ordinary family."

"You really are a bright young girl, Sister Liu. My father is none other than the prime minister of the Prosperous Nation, and that's why we have all of this. Otherwise, how could we afford a resident immortal doctor?" Yu Qi replied.

Liu Le'er's eyes widened in shock upon hearing this, while a proud look appeared on the scholarly-robed young man's face.

"Young masters!" The two guards at the gates immediately approached the group upon catching sight of them, then extended respectful bows.

Yu Qi gave a slight nod to acknowledge the two guards, then led Liu Le'er and Liu Shi through the gates.

After entering the manor, the scholarly-robed young man harrumphed coldly, "Father is going to be furious when he finds out you brought these two outsiders into our manor. Don't blame me for not warning you."

He then stormed off with a disdainful expression, but Yu Qi remained unfazed as he led Liu Le'er and Liu Shi toward another direction the manor. "Don't pay any heed to him. Please come with me."

The interior of the Yu Manor was enormous, with pavilions, pagodas, and gardens everywhere.

The ground was paved with top-tier paving materials such as white jade and azure jade, making for a surface that was as smooth as a mirror and as hard as iron, further displaying the luxury enjoyed by the affluent family.

Yu Qi seemed to be quite an authoritative figure in the Yu Manor, as evidenced by the fact that all of the servants that they encountered bowed respectfully toward him, and some even fell to one knee.

Liu Le'er took a glance at Yu Qi upon seeing this with a distracted look in her eyes, and it was unclear what she was thinking about.

The fact that she and Liu Shi were trailing along behind Yu Qi naturally attracted a great deal of attention, particularly given Liu Shi's imposing frame and strange demeanor, but no one dared to look at them for too long for fear of irking Yu Qi.

Shortly thereafter, the three of them arrived in a long corridor, where they were greeted by a tall and slender servant in a green dress.

A joyful smile immediately appeared on the servant's face at the sight of Yu Qi, and she bounded over to them in a spritely manner. "Welcome back, Young Master!"

"There are guests with me, Xiao Wu! Don't be so cheeky," Yu Qi scolded in a displeased voice.

The servant stuck out her tongue in a sheepish display, but she wasn't actually afraid, so it was clear that she was different from the other servants that they had encountered.

Yu Qi took a resigned glance at her, then said, "You came at just the right time, Xiao Wu. These two are esteemed guests that I've invited to our manor. This is Sister Liu Le'er, and this is Brother Liu Shi. Prepare a place for them to stay in the western courtyard."

Only then did Xiao Wu notice the two people behind Yu Qi, and she was rather taken aback by Liu Shi's wooden demeanor. However, her eyes then immediately lit up as her gaze fell upon Liu Le'er, and she giggled, "What a pretty little girl you are!"

"Stop being so rude! Sister Liu is an esteemed guest of mine! My apologies. Xiao Wu has been serving me from a young age, and I've spoiled her rotten." Yu Qi scolded Xiao Wu before turning to Liu Le'er and Liu Shi with an apologetic smile.

"Fine, I'll behave," Xiao Wu conceded, but she made a funny face at Liu Le'er while Yu Qi's back was turned.

Liu Le'er couldn't help but burst into laughter, and she hurriedly clapped a hand over her mouth to silence herself, but a great deal of the tension and anxiety that she had been feeling had been alleviated.

Yu Qi took a glance at his surroundings, then drew closer to Xiao Wu as he whispered, "By the way, I'll be out for the next few days, so..."

The two of them were standing together in a very intimate manner, and Xiao Wu didn't seem to be opposed to this.

Liu Le'er pursed her lips slightly upon seeing this, and what little positive feelings she had developed toward the white-robed young man instantly evaporated.

After a brief, hushed conversation, Xiao Wu gave a nod before departing.

"Please follow me," Yu Qi said as he continued onward.

Moments later, the three of them arrived in a small courtyard, where they were greeted by Xiao Wu again.

Even though it was referred to as a small courtyard, it was only small in the context of the entire manor. In reality, it was quite spacious with a small cobblestone path, to the left of which was a pine tree, while to the right was a cluster of bamboo trees.

A gentle breeze blew past, causing the pine tree and the leaves of bamboo trees to rustle incessantly.

The furnishings in the room were quite simplistic, but all of the furniture reflected exceptional craftsmanship.

The tables and chairs were spotless, and it was clear that they had just been cleaned.

"You two look rather tired, so why don't you take a rest here? I'll arrange a feast later to welcome the two of you to our manor," the white-robed young man said as he turned to Liu Le'er with a smile.

"There's no need for that. All I want to know is when that immortal doctor can attend to my brother," Liu Le'er said as she inspected the room around her.

Yu Qi was silent for a moment before replying, "Alright, in that case, I'll get Xiao Wu to bring you your dinner later. As for the immortal doctor, that'll have to wait until tomorrow."

"I see." Liu Le'er was rather disappointed to hear this.

"By the way, if you need anything else, feel free to speak to Xiao Wu. Have a good rest, I'll be taking my leave now," Yu Qi said as he took a glance at Liu Shi.

Liu Le'er nodded in response with an absentminded expression.

……

Outside the courtyard, Xiao Wu asked with a curious expression, "Young Master, who are those people? Judging from the way they're dressed, they seem to be commoners. Why are you treating them with so much respect?"

"Don't judge a book by its cover! Earlier today, the Azure Wind Horse drawing the carriage that my brother and I were in went on a rampage, and Liu Shi managed to subdue it with one hand and stop the carriage," Yu Qi replied with a faint smile as gave Xiao Wu's delicate chin a light pinch.

"He stopped an Azure Wind Horse with one hand? That's incredible!" Xiao Wu exclaimed.

"Now you know why I invited them to our manor. If I can get someone with such extraordinary strength to serve me, it'll surely be immensely beneficial to me in the future. On top of that, that little girl, Le'er, is sure to become a stunning beauty once she grows up.

“I can't bear to let a beauty like her wander out in the world with no one to depend on, so it was only natural that I brought her back to our manor as well. Make sure to look after them well. No slacking off, understood?" the white-robed young man instructed with a smile, then turned to depart.

An embarrassing thought seemed to have made its way into Xiao Wu's mind, and she blushed as she hurriedly replied, "Understood."

……

Inside the courtyard.

Having walked the entire day and enduring that close call with the Azure Wind Horse earlier, Liu Le'er was feeling rather weary, and she led Liu Shi into the bedroom to rest.

Even though it was normally considered taboo for two unrelated members of the opposite sex to stay in the same room like this, the two of them had never been apart the past few years, eating and living together, so Liu Le'er saw nothing wrong with this.

As night fell, Xiao Wu delivered a lavish dinner to them.

Looking at the entire table full of delicious dishes, Liu Le'er was salivating incessantly.

She had never enjoyed such a sumptuous feast, and even though the unfamiliar environment of the prime minister's manor made her feel rather uneasy, she still couldn't help but dig in for a massive meal.

In contrast, Liu Shi didn't display much of a reaction to the feast laid out on the table.

As the sky grew darker outside, the moon gradually rose up.

Liu Le'er laid on the bed, tossing and turning, unable to get to sleep. Her mind was completely preoccupied with thoughts of the treatment that Liu Shi was going to be receiving the next day.

She shuffled over to the side of the bed, then asked in a quiet voice, "Brother Rock, do you think that immortal doctor will be able to cure you?"

Liu Shi wasn't laying down. Instead, he was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed by the side of the bed.

He had done this every single night for the past few years, not laying down to sleep even once.

Liu Shi remained completely expressionless and his eyes also remained shut, as if he hadn't heard what Liu Le'er had just said.

Liu Le'er was already accustomed to this lack of response, and she whispered, "Don't worry, Brother Rock. If the immortal doctor here can't cure you, then we'll go somewhere else. I'm sure we'll be able to find someone who can cure you."

A reassured smile then appeared on her face, and she slowly closed her eyes, falling asleep soon thereafter.

Meanwhile, Liu Shi continued to remain completely still like a statue in the darkness.

After an indeterminate period of time, Liu Shi suddenly opened his eyes before casting his gaze toward a certain direction in the Yu Manor. At the same time, he instinctively raised a hand to stroke the dark green accessory that he was wearing around his neck.

……

As it turned out, there was an underground secret chamber in the Yu Manor in the direction that Liu Shi was looking in.

There were dark red runes engraved onto the walls of the secret chamber, converging toward the center from all directions.

At the center of the secret chamber was a black pill furnace, beneath which was a firepit that was holding a scorching flame.

At this moment, the pill furnace was giving off a black glow, and its lid was trembling gently as if it could fly off at any moment.

An elderly man was standing beside the pill furnace, watching it with an anxious expression.

The elderly man was wearing a set of gray daoist robes and a lotus crown on his head. He had a pair of deep-set eyes and a thin and gaunt face. There was a long goatee trailing down from his chin, and his hair and facial hair were all completely white, indicating that he was of quite an advanced age.

Right at this moment, a dull crack rang out from within the pill furnace, following which a burned smell wafted out from within.

The elderly man's expression changed drastically as he swept a hand through the air to release an incantation seal that snuffed out the fire, following which the lid of the pill furnace flew off at his behest.

The pill furnace was still burning hot, but he reached in directly with his hand, only to re-emerge with a handful of black powder, and his expression instantly darkened significantly.

A strong medicinal fragrance intermingled with a burned smell was wafting out from the powder.

The elderly man was furious to see this, and he immediately erupted into an incensed tirade.

Chapter 8: Daoist Master White Stone

The next morning, the sound of footsteps rang out from the western courtyard of the Yu Manor.

There were three people slowly making their way through the corridor leading to another courtyard.

The two people leading the way were walking shoulder by shoulder. One of them was an elderly daoist priest in a gray daoist robe with a lotus crown on his head, while the other was a woman wearing a light yellow palace dress.

Trailing along behind the two was a young woman in servant attire, holding a three-layered hamper made from sandalwood.

The daoist priest was walking along with his white brows slightly furrowed, seemingly a little displeased, and his eyes were looking directly forward, clearly indicating that his mind was elsewhere.

The woman in the palace dress was quite young, appearing to be around 17 to 18 years of age, and even though her body still wasn't fully developed, it was very well-proportioned. She had a set of beautiful facial features that were capped off by a pair of eyes that were as bright as stars, leaving a lasting impression on all those who saw them.

In addition to that, she had applied some rouge to her face, adding a hint of color to her fair cheeks that gave her an even more alluring appearance.

"My sincerest apologies for interrupting your pill refinement, Daoist Master White Stone," the woman said with an apologetic expression.

The elderly daoist priest temporarily set aside his train of thought as he replied, "I don't mind, but I'm just perplexed about why you insist on getting me to attend to a mortal with a mental ailment?"

"Allow me to explain. Yesterday..."

A faint smile appeared on the woman's face as she gave the daoist priest a brief recount of how Liu Shi had stopped the Azure Wind Horse the day before.

The elderly daoist priest listened with a thoughtful expression, and he raised an eyebrow slightly as he heard about how Liu Shi had managed to stop a rampaging Azure Wind Horse cold in its tracks with just a single hand.

"Seeing as you're somewhat indebted to him, I suppose I'm obligated to examine his condition," the elderly man said in an indifferent voice after hearing the young woman's story.

The young woman smiled in response as she extended a slight curtsey.

As for the servant, she was holding the hamper rather anxiously, trailing along behind the two in an obedient manner without making any sound.

Inside the western courtyard, Liu Le'er had already finished getting dressed and washing up, and she was seated on the edge of the bed, having another one-sided conversation with Liu Shi when she suddenly heard the sound of door-knocking ring out.

Once the trio arrived at the western courtyard, the servant immediately strode forward to knock on the door, then called out, "Sister Le'er, our young mistress has brought the immortal doctor here to see you."

Liu Le'er rose to her feet, but she didn't immediately open the door. Instead, she asked in a rather perplexed manner, "Who's this young mistress that you speak of?"

"It's me, Sister Le'er."

The voice coming from outside was rather familiar, and Liu Le'er's befuddlement was even further exacerbated.

After a brief hesitation, she made her way to the door before opening it.

As soon as the door was opened, she immediately caught a whiff of a faint medicinal scent, following which she was greeted by the sight of the three people standing outside.

First, her gaze fell upon the elderly daoist priest, and after ascertaining that the medicinal smell was coming from him, she turned to the servant, only to find that it was Xiao Wu, the personal servant of Yu Qi’s that she had met the day before.

Finally, Liu Le'er turned her gaze toward the woman in the yellow palace dress , and initially, she faltered slightly, following which her mouth gaped open in shock.

"You're the young master from the day before!" she exclaimed as she threw a hand over her own mouth.

"That's right. You can call me Sister Qi if you'd like," the woman in the palace dress said with an amused smile at the sight of Liu Le'er's surprised expression.

Liu Le'er also smiled upon hearing this. "No wonder I felt like you were a little..."

"A little what?" Yu Qi asked as she raised an eyebrow.

"A little... not like a man," Liu Le'er replied in a tactful manner after a moment of deliberation.

"You can avoid a lot of unnecessary trouble by posing as a man. You'll know what I mean once you're all grown up in a few years," Yu Qi said with a faint smile.

Liu Le'er didn't quite understand what Yu Qi was referring to, but she still nodded in response before inviting the trio into the room.

"Sister Le'er, this is the immortal doctor I told you about, you can call him Daoist Master White Stone. Daoist Master White Stone, this is Liu Le'er, and that man over there is her brother, Liu Shi," Yu Qi introduced as she turned to the elderly daoist priest.

Liu Le'er had already guessed that the elderly man was most likely the immortal doctor, but her heart still jolted slightly upon hearing confirmation of her suspicions from Yu Qi, and she hurriedly lowered her head as she extended a respectful salute, not daring to meet Daoist Master White Stone's gaze. "I pay my respects to the esteemed immortal doctor."

Meanwhile, Liu Shi remained seated on the edge of the bed, displaying no reaction to the trio.

Daoist Master White Stone took a brief glance at Liu Le'er, then directed his gaze toward Liu Shi. He made his way over to Liu Shi's side before stepping over to his other side, examining him carefully from head to toe before focusing his gaze on Liu Shi's glabella.

A moment later, Daoist Master White Stone closed his eyes before raising a hand, joining his index and middle fingers together as he extended them toward Liu Shi's glabella.

Liu Le'er was quite taken aback to see this, and she couldn't help but let loose a cry of alarm.

Daoist Master White Stone's arm instantly stiffened, and he turned around to give her a displeased look.

"There's no need for alarm, Sister Le'er. Daoist Master White Stone is examining your brother's condition," Yu Qi hurriedly explained as she gently tugged on Liu Le'er's arm.

"My apologies, Daoist Master White Stone. I didn't do it on purpose," Liu Le'er hurriedly apologized.

Daoist Master White Stone's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he closed his eyes before extending his hand toward Liu Shi's glabella again.

As he extended his fingers forward, a burst of azure light emerged on Liu Shi's glabella, and circular ripples were spreading outward from the azure light, much like the ripples that would arise from a stone being tossed into a lake.

A short while later, a slightly befuddled look appeared on Daoist Master White Stone's face, and he withdrew his hand before slowly opening his eyes.

"How is my brother? Can you cure him?" Liu Le'er hurriedly asked.

Daoist Master White Stone took a glance at her out of the corners of his eyes and offered no response.

Yu Qi gently patted the back of Liu Le'er's hand in a reassuring gesture, indicating for her to be patient.

Liu Le'er reluctantly fell silent and asked no further questions, but her gaze remained fixed on Liu Shi.

Liu Shi seemed to have sensed her gaze, and he turned his face toward her before swallowing the pastry in his mouth, then gave her a faint smile.

Daoist Master White Stone contemplated the situation momentarily before flipping over a hand to summon a rather old copper mirror.

"Go!"

Azure light flashed from the round mirror, and it immediately rose up into the air at his behest, flying over to Liu Shi before coming to a halt directly above his head.

Daoist Master White Stone then began to chant an incantation while swiping his joined fingers through the air, seemingly inscribing some type of mysterious runes into the very air itself.

Shortly thereafter, his fingers fell still, and he pointed directly at the copper mirror.

The suspended copper mirror immediately began to tremble violently, and a layer of azure light emerged, causing its slightly rugged and uneven surface to become smooth and pristine.

Liu Le'er was scrutinizing the surface of the mirror intently with an anxious expression, and she could see that some changes were taking place within the azure light. It seemed that a rather murky image was about to appear.

However, after waiting for a short while, the azure light within the mirror's surface was still as murky as ever, and she was unable to discern anything from it.

Liu Shi also seemed to be rather annoyed by the mirror hovering over his head, and he raised his hand before swatting it through the air as if he were waving a mosquito away. Even though his hand didn't make direct contact with the mirror, it caused the azure light on the mirror's surface to flicker and become even murkier.

"Impossible!"

Daoist Master White Stone's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately swept a sleeve toward the copper mirror, upon which it instantly flew up his sleeve, vanishing without a trace.

Liu Le'er was itching to ask more questions, but she learned to hold her tongue this time.

"Have you identified the problem, Daoist Master White Stone? Is his condition curable?" Yu Qi asked.

There was a rather uncertain look on Daoist Master White Stone's face, and he replied, "It's not impossible, but..."

Liu Le'er was ecstatic to hear this, and she hurriedly implored, "Please cure my brother, esteemed immortal doctor!"

"If you have a way to treat this man, then please do everything in your power, Daoist Master White Stone. I will cover all of your expenses," Yu Qi said.

Liu Le'er turned to Yu Qi with a grateful expression upon hearing this.

Daoist Master White Stone stared at Liu Shi in silence for a long while before finally making up his mind. "In that case, I will be sure to do my best. However, let me make this clear in advance: his soul is in a sealed-off state for some unknown reason, and it'll be very difficult to restore it to its normal state.

“Only by casting a spirit awakening array will there be a chance for his condition to be cured. In order to administer such a treatment, I require an independent secret chamber."

Liu Le'er hesitated momentarily before asking in a low voice, "Can I be there while you're administering the treatment, Daoist Master White Stone?"

"Why do you want to be there? To get in my way? Do you not trust me, you little brat?" Daoist Master White Stone's voice instantly spiked up a few octaves in indignation.

Liu Le'er's heart jolted upon hearing this, and she hurriedly waved her hands in response. "I wouldn't dare, Daoist Master White Stone! I just want to be by my brother's side. All I'll do is watch from the side, I'll make sure not to get in your way."

"Fine, do as you wish. A spirit awakening array is not just a run-of-the-mill array, so I have to go back and make some preparations," Daoist Master White Stone said as he turned to Yu Qi.

"Thank you for your efforts, Daoist Master White Stone," Yu Qi replied with a respectful curtsey.

Liu Le'er hurriedly followed her example, extending a curtsey of her own, but by then, Daoist Master White Stone had already departed from the room.

Following Daoist Master White Stone's departure, Yu Qi and Xiao Wu also left shortly thereafter. Before departing, she offered some words of reassurance to Liu Le'er, telling her not to worry about Liu Shi's condition.

Chapter 9: Array

On the morning of the third day, Xiao Wu arrived at the western courtyard, informing Liu Le'er and Liu Shi that Daoist Master White Stone's preparations were complete, and that he was ready to treat Liu Shi.

With Xiao Wu leading the way, Liu Le'er led Liu Shi through a series of corridors, passing through four small courtyards and emerging from an archway before finally arriving in the backyard of the Yu Manor.

Liu Le'er was already in awe of all of the winding courtyards and corridors, but only after seeing the small lake in the backyard, which was laden with lush lotus leaves, did she truly realize just how massive the Yu Manor was.

The lake was referred to as a small one, but only relative to all of the large rivers and lakes that Liu Le'er had seen in the past. In reality, the lake was at least 3,000 to 4,000 feet in area, certainly far larger than a pond that one would find in the backyard of the average wealthy man's estate.

"That's where Daoist Master White Stone cultivates and refines pills," Xiao Wu introduced as she pointed at a small island at the center of the lake.

Liu Le'er cast her gaze toward the direction that Xiao Wu was pointing in, and she was greeted by the sight of a bridge constructed from white marble, arching over the teeming lotus leaves and leading all the way to the small island.

The island wasn't very large, but it was filled with lush greenery and enshrouded in cloud and mist, making it impossible to get a clear look at it.

The thought that the island could hold the key to curing Liu Shi immediately filled Liu Le'er with excitement, and her thoughts began to wander with her emotions.

Xiao Wu could see that Liu Le'er was rather distracted, and she smiled as she said, "Servants like me aren't allowed to encroach upon Daoist Master White Stone's territory, so you'll have to go on your own from here."

Liu Le'er returned to her senses upon hearing this, and she hurriedly said, "Thank you, Sister Xiao Wu."

Seeing Liu Le'er so excited put Xiao Wu in a good mood as well, and she gave Liu Le'er a cheerful wave before departing.

Liu Le'er cast her gaze toward the small island, and she laid a hand onto the railing of the bridge, but she didn't immediately step onto it. For some reason, a thought had suddenly occurred to her.

Will Brother Rock leave me once he's cured?

A hesitant look appeared on her face as this thought occurred to her, but her heart was immediately put at ease again as she looked up at Liu Shi's familiar features.

"Let's go, Brother Rock."

With that, she stepped onto the bridge, leading Liu Shi toward the small island.

As the two drew closer and closer to the island, Liu Le'er began to feel rather anxious. In contrast, Liu Shi's expression was as calm as ever, and his gaze was occasionally drawn to the carp popping up out of the water beneath the lotus leaves.

After arriving on the island, Liu Le'er was struck by the feeling that the mist wasn't actually as dense as it had seemed from afar. There wasn't much sound on the island, and it was a very peaceful and elegant environment.

The end of the stone bridge was connected to a small, winding path that was paved with stone slabs, extending all the way into the heart of the island.

Liu Le'er and Liu Shi made their way along the path, and there were no other branches that diverged from the path, so they arrived directly in front of an archaic daoist temple with black and white walls.

Daoist Master White Stone was waiting for them outside the temple, and upon their arrival, he instructed them to come in before making his way toward the temple's rear hall.

The two of them followed Daoist Master White Stone through three halls before arriving at the temple's backyard, where a huge fake mountain was standing.

Daoist Master White Stone made his way over to a certain part of the mountain, then pressed a hand onto its surface, and a thick and heavy stone door slowly opened to reveal an opening tall enough to fit an adult human.

The two followed Daoist Master White Stone into the fake mountain, following which the stone door behind them slowly fell shut.

A cave had been excavated into the interior of the fake mountain, and it wasn't a very large space, only slightly larger than the room that Liu Le'er and Liu Shi were staying in. There were several lit lanterns on each of the four walls, and they weren't releasing any smoke, leading Liu Le'er to wonder what type of oil was being burned in the lanterns.

There was an octagonal diagram engraved onto the ground at the center of the cave, and it resembled the eight trigrams, but was somewhat different.

The engravings on the ground were extremely deep, and not only did it hold designs of some peculiar birds and beasts, there were also some strange lines interspersed among those designs. Liu Le'er had a feeling that this was some type of ancient text.

There was a dark red triangular flag situated at each corner of the octagonal design, and these flags also bore peculiar patterns inscribed in golden thread.

Daoist Master White Stone took a glance at Liu Le'er, who was inspecting the array, then urged in a cold voice, "What are you waiting for? Get him to sit down at the center of the array!"

"Yes, Daoist Master!"

Liu Le'er hurriedly withdrew her gaze before guiding Liu Shi to the center of the array, where there was a ring-shaped design.

"You're definitely going to be cured, Brother Rock. I'll be here with you," Liu Le'er said in an earnest voice as she looked into Liu Shi's eyes, then stepped out of the array and planted herself against one of the stone walls off to the side, where she looked on with an anxious expression.

"Stay there from now on. Don't make any sound to distract me, and don't move even a single inch, do you hear me?" Daoist Master White Stone instructed with a serious expression.

Liu Le'er hurriedly nodded in response.

Only then did Daoist Master White Stone make his way over to the array, and he raised a hand in front of his own chest in a daoist prayer, then walked a lap around the array while chanting an indecipherable incantation.

As he began to chant the incantation, the golden lines on the eight small flags around the array lit up with dazzling golden light in unison, then extended toward Liu Shi from all directions.

Liu Shi was inspecting his surroundings, and his body abruptly shuddered as the golden light enveloped his body. It was as if he had been electrocuted, and he instantly sat bolt upright.

Liu Le'er's heart jolted upon seeing this, and her eyes were filled with concern and anticipation.

The golden light began to swirl around Liu Shi's body, forming a series of strange golden patterns. At the same time, there also seemed to be specks of golden light converging within his eyes, presenting quite a peculiar sight to behold.

All of a sudden, Daoist Master White Stone's chanting drew to an abrupt halt, and he suddenly switched to a different hand seal as he yelled, "Restrict!"

The golden light that was revolving around Liu Shi abruptly solidified before enveloping Liu Shi like a layer of golden paper.

Through the golden light, it could be seen that Liu Shi's brows had furrowed together, indicating that he was in some pain.

A loud sizzling sound rang out as bright golden light radiated from the eight flags around the array, and plumes of black mist surged out of the flags before converging toward the center of the array.

Liu Le'er's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and for some reason, she was struck by an instinctive sense of discomfort as soon as the black mist appeared.

All of a sudden, Liu Shi gave a muffled groan as his facial muscles spasmed slightly.

Liu Le'er couldn't help but let loose a cry of alarm upon seeing this, but she then immediately clapped a hand over her own mouth with a fearful expression.

"Shut up! I told you not to make a sound!" Daoist Master White Stone scolded in a cold voice.

Liu Le'er's heart shuddered slightly, and she didn't dare to say anything, but the fear in her eyes didn't abate in the slightest.

The plumes of mist were like living creatures, forming a series of tentacles that wrapped around Liu Shi before completely inundating him.

Immediately thereafter, Daoist Master White Stone made a hand seal and resumed his chanting.

More and more black mist poured out of the flags, and it was becoming denser and denser.

A perplexed look appeared on Liu Shi's face, following which his eyelids began to droop, and he slowly closed his eyes, falling asleep in an upright position.

An elated look appeared on Daoist Master White Stone's face upon seeing this, and he switched to another hand seal as he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which disintegrated into specks of crimson light that vanished directly into the black mist.

A strong bloody scent immediately began to waft out of the mist, and a series of crimson runes rapidly appeared.

Liu Le'er's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and her instincts were screaming at her that something wasn't right. However, she was rather hesitant about how to proceed for fear of offending Daoist Master White Stone.

However, right at this moment, Daoist Master White Stone let loose a low cry, and the temperature of the black mist abruptly plummeted, forming a giant black of black ice that sealed Liu Shi within.

"Stop! What are you doing?" At this point, Liu Le'er could see beyond a doubt that Daoist Master White Stone's intentions were impure, and she stepped toward the array with an alarmed expression as she made a grabbing motion. A palm-sized pellet drum appeared in her grasp amid a flash of light, and she immediately attempted to shatter the block of ice to save Liu Shi.

Chapter 10: Crisis

However, before she had a chance to do anything, Daoist Master White Stone swept a sleeve through the air to release a golden shadow that shot forth like lightning.

In the blink of an eye, the golden shadow transformed into a shimmering golden rope that bound Liu Le'er tightly.

As a result, Liu Le'er was tripped over and fell onto the ground with a dull thump.

"What are you trying to do, you old bastard?"

Liu Le'er glowered intently at Daoist Master White Stone while struggling with all her might, but the golden rope only constricted even tighter around her body as if it could feel her resistance.

Liu Le'er's expression became twisted with agony, and tears welled up in her eyes, but she gritted her teeth tightly and refused to make a sound.

All of a sudden, her ears abruptly vanished, but a pair of pointy triangular fox ears poked through the black hair on the top of her head.

A burst of potent restrictive force was released by the golden rope, completely sealing her magic power.

"What am I trying to do? Hehe, you naive little demon fox! Did you really think you could fool me with that magic tool of yours? What a joke!" Daoist Master White Stone said in a cold voice as he took a glance at Liu Le'er out of the corners of his eyes.

"So you already saw through my identity?" Liu Le'er's heart sank even further upon hearing this, but she still had a stubborn and unyielding look on her face.

"Hehe, is this the time for you to be worrying about that? You were brought into the manor by the young mistress, and the fox race is quite a powerful race in our Spirit Domain Realm, so I originally planned to turn a blind eye, but who could've anticipated that you would bring such a priceless treasure straight to my doorstep?"

Daoist Master White Stone cast his gaze toward Liu Shi as he spoke, and a hint of irrepressible excitement appeared in his eyes.

"Wh... What are you going to do to Brother Rock?" Liu Le'er asked in a trembling voice.

"Don't worry, I couldn't bear to kill this brother of yours. His body is more powerful than any that I've ever seen before, and to make matters even better, his spiritual sense has been harmed, reducing him to an imbecile! All I have to do is use a secret technique to erase what remains of his consciousness, and I'll be able to refine a puppet with boundless potential!" Daoist Master White Stone said with a triumphant expression.

A trail of blood began to trick down from the corner of Liu Le'er's lips upon hearing this, and a desperate look appeared in her eyes as a layer of crimson light emerged on her face. She arched forward violently as an animalistic snarl erupted from her lips, and her pupils began to glow green while large tufts of white fur sprouted all over her entire body.

Every single strand of fur was glowing with translucent light and was extremely hard, making it seem as if she had suddenly transformed into a white hedgehog. Furthermore, the fur on her tail was flashing with arcs of white lightning.

All of a sudden, the white fur abruptly stood up on end to force the golden rope away from her body slightly, and dazzling white light began to glow from her furry tail.

Countless strands of white fur were fired through the air, hurtling directly toward the block of black ice like a barrage of flying needles.

"Insolence!"

Daoist Master White Stone turned around with a furious expression before releasing an ovular black shield, which shot forth as a streak of black light at an incredible speed, arriving in front of the block of black ice just barely before the barrage of white fur arrived.

The ovular shield then immediately expanded to several times its original size to cover the entirety of the block of ice.

A string of loud clangs rang out as the barrage of fur struck the black shield, causing it to tremble incessantly, but ultimately, the attack was kept at bay.

The green light in Liu Le'er's eyes flickered violently upon seeing this, but before she had a chance to do anything else, the golden rope around her suddenly glowed brightly as its constrictive force increased by almost twofold, flattening the white fur against Liu Le'er's body. At the same time, countless finger-length golden needles emerged from the rope, piercing deep into her body.

"Argh!"

Blood began to flow incessantly out of her body, staining large sections of her fur red. However, she gritted her teeth and paid no heed to her own injuries as she swept her tail through the air once again with all of her remaining strength.

Another barrage of white fur was released, but this time, it dispersed before flying toward the block of ice from all directions.

The black shield was like an impregnable wall, but it couldn't cover the block of ice from every direction at once.

Daoist Master White Stone was furious to see this, and he opened his mouth to release a ball of black light, within which was enveloped a serpentine flying sword that flew into the air above the block of ice in a flash.

The flying sword circled through the air, manifesting a burst of black sword qi that formed a wall of sword projections, which enveloped the block of ice.

At the same time, the black shield glowed even brighter as it expanded further in size, protecting the block of ice alongside the sword projections.

A string of metallic clangs rang out, and most of the needle-like fur was kept at bay by the flying sword and the black shield, but there were still some that managed to sneak through the gaps and strike the block of black ice.

The block of ice trembled violently, and many thin holes were punched into it. Several cracks appeared on its surface, and they were rapidly expanding.

Right at this moment, Daoist Master White Stone arrived beside the block of ice in a flash, then raised his hands to release a vast expanse of black mist out of his sleeves. Some of the mist fused into the block of ice, while the rest formed a protective barrier around it.

The cracks on the block of ice immediately stopped expanding, then quickly began to seal, and after just a few seconds, it was already back to its original state.

Daoist Master White Stone heaved a sigh of relief upon seeing this, then turned to glower at Liu Le'er with a furious expression.

Liu Le'er was laying on the ground with an indignant look in her eyes.

All of the fur on her body had already vanished, and her aura was severely diminished. It was clear that the two attacks she had just unleashed had already exhausted all of her magic power.

"Looks like I underestimated you!" Daoist Master White Stone harrumphed coldly.

If he had reacted even a split second later than he had, the block of ice would've most likely been shattered.

With a vicious sweep of his hand, Daoist Master White Stone conjured up a palm of black light, which slammed into Liu Le'er's body.

Liu Le'er was instantly sent flying before crashing into the wall of the secret chamber, and she threw up a large mouthful of blood before falling onto the ground in a heap.

Her entire body was stained with blood, and her hair was completely disheveled. Her face was deathly pale, and she was clearly in terrible condition.

If it weren't for the fact that Daoist Master White Stone intended to sell her for spirit stones, he would've already killed her with that strike.

"Brother Rock..." Liu Le'er raised her head in a feeble manner as she cast her gaze toward Liu Shi, but her body then suddenly spasmed, and she fell unconscious.

Daoist Master White Stone swept a hand through the air to release several talismans, which flew over to Liu Le'er before adhering themselves onto the ground around her.

A vast expanse of black light erupted from the talismans, forming a ball over her body.

Only after doing all of that did Daoist Master White Stone turn his attention back to the block of ice, and he couldn't suppress the smile that crept onto his face.

"Once I successfully refine this puppet, none of my current rivals will be a match for me!"

His smile faded as he raised his hands to release eight more talismans, which fell onto the ground near the block of black ice.

Inky black light rose up from the talismans to form an array, which lifted the block of ice around a foot off the ground.

Daoist Master White Stone then flipped a hand over to produce a black gourd.

There was a circle of blue runes engraved onto the gourd that were giving off a cold light, and it sounded as if there were some type of liquid sloshing around inside it.

He pulled out the gourd cork and carefully tipped it over to pour out a black liquid that gave off an aggressively nauseating stench.

There were specks of black light shimmering within the liquid, and it was squirming incessantly as if it were alive.

Chapter 11: Awakening

Judging from the careful look on Daoist Master White Stone's face, it was clear that this black liquid was quite important to him. With a wave of his hand, he released a burst of black light that enveloped the liquid before falling upon the black block of ice.

As soon as the liquid came into contact with the ice block, it immediately seeped in, quickly turning the transparent block of ice murky black in color, to the extent that the figure of the young man inside became rather blurry and indistinguishable.

A pleased look appeared on Daoist Master White Stone's face, and he stowed the gourd away before sitting down again with his legs crossed.

This liquid was the Black Corpse Soul Corruption Bane that he had carefully refined using over 10 types of rare ingredients. It was an extremely vicious solution capable of infiltrating a cultivator's spiritual sense and harming their soul.

Daoist Master White Stone made a hand seal, and the specks of black light within the ice instantly began to move, with a part of it beginning to shift toward Liu Shi's head.

His plan was to only infuse a bit of the soul corruption bane at a time to gradually erase Liu Shi's soul. In doing so, he would be able to minimize the instinctive resistance that the subject would put up, thereby ensuring the highest probability of success.

Right as the first few specks of light made contact with Liu Shi's head, they immediately vanished into it.

Not only that, but all of the black specks of light in the entire block of ice erupted into a frenzy, surging rapidly into all parts of Liu Shi's body in an uncontrollable manner.

Daoist Master White Stone was extremely alarmed by this, and he frantically made hand seals in an attempt to regain control over the specks of black light, but it was already too late.

All of the Black Corpse Soul Corruption Bane vanished in the blink of an eye, but Liu Shi wasn't displaying any visible changes, and it was as if nothing had happened.

"What's going on? Where is my Black Corpse Soul Corruption Bane?" Daoist Master White Stone rose to his feet with a furious and alarmed expression while releasing his spiritual sense to examine Liu Shi's body over and over again.

However, no matter how much he searched, he wasn't able to find anything amiss.

He stared intently at Liu Shi through the block of ice, then took a deep breath, and the enraged look on his face quickly faded as his brows furrowed tightly in contemplation.

"He's not giving off any magic power fluctuations, so he's definitely not a cultivator. Could it be that he's taken some type of spirit medicine or is carrying some type of protective treasure that just so happens to be able to counteract my Black Corpse Soul Corruption Bane?"

With that in mind, his gaze wandered over to Liu Shi's chest, where there was a slight bulge beneath his robes, and there was a faint glimmer of dark green light there.

In the end, Daoist Master White Stone still decided against undoing the ice seal to search Liu Shi's body. After all, once the array was activated, it couldn't be easily cut off.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce a green gourd, then released an incantation seal, and green light flashed from the opening of the gourd, following which around a dozen thin, dark green insects flew out from within.

These insects were around the same thickness as a strand of hair and around half a foot in length each. They flew through the air while screeching incessantly, and as soon as they emerged, they immediately transformed into streaks of green light that flew into the ice as if they had no substance, then immediately attempted to burrow their way into the top of Liu Shi's head.

Bursts of peculiar screeching rang out from within the ice, but no matter how hard the green insects tried, they were unable to burrow even a single millimeter into the skin on Liu Shi's head.

It was as if there were some type of invisible power in Liu Shi's head that was keeping the insects at bay.

Daoist Master White Stone's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he was finally becoming a little uneasy.

However, after a brief silence, the unease in his eyes was replaced by fury, and he harrumphed coldly, "There's no way an imbecile like you can oppose me!"

With a wave of his hand, he drew the green insects back into his gourd, then gritted his teeth before chanting an incantation.

A burst of gray light flew up from his body, hovering above his head. Within the gray light was a small gray flag, which swelled several times in size in the blink of an eye.

There were countless layers of runes inscribed onto the small flag, striking the beholder with a sense of disorientation, but all of these runes were completely dull and devoid of luster.

Daoist Master White Stone bit through the tip of his own tongue before releasing a mouthful of blood essence, which vanished into the flag. At the same time, he made a hand seal, releasing streaks of black light that also vanished into the gray flag. The flag immediately began to glow with dazzling light, and the runes inscribed upon them gradually began to brighten, following which a layer of gray mist rose up from the flag's surface.

The gray flag then expanded even further, swelling to around 10 feet in size, and the light on its surface flashed as a series of indistinct skull projections flew out from within. There were a total of around seven to eight of these projections, and every single one of them was wailing in a ghastly manner as they pounced toward Liu Shi.

Their collective voices instantly began to echo throughout the secret chamber.

Daoist Master White Stone's eyes were wide and bloodshot as he stared intently at the skull projections.

Right at this moment, an unexpected turn of events arose.

Right as the skull projections were about to plunge into the giant block of ice, the faint shadow of Liu Shi that was cast onto the ground suddenly rippled like water, following which a black object flew out from within before transforming into a sinister ghostly head with a pair of horns on its head.

The ghostly head was around the size of a washbasin, and it was cackling incessantly. The green flames in its eyes flickered as it cast its gaze toward the skull projections, and it opened its mouth up wide to release a vast expanse of silver light.

It was as if this silver light were the bane of the skull projections' existence, and they were completely powerless to evade as they were swept up by the golden light before being devoured by the ghostly head.

After that, the sinister ghostly head smacked its hideous lips, seemingly still not satisfied by the meal. Immediately thereafter, the golden flames in its eyes flashed, and it turned around before releasing a large burst of azure qi out of its mouth, then vanished on the spot in the blink of an eye.

The azure qi struck Liu Shi in the face before vanishing into his body without a sound.

All of this happened in the blink of an eye, concluding before Daoist Master White Stone even had a chance to react.

As a Core Formation cultivator, Daoist Master White Stone considered himself to be quite experienced and knowledgeable in the field of cultivation, but he had never seen anything so strange before, and he was completely rooted to the spot, at a loss for what to do.

Right at this moment, a crisp crack rang out, and a series of white cracks suddenly appeared on the surface of the block of black ice, following which Liu Shi slowly opened his eyes.

His eyes were far clearer than before and were no longer looking lost and vacant.

He inspected his surroundings, then furrowed his brows and shrugged his shoulders slightly.

A resounding boom rang out as the cone of fire struck the light barrier, and having already been struggling to hold itself together, the light barrier instantly shattered upon impact.

A loud thump rang out as the entire block of ice exploded outward from the inside, sending shattered chunks of black ice flying in all directions before clattering onto the ground.

Liu Shi raised his head to take a glance at Daoist Master White Stone, and it seemed like he was about to say something, but in the next instant, a disoriented look suddenly appeared on his face, and he threw his hands over his own head as he began to howl in agony.

The joints in his body cracked and popped while his arms and legs expanded like an inflating balloon, and in the blink of an eye, his body had swelled to around twice its original size. At the same time, countless golden scales around the size of copper coins had appeared over the surface of his skin, including his face and his neck.

These scales looked as if they were forged from pure gold and were shimmering with a cold light, giving off a completely indestructible appearance.

Daoist Master White Stone was flabbergasted to see this, and he knew that at this point, things had already completely spiraled out of his control.

Upon returning to his senses, a fierce look appeared on his face, and he gritted his teeth before opening his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which vanished into the gray flag in a flash.

The gray flag began to glow brightly again, and the runes on its surface began to squirm as if they had sprung to life. A burst of cracking rang out, and the flag abruptly transformed into a gray centipede that was 50 to 60 feet in length.

Daoist Master White Stone then patted the storage bag hanging from his waist, and seven or eight fist-sized black balls came flying out. Black qi was swirling around the balls, and they were giving off an incredibly pungent stench.

In spite of the terrible stench, the gray centipede let loose a joyful cry as it opened its mouth and eagerly devoured the black balls. Large black sections immediately appeared on the surface of its exoskeleton, and those areas rapidly expanded, turning its entire body pitch black in the blink of an eye. At the same time, its exoskeleton had taken on a metallic sheen, as if it were constructed from impregnable black steel.

The centipede screeched in excitement as faint red light began to glow in its tiny eyes. It roamed through the secret chamber, and as its sickle-like legs scratched across the hard stone walls, they were able to inflict a series of deep marks onto the walls like hot knives cutting through butter.

At the same time, the surrounding stone walls were stained an inky black color and began to give off a foul stench, clearly indicating that the centipede's legs were tipped with some type of extremely potent poison.

"Kill him!" Daoist Master White Stone roared as he pointed at Liu Shi.

Chapter 12: I Am Han Li

The black centipede screeched as it shook its body from side to side, then shot forward as a black shadow, reaching Liu Shi in the blink of an eye. It opened its mouth to reveal rows of dagger-like white fangs that were shimmering with a sinister light, and it bit down viciously upon Liu Shi's shoulder.

Liu Shi was still screaming with his hands clutching at his own head, completely oblivious to what was happening around him, and the centipede was able to chomp down onto his shoulder without any resistance.

A cruel smile appeared on Daoist Master White Stone's face upon seeing this.

He was well aware of how powerful the centipede was. It was capable of even shattering the average magic tool with a single bite, and what was even more terrifying about it was that its entire body was covered in lethal poison that could kill even with the slightest wound.

However, in the next instant, Daoist Master White Stone's smile abruptly stiffened.

The black centipede suddenly let loose an agonized screech as it reared back with blood gushing out of its mouth, and all of its sharp fangs had been completely shattered.

As for the golden scales on Liu Shi's shoulder, there wasn't even a single mark that had been left on them.

Even though the black centipede's fangs had been shattered, the pain seemed to have ignited its ferocity, and it wrapped itself around Liu Shi like a constricting boa, slicing at his body from all directions with its sharp legs.

Sparks were sent flying everywhere, but Liu Shi's scales remained completely unharmed.

Daoist Master White Stone was so shocked to see this that his eyes were on the verge of popping out of their sockets.

"I remember everything now... I am Han Li, the number one cultivator of the human race and the most powerful Grand Ascension cultivator of the Spirit Realm!"

All of a sudden, Liu Shi's screaming ceased, and he suddenly raised his head to reveal a pair of bright and clear eyes that were no longer disoriented in the slightest.

He was none other than Han Li, who had ascended to the Immortal Realm after enduring countless hardships in the Spirit Realm. [1]

Han Li didn't even look at the black centipede that was wrapped around his body as he plunged his hand into the hard exoskeleton on its back. His hand was like a steel spike, and after impaling the centipede, he casually tore it off himself with ease.

The black centipede was screeching incessantly as it thrashed desperately from side to side, but was unable to get free.

A dull thump rang out as Han Li's hand quivered slightly, and a burst of enormous power immediately surged throughout the centipede's entire body.

With one final anguished wail, the centipede fell completely limp and was unable to struggle any further.

Han Li plunged his other hand into the creature's body as well, then spread his arms wide to tear the centipede into two, then casually tossed the two halves of its body aside.

The two halves of the centipede's carcass spasmed violently on the ground for a moment before reverting back to the small black flag, which had already been torn into two, and the spiritual light glowing on its surface had completely faded, clearly indicating that it had been ruined.

All of this had happened in the blink of an eye, and Daoist Master White Stone was still looking on with a slack-jawed expression, unable to believe what he was seeing.

Only now did Han Li turn to take a glance at Daoist Master White Stone, and as soon as Daoist Master White Stone met Han Li's gaze, he immediately shuddered involuntarily. He felt as if his heart had been plunged into a bottomless glacial pit, and his entire body was freezing cold.

His expression changed several times in succession, following which he abruptly let loose a loud cry as he made a hand seal.

The black array in the secret chamber immediately began to glow brightly as a loud buzzing sound rang out, and tendrils of black mist surged rapidly toward Han Li again.

At the same time, Daoist Master White Stone swept a sleeve through the air to release a white flying spear, which shot forth toward the door of the secret chamber in an attempt to facilitate his escape.

"You're not going anywhere!" Han Li harrumphed coldly as golden light flashed from the scales on his arm, and he slammed his fist into the ground.

A resounding boom rang out as shattered stone chunks flew in all directions, and a massive crater was smashed into the ground. The black array was completely destroyed, and all of the black mist also ceased to exist.

Daoist Master White Stone shuddered as he heard the sound of the array being destroyed behind him, but at this point, he had already flown to the entrance of the secret chamber and was about to crash through it to make his escape.

However, right at this moment, a figure appeared directly in front of him, following which an explosive boom rang out.

Daoist Master White Stone was instantly sent flying back like a ragdoll, crashing heavily into the stone wall with a resounding thump.

Daoist Master White Stone immediately threw up a large mouthful of blood from the impact, and he slumped onto the ground with a horrified expression. The flying spear that was previously beneath his feet was already nowhere to be seen.

Han Li was standing at the entrance of the secret chamber, and he slowly withdrew his outstretched left fist, then abruptly appeared directly in front of Daoist Master White Stone again in a wraith-like manner, looking down at him with a cold expression.

"Please spare me, Senior! I was a fool to have failed to recognize your brilliance! I'm willing to offer up everything I have in exchange for my life!" Daoist Master White Stone was trembling uncontrollably as he struggled to a kneeling position, then pulled out the storage bag from his waist before setting it down reverently in front of Han Li's feet with both hands.

At the same time, he was kowtowing desperately with such force that his head was slamming audibly into the ground.

Han Li remained completely expressionless, and he didn't even bother to take a glance at the storage bag.

Han Li's silence struck further panic into Daoist Master White Stone's heart, and he hurriedly continued, "Aside from this, I have treasures elsewhere that I can offer to you, Senior. As a guest elder at the prime minister's manor, I know where the treasure pavilion in the prime minister's manor is. As soon as you give the nod, I can fetch all those treasures and bring them to you right away!"

For the sake of survival, he was willing to completely discard his moral compass.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and it seemed that he was rather tempted by the offer.

The golden light glowing from his body slowly faded, and Daoist Master White Stone was ecstatic to see this.

However, right when he was about to say something, Han Li suddenly raised his hand before making a grabbing motion, releasing a ball of black qi that vanished directly into Daoist Master White Stone's face at Han Li's behest.

"Spare me, Senior!"

Daoist Master White Stone was greatly alarmed by this, and he hurriedly inspected his own internal condition. However, he didn't discover anything amiss, but that only made him even more terrified.

"Rest assured, I won't kill you for now, I'm just repaying the favor for what you tried to do to me. All it'll take from me is a single thought for that black of black qi in your body to explode, and I'm sure you know what'll happen to you after that. Also, I've regained my memories. My surname is Han, not Liu," Han Li said in an indifferent voice, and his body began to shrink back to its original size while the golden scales on his skin quickly faded.

Daoist Master White Stone's face was deathly pale, but he was quite relieved to hear that Han Li was going to spare him, and he hurriedly nodded in response.

Han Li grabbed onto Daoist Master White Stone's collar to lift him up from the ground, then tapped his right index finger against the daoist priest's glabella and released a burst of black light into it from his fingertip.

"Senior..." Daoist Master White Stone was horrified, thinking that Han Li had suddenly changed his mind, but before he had a chance to say anything, his eyes suddenly became completely glazed over.

Han Li's lips were tightly pursed, and a layer of sweat appeared on his forehead as his complexion paled slightly.

Moments later, he exhaled, and the black light glowing from his fingertip faded.

Daoist Master White Stone's eyes rolled into the back of his head, and he immediately fell unconscious.

Han Li tossed him onto the ground, and only after taking a few deep breaths did his complexion return to normal. However, his brows then furrowed tightly, and a grim look appeared on his face.

He had just unleashed a soul search technique that had allowed him to gather the information that he wanted from Daoist Master White Stone.

Han Li turned his gaze toward Liu Le'er, who was also unconscious, and a gentle look appeared in his eyes. Without any further injection of magic power, the golden rope around her had already fallen slack, but she was still trapped within the black light barrier.

He made his way over to her side, then swept a hand through the air to release a burst of enormous force that shattered the black light barrier in an instant.

Liu Le'er's body was riddled with wounds, and looking down at her, Han Li heaved a faint sigh. After a moment of hesitation, he made a hand seal,

A hint of color immediately returned to Liu Le'er's pale cheeks, and the wounds on her body began to heal at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

"You've been through a lot the past few years. With that, I don't have much magic power left," Han Li murmured as he looked at Liu Le'er.

He then made his way over to Daoist Master White Stone before picking up his storage bag, then tore it into two, causing all of its contents to fall onto the ground.

Most of its contents were materials and ingredients, but there were also some pills.

After some careful examination, Han Li picked out two vials, tipping out an azure pill and a red pill from the vials before feeding them to Liu Le'er.

[1]. For those who haven't, please read the first installment of RMJI to see the story of Han Li's adventures in the Spirit Realm.

[Back]

Chapter 13: Mo Guang

Only after seeing Liu Le'er's breathing and aura gradually even out did Han Li sit onto the ground again with his legs crossed.

He reached into his own collar, and after some searching, he pulled out the accessory that he had always worn around his neck, which was a small vial that was light green in color.

There were a series of dark green leaf patterns all over the surface of the small vials, and they were extremely beautiful and life-like.

Han Li gently massaged the vial with his fingers, and an absentminded look appeared in his eyes as he felt its familiar texture.

After being lost in deep thought for a long while, he suddenly stowed the vial away before calling out the name "Mo Guang". [1]

The secret chamber was completely silent aside from the echoing of Han Li's voice.

However, moments later, the shadow in front of him warped slightly, then elongated forward marginally.

All of a sudden, a dark humanoid figure split itself off from Han Li's elongated shadow before slowly rising to its feet.

The figure had skin that was as black as ink and his appearance was rather similar to Han Li's. He was wearing a black robe, and his head of black hair was unbound, casually spilling down around his head. What was most remarkable about him was the indescribable aura of decay that he was giving off.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Han," the figure said in a wooden manner as his gaze fell upon Han Li.

"What happened, Mo Guang? How did you become like this?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I don't know. I only awakened a few years earlier than you did, and as soon as I awakened, I discovered that I had lost all of my spiritual nature, and all that remained of me was a wisp of my soul. Due to the Heavenly Devil Contract, I can only reside in your shadow, and I'm unable to show myself unless you summon me or someone is trying to hurt you," Mo Guang replied in a rather mechanical voice.

Han Li was silent for a moment before asking, "Do you remember the last thing that happened before you fell into your slumber?"

"I can recall everything before your ascension clearly, but after your ascension, all I can recall is that you left the Ascension Platform with that immortal by the name of Gao Sheng, and that's where my memories end," Mo Guang replied.

"I see. My memories are also cut off from the moment we left the Ascension Platform. It looks like we'll have to seek out Gao Sheng if we want to know exactly what happened. However, we're currently not in a very good situation.

“I searched that man's soul just now, and it seems that not only are we in the Spirit Domain Realm, a lower realm directly under the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, 300 years have already passed by, which means that both of us are missing three centuries worth of memories," Han Li said.

"That is indeed terrible. Do you have any plans, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang asked.

"There may only be a wisp of your soul left, but you're still a Heavenly Devilish Monarch. Surely you still have some abilities up your sleeve," Han Li said as he raised an eyebrow.

"At the moment, I've lost almost all of my magic power and abilities, and I can only unleash some low-grade secret techniques," Mo Guang replied.

In spite of this piece of bad news, Han Li seemed to have drawn reassurance from it.

"This is already far better than the situation that I envisioned. Compared with you, I'm in a far worse state. I just examined myself, and not only have I lost all of my treasures and pills, nothing remains of my magic power, and my soul and physical body have all suffered severe trauma, so I'm currently nothing more than a shadow of my former self. The only good news is that I've finally awakened.

“As long as I can find the right spirit medicines to treat my condition, I should be able to recover very quickly. On top of that, I can sense Fellow Daoist Xie and the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch's existence through their soul contracts, but I don't know where they are. It looks like I'll have to find a way to recover them in the future."

"It sounds like you truly are in a troublesome situation, Fellow Daoist Han. In order to find Gao Sheng, you'll have to return to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. If I recall correctly, it's far easier to ascend to the Immortal Realm from a realm that's directly under it, but you'll still require the assistance of an Ascension Platform and an immense amount of magic power to protect your body and allow you to forcibly break through the boundaries of the realm," Mo Guang said.

"There's no hurry in returning to the Immortal Realm. There's plenty of time for me to think about that. However, one thing is for sure: whoever is responsible for reducing me to this state, I'll be sure to have a good chat with them once I return to the Immortal Realm," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice, and his expression was quite calm, but one couldn't help but wonder if he were truly as calm as he appeared.

Mo Guang offered no response.

"Are you willing to continue following me, Fellow Daoist Mo Guang? As you can see, I'm in an extremely terrible situation right now. If you want to leave, I won't stop you."

"There's no need to test me, Fellow Daoist Han. Even in my current condition, the Heavenly Devil Contract is still effective, and as I am now, I won't even be able to resist the binding power of the contract. If I were to try and leave you now, I would be placing myself in even more severe peril," Mo Guang replied.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he said, "Alright, in that case, I'll do my best to ensure that you don't regret your decision. As long as I can recover to the peak of my powers, I'll be sure to do everything in my power to restore your soul and spiritual nature. What we have to do now is gather some information and resources from this realm to see if we can recover my magic power to its former heights."

"I'll leave everything to you, Fellow Daoist Han. In my current state, it's a struggle to show myself for too long, so I'm going back to rest and recuperate," Mo Guang said in a calm manner, then transformed into a cloud of black mist that quickly vanished into Han Li's shadow.

Han Li exhaled before taking a glance at Liu Le'er, who was still sound asleep, and he also closed his eyes to rest.

Only after close to half a day later did Liu Le'er finally wake up.

As soon as she opened her eyes, she caught sight of Han Li, who was seated beside her with his legs crossed and his eyes closed, and the Daoist Master White Stone, who was standing off to the side with a wary expression.

Almost at the exact same moment, Han Li opened his eyes and said with a smile, "You're finally awake."

Liu Le'er's body instantly stiffened upon hearing this, and she looked into Han Li's eyes with a complex expression as she murmured, "Brother Rock, you're all cured now..."

"Le'er, my name is Han Li. You can call me Brother Han from now on," Han Li replied in a gentle voice.

A rather dejected look appeared on Liu Le'er's face upon hearing this, and she reluctantly obliged. "Brother Han."

In this moment, the young man before her was looking rather unfamiliar.

Han Li could tell what she was thinking from the changes in her expression, and he smiled as he said, "I may be awake now, but I still remember everything that happened these past few years. I'm still Brother Rock to you, and that's never going to change."

Liu Le'er was ecstatic to hear this, and tears welled up in her eyes as she dove straight into Han Li's arms.

"I know you have many questions you want to ask me, but now's not the time. I'll explain everything to you when a suitable opportunity arises," Han Li said in a gentle voice as he patted Liu Le'er's head in a doting manner.

Liu Le'er nodded obediently in response and didn't ask any further questions. However, her gaze then fell upon Daoist Master White Stone, and a wary look immediately appeared in her eyes.

[1]. For more information on Mo Guang, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2435: Soul Badge.

[Back]

Chapter 14: Attack

"Don't worry, Fellow Daoist White Stone is on our side now. He wouldn't dare to do anything to you in the future," Han Li said with a smile as he rose to his feet, taking a subtle glance at Daoist Master White Stone as he did so.

The elderly daoist priest shuddered upon hearing this, and he hurriedly nodded insistently to pledge his loyalty, while his back was already drenched in cold sweat.

Liu Le'er's expression eased slightly upon seeing this.

"Let's get out of here."

Han Li latched onto Liu Le'er's hand and made his way over to the stone door of the secret chamber before pressing his palm against it.

Right as he was about to push the door open, he suddenly stopped what he was doing, and his brows furrowed slightly.

Liu Le'er could sense the slight change in Han Li's demeanor, and she raised her head to look up at him with an inquisitive expression.

"What a coincidence!" Han Li chuckled before pushing the stone door open and making his way outside.

The sky outside was quite dark, indicating that it was already nighttime, but from the island, one could see that the entirety of the Yu Manor was as bright as day, having been illuminated by flames.

Sounds of battle could be heard ringing out from the front yard, interspersed with booming explosions.

Dense smoke was rising up from all over the Yu Manor like a series of black demonic dragons ascending into the night sky.

Even though Han Li's trio was situated on the island far away from where everyone else in the Yu Manor was, there was still a remarkably strong scent of bloodshed in the air.

"What's going on?" Liu Le'er asked as she swept her gaze around the Yu Manor with an incredulous expression.

"Do you know what's happening?" Han Li asked as he turned to Daoist Master White Stone.

"I'm afraid not, Senior. Perhaps the Yu Family is being attacked by its enemies," Daoist Master White Stone replied in a hesitant voice, then fell silent with a respectful expression, awaiting further instructions.

Han Li took a glance at Liu Le'er to find that she was also looking up at him, and after a moment of contemplation, he said, "I suppose I owe Yu Qi a favor for waking me up from my prior state, so I can't just leave without doing anything. Let's go and take a look."

With that, the three of them emerged from the daoist temple, then traveled toward the front yard of the Yu Manor.

The closer they drew to the front yard, the clearer the sounds of battle became. By the time the three of them arrived at that circular archway, they were greeted by the sight of a hellish scene.

The small courtyard beyond the archway was laden with piles upon piles of mangled bodies, most of which were wearing the armor assigned to the guards of the prime minister's manor, while only a very small proportion of them were wearing black assassin garments.

The courtyard was illuminated by fire, and there was a white light barrier in the corner of the courtyard that was closest to the front yard, which was keeping around a dozen black-suited figures at bay.

Right at this moment, a spiral-shaped cone of fire shot up from the group of black-suited figures, and upon reaching an altitude of several dozen feet above the light barrier, it suddenly descended from above, swooping down like a rapidly revolving fiery dragon.

A resounding boom rang out as the cone of fire struck the light barrier, and having already been struggling to hold itself together, the light barrier instantly shattered upon impact.

Immediately thereafter, a deep voice rang out. "Kill them!"

The dozen or so black-suited figures immediately charged toward the corner with their weapons raised.

"Stop them," Han Li ordered in an indifferent voice.

Daoist Master White Stone immediately stepped into the courtyard before opening his mouth to release a burst of black light.

The ball of black light contained the same serpentine flying sword from before, and it arrived above the black-suited figures in the blink of an eye.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as the flying sword shuddered, releasing several dozen bursts of black sword qi that shot down rapidly from above.

The sound of flesh and bones being punctured rang out incessantly within the courtyard, accompanied by agonized howls.

All of the black-suited figures were instantly killed on the spot, with the exception of one with a short beard who managed to react quite quickly and rolled several dozen feet away.

"Who's there?" the black-suited man asked in an aggressive voice.

Daoist Master White Stone offered no response as he swept a hand through the air, and the flying sword that was hovering in mid-air instantly came swooping down, hurtling directly toward the man's chest.

The black-suited man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air to release a small blue shield, which quickly expanded to form a giant shield that positioned itself in front of him.

At the same time, he raised his other hand, and the flames of the cone of fire reared up as it sped rapidly toward the black flying sword.

A resounding boom rang out, and flames scattered in all directions as the cone of fire exploded, falling down from above as balls of fire.

As for the black flying sword, it pierced directly into the black-suited man's chest. The giant blue shield had also been punctured as if it were nothing more than a papier mache structure, posing no resistance to the flying sword at all.

"You're... a Core Formation cultivator..." the black-suited man gurgled as blood poured out of his mouth and nostrils.

Daoist Master White Stone drew his flying sword back to himself with a wave of his hand, then scoffed in a disdainful voice, "To think that a mere Foundation Establishment cultivator dares to oppose someone as mighty as myself..."

Before he finished his sentence, he abruptly shut his mouth, then stole a fearful glance at Han Li.

Han Li didn't react to his arrogant proclamation at all. All he did was make his way over to a corner of the courtyard, where two people were huddled together.

One of them was a young man in a bloodstained azure robe with a head of disheveled hair. He was a Foundation Establishment cultivator, but his aura was quite feeble, and it was clear that he was close to being a spent force.

Behind him was a young woman in servant's clothing, curled up into a ball. Her entire body was stained with blood, and she was trembling with fear, not daring to raise her head.

Liu Le'er faltered slightly upon identifying the young woman, then called out, "Sister Xiao Wu?"

The young woman's body stiffened upon hearing this, and she slowly poked her head out from behind the young man. In the instant that she caught sight of Liu Le'er, she immediately burst into tears.

Liu Le'er hurriedly rushed forward to help her to her feet.

The young man hesitated momentarily, then also struggled to his feet before imploring, "Daoist Master White Stone, please save the young mistress... Hurry!"

Daoist Master White Stone faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he offered no response. Instead, he took a glance at Han Li.

"Where is the young mistress?" Han Li asked.

The young man clearly didn't recognize Han Li, so he was rather taken aback by this question, but he still replied, "When Xiao Wu and I were sent to request reinforcements from the island, the young mistress was being protected by the other elders at the main estate, but given how fearsome the enemies are, I don't think they'll be able to last much longer."

"Stay here and treat your own wounds. Xiao Wu, you're most familiar with the layout of the Yu Manor, lead the way to the main estate," Han Li instructed in an indifferent manner.

At this point, Xiao Wu had stopped crying under Liu Le'er's consolation, and she turned to Han Li with a perplexed expression, wondering why the man who had been mentally handicapped just a few hours ago had suddenly started issuing orders to everyone.

The young man was also rather bewildered.

It was clear to him that Han Li was the leader of the group. Daoist Master White Stone was one of the most respected figures in the Yu Manor, yet he seemed to also be content to follow Han Li's lead.

"Alright, come with me."

Xiao Wu took a moment to collect herself, then rushed toward the front yard, followed closely by Han Li's trio.

Some time had already passed since the Yu Manor was first attacked, and the entire front yard of the manor was laden with bodies, some of which were guards, while others were servants. It seemed that the black-suited figures were intent on slaughtering everyone in the Yu Manor.

Liu Le'er was horrified by the sights that she beheld along the way. Even though she was already aware of the cruel and bloodthirsty nature of humans, the scenes presented to her still made her develop a completely new understanding of the human race.

Aside from the piles of bodies everywhere, they also encountered several groups of black-suited figures, but almost all of them were killed by Daoist Master White Stone in mere moments.

Occasionally, they would encounter some Foundation Establishment cultivators, but they were no match for Daoist Master White Stone, either.

Thus, the four of them passed through a corridor and continued to rush toward the main estate.

Chapter 15: Badge

At the main estate of the Yu Manor, the previously lavish and immaculately maintained courtyard had been reduced to a set of ruins. There were corpses and flowing blood everywhere, and the stench of blood in the air was so strong that it was downright nauseating.

All of the survivors of the Yu Family were gathered here, and there were only about two dozen of them left. Some were young and some were old, and Yu Qi and the second young master of the family were both among them.

All of them wore horrified expressions, and there were a few women among them who were trembling uncontrollably. Only Yu Qi and a few others were able to maintain some modicum of composure.

There was a particularly large number of black-suited figures here, close to 30 at a rough glance, and they had trapped the surviving members of the Yu Family in the courtyard from three sides. They were split up into small groups of around three to five people, and all of them were cultivators with most of them wielding magic tools.

Thankfully, the other elders of the Yu Family finally arrived to protect the surviving members of the Yu Family.

The Yu Family was the family of the Prosperous Nation's prime minister, so the cultivator elders assigned to the family were all quite powerful. In particular, there was a middle-aged red-robed cultivator standing in front of the surviving members of the Yu Family.

He had pockmarks all over his face and a short figure that was completely unremarkable, but red light was surging around his entire body, and he was giving off the enormous spiritual pressure of a Core Formation cultivator.

There was a crimson fire bead treasure that was hovering above his head, and several crimson balls of fire were revolving around it.

The other three elders of the Yu Family consisted of two men and a woman, and their cultivation base was inferior to that of the red-robed man, but they were also quite formidable in their own right. One of them was a black-robed young woman with a set of elegant features, but they were marred by a scar on her face. She was standing on one side of the red-robed cultivator, while another thin middle-aged man with a pair of deep-set eyes stood on his other side.

The final cultivator was a thin elderly man with dark skin, resembling an old farmer, and he was standing slightly back from the trio.

Even though there was a Core Formation cultivator among them, they were still only a group of four, and they had to prioritize the safety of the Yu Family's survivors, so they found themselves locked in an impasse against the black-suited cultivators around them.

"We can't keep going like this. Protect the young mistress and everyone else, and prepare to rush out as soon as the opportunity arises!" the red-robed cultivator instructed, then made a hand seal before opening his mouth to release a burst of red light, which vanished into the fire bead above his head.

The fire bead instantly began to rotate at a far greater speed, to the point that it had become a crimson blur.

Around a dozen giant fireballs flew out of the bead before quickly fusing together to form a thick fiery dragon that was over 100 feet in length.

The fiery dragon was covered in a layer of clear-cut red scales, and it let loose a furious roar as it swooped down into the crowd of black-suited figures up ahead.

The first group of black-suited figures were caught off guard and sent flying by the fiery dragon, with two of them being reduced to ashes on the spot.

Immediately thereafter, the fiery dragon swept its tail violently through the air to release a wave of fire, forcing all of the black-suited figures in the general vicinity to rush back in retreat.

After a brief moment of chaos, all of the black-suited cultivators steadied themselves before bombarding the fiery dragon with a barrage of attacks.

The fiery dragon's giant body swayed from side to side from the impact of the attacks, and the flames on its body were churning incessantly, but none of the attacks were sufficient to deal a fatal blow. The dragon continued to wreak havoc to its heart's content, and after just a few seconds, close to half of all of the black-suited figures were either dead or injured.

"Go!" the red-robed cultivator yelled at his three companions.

However, right at this moment, a burst of blurry black light shot forth at an incredible speed, striking the lower abdomen of the fiery dragon directly like a bolt of black lightning.

The burst of black light pierced deep into the fiery dragon's body, revealing itself to be a black arrow that was riddled with black runes.

The runes on the arrow's shaft abruptly released an enormous burst of black light before exploding violently with an almighty boom, sending a giant dark red mushroom cloud rising up into the air, causing violent tremors to run through the nearby ground.

A huge hole was instantly blown into the fiery dragon's lower abdomen, and the flames around it flashed erratically.

The red-robed cultivator and the other three elders were all stunned to see this.

Another black-suited figure had appeared at the entrance of the courtyard, and he was wielding a large black bow with black light surging around his body. The aura that he was giving off indicated that he was a peak Foundation Establishment cultivator.

Immediately thereafter, four more black-suited figures emerged from the darkness behind him. They were all also at the peak of the Foundation Establishment Stage, wielding the same black bows that they drew and fired in unison.

Four black runed arrows shot forth, racing rapidly through the night sky like a cluster of black shooting stars.

The red-robed cultivator hurriedly made a series of hand seals to control the fiery dragon to evade the arrows, but it was far too big a target, and the archers were exceptionally skilled. In the end, it was only able to dodge one of the arrows, while the other three all struck their target.

The three runed arrows exploded in unison, and three more massive holes were blown into the fiery dragon's body.

As a result, it was unable to maintain its form any longer, and it exploded into a flurry of crimson flames that quickly fizzled out into nothingness.

The red-robed cultivator gave a muffled groan as his body swayed slightly.

Right at this moment, a ghastly screech rang out, and a streak of white light shot out of the darkness. It was several times faster than even the runed arrows from before, and it reached the red-robed cultivator in the blink of an eye.

The red-robed cultivator was greatly alarmed by this, and the crimson fire bead above his head immediately flew forward to meet the streak of white light at his behest. At the same time, he flew back while raising his hands to release two streaks of light, one blue and one red, containing a small blue sword and a crimson flying trident, respectively, both of which also flew toward the streak of white light.

The white light flashed, revealing itself to be a blade of bone that was around three feet in length with gusts of Yin wind swirling around it.

Large swathes of black threads abruptly appeared on the surface of the blade amid a faint buzzing sound, and the threads wrapped themselves around the fire bead, the blue sword, and the crimson flying trident.

The spiritual light radiating from the three treasures instantly dimmed, and they slowed down significantly, looking as if they could fall out of the air at any moment.

Meanwhile, the bone blade passed right through the three sluggish treasures in a flash, then suddenly appeared near the red-robed cultivator's head before flashing through the air like lightning.

The red-robed cultivator let loose a bloodcurdling cry that was abruptly cut short as his head slid off his neck, having been decapitated.

Blood spurted several feet up into the air like a gory geyser, and his headless body swayed momentarily before toppling to the ground.

"Daoist Master Red Robe!" the survivors of the Yu Family exclaimed in unison.

The other three elders were also horrified to see this, and they all backtracked a few steps, unsure of how to proceed.

Immediately thereafter, a young man with a set of sinister features slowly emerged from the crowd. He was none other than the man who had been spying on Yu Qi in secret back in Farbright City, but he wasn't accompanied by the gray-robed man here.

All of the surrounding black-suited figures immediately stopped what they were doing and bowed respectfully toward the young man.

With a wave of his hand, the white bone blade shot back to the young man, carrying Daoist Master Red Robe's three treasures along with it.

He took a glance at the three treasures, and a disdainful look appeared on his face, but he still stowed them away before turning to the survivors of the Yu Family with a cold expression. "Kill them all! Don't let a single one of them live!"

"Yes!" the black-suited figures hurriedly replied in unison before stepping forward to carry out his orders.

The three elders of the Yu Family looked on with grim expressions, but none of them stepped in to intervene.

Some of the women and children among the Yu Family's survivors were sobbing in despair, while others had already collapsed to the ground, and there were even a few who had soiled themselves.

"Hold on!"

A pleasant voice rang out, and Yu Qi stepped forward to confront the black-suited figures.

She had put on her male attire once again, but there was no disguising the hint of seduction in her features.

The young man's eyes immediately lit up at the sight of her, and his lecherous gaze roamed greedily over her body.

Yu Qi's face was quite pale, but she was still just barely able to maintain her composure. She fought back the urge to gouge out the deplorable young man's eyes as she pulled out a purple and golden badge before displaying it to the group.

There was an extremely vivid and detailed purple and golden flame design emblazoned upon the badge.

"How dare you slaughter the members of our Yu Family? Do you have no regard for the Cold Flame Sect?"

Chapter 16: Despair

The young man took a glance at the purple and golden badge, then turned his gaze back to Yu Qi with a faint smile. "Ah, I see you have an acceptance badge from the Cold Flame Sect. I've long heard that you are the number one beauty of Farbright City, and I can see that those rumors certainly aren't unfounded."

Yu Qi was instilled with some confidence by the fact that the young man recognized the badge in her hand, and she declared, "I don't care who you are, leave the Yu Manor right this instant. Otherwise, you'll be making an enemy out of the Cold Flame Sect!"

The three elders of the Yu Family were originally planning to take no further part in this confrontation, but they were all very much encouraged by this turn of events.

A hint of hope was also ignited in the hearts of the Yu Family's survivors.

The young man suddenly burst into laughter upon seeing this. "Am I supposed to be afraid of the Cold Flame Sect?"

"How dare you look down on the Cold Flame Sect?" Yu Qi accused with a furious expression.

"All you have is an acceptance badge, so you're not even an official disciple of the Cold Flame Sect. Even if you were an official disciple, did you think that would be enough to faze me?" A cold smile appeared on the young man's face as he flipped a hand over to produce a black badge that was around the same size as the badge in Yu Qi's hand, and there was a silver skull design emblazoned onto its surface.

A stunned look appeared on Yu Qi's face upon seeing this. "That's a Heavenly Ghost Sect inner court disciple badge! You're from the Heavenly Ghost Sect!"

The Heavenly Ghost Sect ranks alongside the Cold Flame Sect!

The three elders of the Yu Family drew a collective sharp breath, and they exchanged a glance with one another before falling silent.

A thought seemed to have occurred to Yu Qi, and a hint of color returned to her face as she declared, "Even if you're a disciple of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, don't forget that the Cold Flame Sect belongs to the Prosperous Nation. Are you trying to instigate a war between the two sects with your actions?"

"Under normal circumstances, I would say that you're correct, but I'm afraid that you're sorely mistaken here," the young man countered with a disdainful sneer.

Yu Qi faltered slightly upon hearing this.

"Let me fill you in. The Cold Flame Sect has already been defeated in the contest against our sect, and they've handed over the jurisdiction rights over the Prosperous Nation, so now, the entire nation belongs to our Heavenly Ghost Sect," the young man revealed with a cruel smile.

Yu Qi was completely rooted to the spot upon hearing this as if she had been struck by a bolt of lightning.

The three elders of the Yu Family were also stunned by this revelation, and they reflexively backed away to open up some distance between themselves and the surviving members of the Yu Family.

Everyone from the Yu Family was even more disheartened by this, and their hearts had completely sunk.

They didn't know much about the world of cultivators, but they could tell from this exchange that this was not good news for them.

"By the way, there's something else I forgot to mention that I'm sure you'll be very interested to hear," the young man continued as his sinister smile widened.

Yu Qi's heart jolted upon hearing this, and she knew that there could only be more bad news to come, but she still couldn't help but ask, "What is it?"

"Some of the officials in the imperial court of the Prosperous Nation dared to oppose the orders of our Heavenly Ghost Sect, and they've been charged with treason. Yesterday, all of them were beheaded in public in the capital city, and I recall that Prime Minister Yu seemed to have been among them, alongside his two sons who were also serving under him," the young man said as he looked directly into Yu Qi's eyes.

Yu Qi's vision darkened momentarily upon hearing this, and she collapsed to the ground, while the badge in her hand also slipped out of her grasp.

Everyone else from the Yu Family was also plunged even further into the depths of despair upon hearing this, and several women were unable to contain themselves any longer as they burst into tears.

Just a moment ago, they had been the esteemed members of Prime Minister Yu's family, revered by the common folk from their lofty perches at the upper echelons of society, but all of a sudden, they were told that their nation had been conquered, the prime minister had been beheaded, and they were about to follow him soon.

The despair on Yu Qi's face brought a look of sadistic pleasure to the young man's face, and his cheeks became flushed with excitement as he cackled like a madman.

He loved nothing more than to drive others into the abyss of despair before taking in their expressions at the height of their helplessness.

Once his cackling subsided, the flush in his cheeks gradually faded, and he ordered in a cold voice, "Kill everyone, but leave the young mistress alive."

The black-suited figures immediately gave affirmative responses before closing in on the surviving members of the Yu Family with cruel grins.

At this point, the three elders had already backed away to the side with their heads lowered, seemingly waiting for an opportunity to escape. The young man was quite pleased to see this, and he made no effort to stop them.

One of the black-suited figures approached the young man as he said with a fawning expression, "You have an exceptional eye, Young Master Qi! This woman possesses no cultivation base, but she's already received an acceptance badge from the Cold Flame Sect, which means that she must possess decent cultivation aptitude. She would be a perfect dual cultivation partner for you,"

The young man burst into laughter once again upon hearing this.

Yu Qi shuddered as a hint of clarity returned to her eyes, and a look of finality appeared on her face. With one swift motion, she drew a dagger from her waist before plunging it viciously toward her own heart.

The young man's smile stiffened upon seeing this, clearly not expecting her to be so fiery and unyielding, and it was already too late to stop her.

All of a sudden, a sharp gust of wind whistled through the air before striking the dagger in Yu Qi's hand, instantly sending it flying away before clattering onto the ground.

Several more sharp gusts of wind shot through the air, hurtling toward the black-suited figures who were about to slaughter the survivors of the Yu Family.

A string of agonized howls rang out, and the sharp gusts of wind were so strong that the black-suited figures who were struck were instantly sent flying with blood gushing out of their mouths.

All of their companions immediately stopped in their tracks with alarmed expressions.

"Who's there?" the young man asked as he turned toward an opening not far away.

Everyone else also turned toward the same direction, and the sound of footsteps rang out as several figures slowly emerged, revealing themselves to be none other than Han Li and his group.

The young man cast his gaze toward the group through narrowed eyes, but his gaze only lingered on Han Li for a brief moment before he quickly directed his attention toward Daoist Master White Stone.

"Daoist Master White Stone!"

"Daoist Master White Stone, save us!"

The survivors of the Yu Family were already awaiting death in a state of complete despair, but the arrival of Daoist Master White Stone instilled them with a renewed sense of hope, and they desperately implored for him to step in.

"Young Mistress!"

Xiao Wu paid no heed to the nearby black-suited figures as she rushed over to Yu Qi before helping her to her feet.

"Xiao Wu."

Yu Qi cast a complex gaze toward Daoist Master White Stone.

Daoist Master White Stone was a Core Formation cultivator, but the same had also applied to Daoist Master Red Robe, and he had been slain by the young man with ease, so Daoist Master White Stone was most likely no match for him, either.

All of a sudden, her gaze fell upon Han Li.

His physical appearance hadn't changed at all, but his eyes were no longer vacant, and he was giving off a sense of remarkable calmness given the situation that he was in.

"So you're Daoist Master White Stone? I'd advise you not to stick your nose into other people's business if you value your life!" the young man said as he turned to Daoist Master White Stone, and black light radiated from his body as he released a burst of enormous pressure.

Those sharp gusts of wind just now had been incredibly powerful, but they possessed no form, and it was as if they had arisen out of thin air.

The young man had no clue how those sharp gusts of wind had been generated, so he was rather wary of Daoist Master White Stone and was releasing his spiritual pressure for intimidation.

Daoist Master White Stone shuddered, and a hint of fear flashed through his eyes.

The spiritual pressure being released by the young man was already at the mid-Core Formation Stage, while he was only an early-Core Formation cultivator, so he was no match for the young man. With that in mind, he couldn't help but turn his gaze toward Han Li.

He had witnessed exactly what had happened earlier, so he knew that those sharp gusts of wind had been produced by nothing more than a few casual flicks of Han Li's finger.

A hint of a smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he didn't say anything.

Daoist Master White Stone's heart sank slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately made his decision, stepping forward in a righteous manner as he yelled, "I am an elder of the Yu Manor, how could I possibly just stand by and watch while you do as you please? You brazen bastards must be punished for the heinous acts you've committed here!"

A violent look appeared on the young man's face upon hearing this. "Fine. If you have a death wish, then I'll kill you along with everyone else!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he raised a hand, and his white bone blade shot forth directly toward Daoist Master White Stone.

At the same time, he made a series of hand seals, and a vast expanse of white light erupted from the bone blade. A series of white skull projections emerged within the white radiance, and a chorus of ghostly howls began to ring out incessantly.

Chapter 17: Slaying the Two Cultivators

"Look out, Daoist Master White Stone! Daoist Master Red Robe perished to this very same weapon!" Yu Qi cautioned in a loud voice.

Daoist Master White Stone was already greatly alarmed by the power imbued within the bone blade, and his expression changed drastically upon hearing this. His first instinct was to flee the scene, but with Han Li present, he had no choice but to grit his teeth before opening his mouth to release his serpentine flying sword.

He then quickly made a hand seal, and the sword began to glow with black light, wrapping around the bone blade like a black python.

A cold smile appeared on the young man's face as he made a sequence of hand seals before pointing a finger forward, and the light radiating from the bone blade became even brighter as it tore viciously through the air.

A dull thump rang out from the serpentine flying sword, and it was snapped into several pieces that fell out of the air.

Daoist Master White Stone hurriedly raised his hand to release a round azure shield to take the flying sword's place.

The light radiating from the bone blade had dimmed slightly, but its power wasn't diminished at all as it struck the azure shield with tremendous force.

This time, the azure shield was able to pose some resistance, but it was still snapped in half in the end. The bone blade was stopped in its tracks for a brief moment before glowing brightly once again as it continued to hurtle toward Daoist Master White Stone.

Daoist Master White Stone was greatly alarmed to see this, and he ducked behind Han Li during the split second that the bone blade was kept at bay by the azure shield.

In the past, even if he were no match for the young man, he would've still been able to put up a good fight. However, all of his most powerful treasures had been destroyed during his clash with Han Li earlier, so he was completely powerless to stop the bone blade.

In the blink of an eye, the bone blade appeared in front of Han Li before continuing onward at an incredible speed, aiming to slice through both Han Li and Daoist Master White Stone's bodies at the waist.

"Senior Han!" Daoist Master White Stone exclaimed in a panicked voice.

Han Li remained as calm as ever as he raised a hand, and golden light flashed from his palm as he reached out like lightning while a series of golden scales surfaced over his skin.

A loud clang rang out, and the light glowing from the bone blade completely faded, as did the ghostly howls that were ringing out incessantly. As for the bone blade itself, it had been caught in Han Li's grasp, and it was squirming and struggling incessantly like a small fish, but it was unable to break free.

"Impossible!"

The young man's eyes widened with incredulity, and he couldn't believe what he was seeing.

The bone blade appeared to be quite ordinary, but it was a replica of the Heavenly Ghost Blade, the most powerful treasure of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and it had been crafted for him using a vast array of precious materials by the seniors of his family. It was such a formidable artifact that even late-Core Formation cultivators would struggle to withstand its power, yet Han Li had caught it with his bare hand.

Everyone else at the scene was also looking on with astonished expressions.

Yu Qi was just as shocked as everyone around her, and she was staring at Han Li with bewilderment and a hint of admiration in her eyes.

Daoist Master White Stone was also staring at Han Li with a slack-jawed expression. He knew that there was a good chance that Han Li would be capable of stopping the bone blade, but he didn't think that Han Li would be able to grab it out of thin air with such ridiculous ease!

With that in mind, he couldn't help but wonder just how powerful Han Li was.

At the same time, he was also counting himself to be quite fortunate.

It was clear to him that if Han Li hadn't held back during their clash, then he would've already been dead by now.

In contrast with everyone else, Liu Le'er's eyes were filled with excitement, and she wasn't surprised in the slightest. In her eyes, her Brother Rock was the epitome of invincibility, so this display of power was only to be expected for her.

"It's been a very long time since I've dealt with such a low-grade treasure," Han Li said as he took an indifferent glance at the bone blade in his hand, then abruptly closed his fingers around it.

The bone blade was instantly crushed in his grasp with a dull thump, scattering onto the ground as specks of gray light.

"No!"

The young man's face instantly paled, and he threw up a mouthful of blood.

That blade was his bonded treasure, and for him, its destruction was akin to having an arm chopped.

"I'm going to make you pay with your life for destroying my treasure!"

A look of vicious resentment appeared in the young man's eyes as he made a hand seal and let loose a thunderous roar. Bursts of black qi rose up all around him, forming an inky-black cloud in the blink of an eye, within which were countless indistinct ghostly shadows.

Immediately thereafter, he slammed his palm into his own chest thrice in rapid succession, releasing three mouthfuls of blood essence. With each mouthful of blood essence that was released, his face would pale slightly further, and by the time all three mouthfuls of blood essence had been expelled, he was already looking as pale as a sheet.

The blood essence that was released instantly swelled to form a vast expanse of dense blood mist that fused into the black cloud.

The black cloud instantly turned as red as blood, and it churned violently as it expanded by severalfold. The indistinct ghostly shadows within it also became several times more substantial as they let loose chilling howls.

The young man then stepped forward and vanished into the blood cloud without a trace.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and in the instant that the blood cloud appeared, the temperature in the entire courtyard plummeted drastically as if the entire area had been plunged into a glacial pit.

Even a cultivator of Daoist Master White Stone's caliber couldn't help but shiver from the cold, and he hurriedly summoned a jade pendant treasure that released a white light barrier to encompass both himself and Liu Le'er, then retreated into the distance.

The black-suited figures in the courtyard and the three elders and surviving members of the Yu Family were all shivering uncontrollably from the freezing cold.

Liu Le'er only felt the biting chill for an instant before the freezing sensation was immediately alleviated by a white light barrier.

She turned to discover that Daoist Master White Stone had arrived by her side, and that the white light barrier had been conjured up by a jade pendant that he had summoned.

At the sight of Liu Le'er's surprised gaze, Daoist Master White Stone immediately flashed her a fawning smile, then retreated to over 100 feet away with her in tow.

A peculiar look appeared on Han Li's face as he cast his gaze toward the blood cloud in the sky, and he suddenly threw a punch in a certain direction.

A faint ghostly shadow was sent flying out of thin air, and it let loose an anguished wail before exploding into a cloud of gray mist.

However, right at this moment, several black chains shot out from beneath Han Li like a nest of vicious spitting vipers, instantly binding his entire body tightly.

Immediately thereafter, a gray-robed man emerged silently nearby with his hands locked in a hand seal. It was none other than the very same gray-robed man who had accompanied the young man back in Farbright City.

The aura that he was giving off was even superior to that of the young man's, and his entire body was encompassed within the black ghostly shadow. It seemed as if the two had fused as one, and his body had also taken on a semi-transparent state, looking as if it could vanish into thin air at any moment.

"You came just in time, Senior Martial Brother Fan! Let's kill this man together!" The young man's chortling voice rang out from within the blood cloud, followed by a burst of chanting.

Gusts of fierce wind were instantly swept up, and the blood cloud surged toward Han Li like a giant wave.

Han Li remained completely expressionless as he stood still on the spot, allowing the blood cloud to devour him in an instant.

The ghostly shadows within the blood cloud all had bloodthirsty looks in their eyes, and they were howling incessantly with their menacing fangs bared, looking as if they wanted to tear Han Li into pieces.

The young man was ecstatic to see this.

These blood souls were all refined using a special secret technique, making them extremely difficult to kill. Anyone who was caught among them would be powerless to escape and worn down until they died.

The gray-robed man was quite surprised that the concealed ghostly entity that he was controlling had been detected by Han Li, but a cruel smile then quickly appeared on his face as he said, "No matter who you are, you're going to pay with your life for opposing our Heavenly Ghost Sect!"

Immediately thereafter, he appeared directly above Han Li in a flash, then thrust his palms downward. Two giant black ghostly claws appeared out of thin air with green light revolving around the tips of the claws, and they were giving off a foul stench, indicating that they were carrying lethal poison.

The two massive claws came swooping down viciously, and Liu Le'er immediately rushed toward Han Li without any regard for her own safety.

Daoist Master White Stone hurriedly pulled her back with an alarmed expression. "Stop! With Senior Han's unfathomable powers, I'm sure he'll have a way to break free!"

Despite what he was saying, he was also feeling rather uneasy. Another powerful enemy had arrived on the scene, this one seemingly even more formidable than the first one, and he didn't know if Han Li would actually be able to hold his own against them.

In the distance, the three elders and surviving members of the Yu Family were all looking on with bated breath, hoping against hope that their unlikely savior would be able to rise to the occasion.

Han Li remained completely unfazed by the situation that he was in, and a string of dull cracks suddenly rang out from within his body. At the same time, he suddenly swelled drastically in size while a layer of golden scales surfaced over his skin.

With a casual shrug of his shoulders, the black chains around him instantly snapped into pieces. He then lashed out with his fists, unleashing a dense wall of golden fist projections that erupted in all directions like a ferocious storm.

As soon as the black ghostly claws came into contact with the golden fist projections, they instantly shattered and disintegrated into nothingness. The gray-robed man was also struck by countless fist projections amid an alarmed cry that was quickly cut short.

The black ghostly shadow around him was immediately destroyed, and he was sent flying like a ragdoll before slamming heavily down onto the ground. By the time he came to a rest, his entire body was nothing more than a gruesome mass of mangled flesh and blood. His body and soul had been instantly destroyed, and he was well and truly dead.

At the same time, the entire blood cloud and all of the ghostly shadows within it were also completely erased by the golden fist projections, forcibly revealing the young man.

At this moment, he was completely rooted to the spot, but in the instant that he met Han Li's icy cold gaze, he immediately shuddered before making a hand seal, upon which a vast black cloud surged out of his body, and he sped away into the distance as quickly as he could.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he took a deep breath before exhaling sharply.

A burst of white light shot out of his mouth, piercing into the black cloud in a flash.

A blood-curdling cry rang out, and the black cloud abruptly disintegrated, following which the young man fell out of the sky, having had a hole punched through his head.

Complete silence descended upon the entire courtyard.

"He's a sword cultivator!" someone exclaimed in a feeble voice.

Chapter 18: Request

No more than three seconds had passed from the moment that the gray-robed man appeared to the instant that Han Li slew both of his assailants.

Two seemingly invincible Core Formation cultivators had fallen in what seemed like the blink of an eye, and everyone in the courtyard, including the black-suited figures and everyone from the Yu Family, was completely flabbergasted.

What was particularly astonishing to them was the burst of white light that Han Li had blasted out of his mouth. It was far too fast to be traced with the naked eye, and it had slain the young man in an instant, even though he had already fled far from the scene.

In addition to that, the assertion that Han Li was a "sword cultivator" had all of the black-suited figures completely petrified, and they didn't dare to stay any longer as they summoned their magic tools and frantically attempted to flee the scene.

In the Spirit Domain Realm, sword cultivators were able to easily crush other cultivators of the same caliber. In addition to that, flying swords were extremely fast and could kill in an instant, so if they didn't get away now, it would be too late.

Spiritual light of all different colors appeared in the courtyard in rapid succession as around a dozen flying treasures rose up into the air at once before fleeing in different directions.

Han Li didn't even bother to take a glance at those people. Instead, he cast his gaze toward the young man's body, and he raised an eyebrow as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

All of the surviving members of the Yu Family exchanged a series of bewildered glances, and no one dared to say anything. As for the three elders, they didn't even dare to breathe too loudly for fear of attracting Han Li's attention.

Meanwhile, Daoist Master White Stone stole a glance at Han Li, and after a brief hesitation, he suddenly swept his right hand toward one of the fleeing black-suited cultivators.

His sleeve bulged slightly, following which a long golden rope shot out like a viper springing out of its cave, then ensnared something in mid-air before rapidly flying back.

A thin black-suited cultivator was dragged back out of mid-air by the golden rope, and he was completely bound as he slammed onto the ground in front of Han Li.

The black-suited cultivator paid no heed to the pain from falling from such a height as he immediately implored, "S... Spare me..."

Han Li ignored the black-suited cultivator before him as he turned to Daoist Master White Stone before asking, "Do you know of this Heavenly Ghost Sect?"

Daoist Master White Stone took a glance at Yu Qi, then carefully answered, "The Heavenly Ghost Sect and the Cold Flame Sect are both considered to be among the most powerful sects in the Spirit Domain Realm."

Han Li nodded in response, then turned to the black-suited man. "How many people did the Heavenly Ghost Sect send to Farbright City?"

The black-suited cultivator struggled into a sitting position as he hurriedly replied, "According to my knowledge, it's only the people that were sent to the Yu Manor today."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he felt a bone-chilling sensation run through his entire body, as if he had been plunged into a glacial pit.

The tall and imposing young man before him was suddenly looking at him with an incredibly cold gaze. His inky-black pupils seemed to have suddenly become infinitely massive, transforming into a pair of bottomless black vortexes, and if he dared to even consider the idea of telling a lie, he would immediately be sucked in.

This feeling only lasted for an instant before fading, but it still made all of the fine hairs all over his entire body stand up on end, and his back was completely drenched in cold sweat.

The black-suited cultivator wanted to kneel down and kowtow to Han Li, but he was unable to do so as he was bound by the golden rope, so he could only lower his head as a gesture of submission. "You have to believe me, Senior! I'm telling the truth!

“We are only outer court disciples of the sect who were ordered to come on this mission to the prime minister's manor. As for whether there are other disciples of our sect in the city, that is something I truly do not know!"

"Whose orders are you following? His orders?" Han Li asked as he pointed at the body of the young man not far away.

"Yes. His name was Qi Minghao, and he was an inner court disciple of our sect. He possessed exceptional cultivation aptitude, so he was held in very high regard in our sect. On top of that, one of his granduncles is an elder of our sect, and that further strengthened his standings, so we didn't dare to refuse his orders.

“If we had known that the Yu Manor was under your protection, we would've never dared to set foot here!" the black-suited cultivator said in a pitiable voice.

At this point, Yu Qi had already made her way over to the black-suited figure, and there were tears swimming in her eyes as she asked, "Was Yu Minghao telling the truth? Are my father and brothers..."

"Outer court disciples like myself had no right to participate in what happened in the capital city, but according to what I've heard, the situation is much the same as what Yu Minghao described," the black-suited cultivator replied in a fearful manner.

Yu Qi closed her eyes upon hearing this, and tears quickly flowed down her cheeks.

Another burst of sobbing rang out from the women and children among the Yu Family's survivors.

A moment later, Yu Qi reopened her eyes before asking with a pained expression, "If your Heavenly Ghost Sect has already taken over the Prosperous Nation, then just seize control over the existing imperial family. Why do you insist on wiping out our Yu Family?"

"This is an established practice in our sect. In order to gain complete control over the Prosperous Nation, the imperial family tied to the Cold Flame Sect and all of the families of the officials that served the past imperial family are to be killed, and the Yu Family falls under this category."

All of a sudden, a thought seemed to have occurred to the black-suited cultivator, and his voice began to tremble with fear as he continued, "Please forgive me for going off on a tangent, but Elder Qi of our sect is renowned for being protective of his juniors, so he's definitely going to come after all those involved in the death of his grandnephew. Even the outer court disciples like myself who accompanied him on this mission are sure to be killed."

All of the survivors of the Yu Family were horrified to hear this, and the expressions of the three elders also became extremely grim.

At this point, the graceful and regal facade of the Yu Family's second young master had been completely torn away, and his face was smeared with tears, dirt, and blood as he implored in a sobbing voice, "We can't afford to waste any more time here, Sister. We have to leave this place right away! You have a master at the Cold Flame Sect, don't you? Let's go to her, I'm sure she'll take us in."

Yu Qi paid no heed to him as she raised a hand before wiping her tears dry with her sleeve. She then made her way over to Han Li, Liu Le'er, and Daoist Master White Stone before extending a respectful bow. "Thank you for saving our lives."

Han Li offered no response and accepted her gesture of gratitude.

Daoist Master White Stone also remained silent, merely nodding in response.

"Sister Qi..." Liu Le'er's family had also perished under terrible circumstances, so she could empathize with Yu Qi. She wanted to say something to console her, but she didn't know what to say, so her voice trailed off into silence.

Yu Qi gave her a slight nod and forced a faint smile onto her own face.

After that, the grief and dejection in her eyes gradually faded, and a resilient and unyielding look appeared on her face. Even though she was still in her female attire, it was as if she had turned from the young mistress of the Yu Family to the young master that she occasionally posed as.

She picked up the dagger that had been knocked out of her hand earlier by Han Li, then plunged it viciously toward the black-suited cultivator's chest in a flash.

"No! Spare me..."

A blood-curdling howl rang out as the dagger was buried all the way up to its hilt.

The black-suited cultivator collapsed into a puddle of his own blood and spasmed a few times before falling still.

The survivors of the Yu Family couldn't help but exchange a few uneasy glances upon seeing this.

At this point, only around a dozen members of the Yu Family still remained, and Yu Qi turned to them with a determined expression as she declared, "The Yu Manor has fallen. Even with the Cold Flame Sect as our backer, we won't be able to recover from this anytime soon. All members of our Yu Family are to come with me to the Cold Flame Sect. As for everyone else, if you no longer wish to follow me, you can take some money from the storeroom and leave."

The surviving members of the Yu Family were horrified and at a complete loss for what to do, but with Yu Qi taking control of the situation, they gradually calmed down, and the sobbing coming from the women and children slowly subsided.

Han Li was quite impressed by this, and he turned to Yu Qi with a hint of approval in his eyes.

Yu Qi then cast her gaze toward the three elders and continued, "Elders, you have risked your lives to protect us, and words cannot express my gratitude. If you wish to leave, you can each choose a few of the treasures in our manor to take with you. However, if you're willing to continue protecting us on our journey to the Cold Flame Sect, then I'll be sure to offer your further compensation in the future."

The three elders exchanged a few hesitant glances upon hearing this, and all of them seemed to be waiting for Han Li and Daoist Master White Stone to make their decisions first.

Yu Qi took a glance at Han Li, and she immediately understood what the three elders were thinking. With that in mind, she immediately strode over to Han Li before extending a curtsey.

"Brother Liu, I know next to nothing about you, but it's clear to me that your powers are beyond what I can fathom. Normal treasures will most likely completely fail to appeal to you, so the only thing that I can offer you is a Wyrm Essence Bead that has been passed down in our family for generations.

“I'm willing to offer the treasure to you as compensation if you accompany us to the Cold Flame Sect," Yu Qi said as she looked straight into Han Li's eyes with an earnest expression.

A hint of greed appeared in Daoist Master White Stone's eyes upon hearing mention of a Wyrm Essence Bead, but he then took a glance at Han Li out of the corners of his eyes, and any sneaky thoughts in his mind immediately disappeared.

"Have you gone insane, Sister? How could you offer him our Wyrm Essence Bead?" the second young master of the Yu Family exclaimed in an alarmed voice.

Yu Qi didn't even bother to take a glance at her brother as she continued to look directly at Han Li. "The Yu Manor is already gone, what is a mere Wyrm Essence bead in comparison? If you're willing to accept my offer, I can bring you the treasure from our secret vault right away. What do you say, Brother Liu?"

Chapter 19: Grandnephew of A Deity Transformation Cultivator

"Wyrm Essence Beads are capable of helping Core Formation cultivators break through cultivation bottlenecks, so this is indeed quite a remarkable treasure, but I have no need for such a thing, so I'm afraid I must refuse," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

Yu Qi's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, but she still wasn't willing to give up. "If you have any other demands, feel free to state them. As long as it's not something completely out of my reach, I'll do everything in my power to fulfill your request."

"I do owe you a favor for helping me awaken from my prior state, but I just prevented your suicide and killed those two Core Formation cultivators of the Heavenly Ghost Sect for you, so surely I've already done enough to return the favor.

“Under normal circumstances, perhaps I would be willing to accompany you, but I've only just awakened and have my own problems to take care of, so I'm afraid I won't have the time to spare to accompany you on a journey to the Cold Flame Sect," Han Li replied.

Yu Qi was distraught to hear this, but she was still holding onto one final shred of hope as she turned to Liu Le'er with an imploring gaze.

Liu Le'er couldn't bear to see her look so dejected, and she tugged on Han Li's sleeve with a hesitant expression.

Han Li was naturally aware of what she was thinking, and he gently patted her head, then cast his gaze toward a certain direction outside the courtyard as he said in a calm voice, "Rest assured, even if you don't have me in accompaniment, there will be others to protect you on your journey to the Cold Flame Sect."

Yu Qi faltered slightly upon hearing this, clearly failing to understand what Han Li was alluding to.

Right at this moment, several figures appeared in the distance.

Yu Qi and the other survivors of the Yu Family were all quite alarmed by this, and they immediately turned toward that direction. Daoist Master White Stone and the three elders had also summoned their magic tools again.

Shortly thereafter, several objects flew through the air, having been tossed into the courtyard from outside before landing on the ground. The objects rolled around briefly before coming to a rest, revealing themselves to be a cluster of human heads.

The heads belonged to the black-suited figures who had fled the scene earlier, and their faces were all twisted with shock and horror.

Everyone was given quite a fright by this, and Liu Le'er reflexively tightened her grip on Han Li's sleeve.

However, Han Li's expression remained as calm as ever as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction.

There, a white figure abruptly emerged amid a flash of white light, then drifted down into the courtyard with her clothes flapping around her.

It was a tall woman dressed in white who appeared to be in her thirties, and it was clear to see that she would've been a stunning beauty a decade ago. She was holding a black longsword, and was giving off a sharp and dangerous aura that was rarely seen in women.

"Master!" Yu Qi called out in an elated voice before rushing over to the woman.

"I'm so glad that you're safe, Menghan." The woman latched onto Yu Qi's hand as she gently stroked her hair, and her expression eased slightly as a doting look appeared in her eyes.

Yu Qi's reaction to the woman's arrival made it clear that she was not an enemy, and all of the surviving members of the Yu Family heaved a collective sigh of relief.

At the same time, Daoist Master White Stone and the three elders spotted a small flame pattern embroidered onto the woman's sleeves, a pattern that was identical to the one emblazoned on the badge that Yu Qi had brought out earlier, and respectful looks immediately appeared on their faces.

Liu Le'er seemed to be rather fearful of the woman, and she ducked behind Han Li as she clutched tightly onto his sleeve.

Han Li knew what she was concerned about, and he consoled in a gentle voice, "Don't worry, I'm here."

Liu Le'er was very much reassured by this, and she nodded in response.

"Why are you here, Master?" Yu Menghan asked as she fought back the tears in her eyes.

"I received news that the Heavenly Ghost Sect was going to attack the Yu Manor, so I immediately traveled here from the sect, but I was intercepted by the Heavenly Ghost Sect on the way, so I was delayed. Thank heavens I'm not too late," the woman said in a doting manner.

Yu Menghan led her master over to Han Li and the others before introducing everyone, putting special emphasis on her introduction of Han Li. "It's all thanks to our elders and Brother Liu here that we were able to survive. Everyone, this is my master. Master, these four are the elders of our Yu Manor, and this is Liu Shi. He took down two of the Heavenly Ghost Sect's Core Formation cultivators and played a pivotal role in saving us all."

Daoist Master White Stone and the elders hurriedly extended respectful salutes toward the woman.

Han Li didn't bother with such formalities, and he smiled as he turned to Yu Menghan. "I haven't had a chance to tell you this yet, but my name is actually Han Li. Liu Shi is just a moniker that I adopted."

Yu Menghan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied with a smile, "I see."

"I am Gu Yunyue of the Cold Flame Sect. Thank you for saving my disciple's life, Fellow Daoist Han. May I ask which sect you belong to?" the woman asked with an indifferent expression as she directed a sharp gaze toward Han Li and the others.

In the face of her probing gaze, Daoist Master White Stone and the others felt as if their skin were being pricked by sharp needles, and that only heightened the awe and veneration they felt toward the woman.

Gu Yunyue's gaze only roamed over the likes of Daoist Master White Stone and Liu Le'er for a brief moment before settling on Han Li, and the indifferent look on her face was instantly replaced with a hint of wariness.

Han Li's aura was extremely indistinct, and she was unable to see through him even with her spiritual sense, something that she found to be rather concerning.

"I don't belong to any sect, I'm just a vagrant cultivator. I only stepped in because I was indebted to Young Mistress Yu, and I was only repaying my debt," Han Li replied with a calm expression.

With his powerful spiritual sense, he was naturally able to see through the woman in an instant, and he discovered that she was a mid-Nascent Soul cultivator.

"I see..." Gu Yunyue was rather surprised to hear this.

The fact that he was able to kill two Core Formation cultivators clearly indicated that he was quite a powerful cultivator himself, but there were very few cultivators at or above the Nascent Soul Stage among vagrant cultivators.

Gu Yunyue could see that Han Li was unwilling to divulge any further information, so she gave him a nod, then turned back to Yu Menghan. "The Prosperous Nation belongs to the Heavenly Ghost Sect now, so we can't linger here. We have to leave right away."

The survivors of the Yu Family were eager to get away from here, and they were all ecstatic to hear this.

"Hold on a moment, Master, I have something to show you," Yu Menghan suddenly said, then led Gu Yunyue over to the body of Qi Minghao.

"That's Qi Minghao! Why is he here?" Gu Yunyue asked with a surprised expression.

Yu Menghan's heart jolted slightly at the sight of Gu Yunyue's reaction, and she asked, "So you recognize him as well, Master. Is his granduncle really an elder of the Heavenly Ghost Sect?"

"That's right. His granduncle, Qi Xuan, is an elder of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and he's already at the Deity Transformation Stage. On top of that, he's extremely protective of his juniors, and if he finds out that his grandnephew has been killed, he definitely won't let things slide," Gu Yunyue said.

Yu Menghan's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and Daoist Master White Stone and the others were also horrified.

Deity Transformation cultivators transcended above even Nascent Soul cultivators, and a cultivator of that caliber could easily erase them out of existence without even raising a finger.

"Who killed Qi Minghao?" Gu Yunyue asked, and her gaze was already wandering toward Han Li.

Meanwhile, Han Li casually made his way over to the body of the gray-robed man before picking up a storage bag and examining its contents as if he didn't have a care in the world.

"It was indeed Brother Han who killed this man," Yu Menghan confirmed.

A grim look appeared on Gu Yunyue's face upon hearing this.

"Master, will Qi Xuan try to personally avenge his grandnephew?" Yu Menghan asked in an uneasy manner.

Gu Yunyue considered the question momentarily, then shook her head in response. "Qi Xuan holds a very lofty position in the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and he has many descendants, so he most likely won't leave the sect just over the death of a grandnephew. At the very most, he'll only send some disciples of the Heavenly Ghost Sect to investigate this matter."

Yu Menghan's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"Even so, we can't afford to get complacent. Menghan, you and I need to set off right away and ensure that we return to the Cold Flame Sect before the people sent by Qi Xuan arrive," Gu Yunyue continued in a grim voice.

Yu Menghan's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. Judging from what Gu Yunyue had just said, it sounded like she was only planning to take Yu Menghan with her and no one else.

"Master, can my family also come to the Cold Flame Sect with me?"

All of the survivors of the Yu Family turned to Gu Yunyue upon hearing this, and Daoist Master White Stone and the other elders also turned to her with hopeful expressions.

If they could take advantage of this opportunity to join the Cold Flame Sect, even if they could only be outer court disciples, it would still be far better than being vagrant cultivators, particularly given that they had already made an enemy out of the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

Chapter 20: Invitation

"No. Our Cold Flame Sect can't just take in a bunch of mortals. Your family can escape to the Creek Nation under the protection of the elders for refuge for now," Gu Yunyue said with a shake of her head.

The Creek Nation was situated to the northeast of the Prosperous Nation, and at the moment, it still belonged to the Cold Flame Sect.

The elders of the Yu Manor were quite disappointed to hear this, but they didn't dare to contest Gu Yunyue's decision.

The survivors of the Yu Family were very much alarmed by this turn of events, and they all turned to Yu Menghan with imploring looks in their eyes.

"We'll all be screwed if the Heavenly Ghost Sect hunts us down! You can't just abandon us now that you've managed to join an immortal sect..." the second young master of the Yu Family yelled in a panicked voice.

"Shut up!" Yu Menghan scolded with a stern expression.

The second young master shuddered, and he didn't dare to say anything further.

Even though Yu Menghan was putting on a stern display, she was also quite concerned about the safety of her family, and she turned to Gu Yunyue before asking, "Master, will it really be alright to send them to the Creek Nation? Surely it won't be very difficult for the Heavenly Ghost Sect to track them down."

"Rest assured, Menghan. According to the rules of the Spirit Domain Realm, as long as you can officially become an inner court disciple of the Cold Flame Sect, the Heavenly Ghost Sect will be prohibited from attacking your family. Otherwise, they'll be committing what's considered to be a cardinal sin in this realm.

“If they dare to hunt down your family, then once you become an established cultivator, you'll also have an excuse to attack the families of the Heavenly Ghost Sect's disciples. They attacked the Yu Manor because they didn't know that you had an acceptance badge from our sect.

“Now that I've made an official appearance, things are completely different. The most important thing now is to get you to the Cold Flame Sect safe and sound," Gu Yunyue said with a serious expression.

Yu Menghan was quite relieved to hear this, and everyone else from the Yu Family was also put at ease.

"Elders, I'll be counting on you to look after my family. Once I become an established cultivator in the future, I'll be sure to reward you handsomely," Yu Menghan said as she extended a curtsey toward Daoist Master White Stone and the other three elders.

"You're far too kind, Young Mistress. As elders of the Yu Manor, we've always been treated very well by Prime Minister Yu and yourself. Now that Yu Manor has gone through such a tragic catastrophe, it is our duty to protect your family," the elders hurriedly replied, vowing to protect the survivors of the Yu Family.

Even though they couldn't join the Cold Flame Sect, it would benefit them immensely to establish close ties with Yu Menghan, who was on track to become an inner court disciple of the Cold Flame Sect.

However, a reluctant look appeared on Daoist Master White Stone's face, and he stole a glance at Han Li.

Han Li was in the process of examining the storage bag in his hands, and he turned to Daoist Master White Stone with a hint of a smile on his face as he said, "Fellow Daoist White Stone, given how long you've been serving the Yu Manor, it should only be right that you accompany them on this trip as well."

Only then did Daoist Master White Stone force a smile onto his face and accept this arrangement.

Yu Menghan pretended not to have seen this exchange, and she extended another curtsey toward the elders. "You have my utmost gratitude."

Thus, with everything decided, the survivors of the Yu Family immediately began to prepare for the upcoming journey, gathering all of the treasures and valuable items in the manor.

Meanwhile, Han Li casually pocketed the storage bag in his hands, then made his way over to Qi Minghao's body before taking his storage bag as well.

As for the belongings of the black-suited cultivators, he couldn't even be bothered to pick them up.

Daoist Master White Stone and the others were ecstatic to see this, and they hurriedly gathered the scattered belongings of the black-suited cultivators.

"What are your plans for the future, Fellow Daoist Han?" Gu Yunyue asked as she approached him.

"It's a complete accident that I even came to Farbright City in the first place. Now that I've made an enemy out of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, I'll naturally have to get far away from here," Han Li replied in an indifferent voice.

"Not only have you gotten yourself involved in all of this, you've slain Qi Minghao as well, so I'm afraid it may not be a simple matter for you to get away. Given the power and reach of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, I'm sure they'll find out about you very soon," Gu Yunyue said.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he asked, "What are you trying to say, Celestial Maiden Gu?"

"If you're not opposed to the idea, how about you join our Cold Flame Sect? Our sect has always welcomed powerful vagrant cultivators. Given how you were able to slay those Core Formation cultivators so easily, you must possess Nascent Soul Stage power yourself, so it's not out of the question for you to become a guest elder of our sect. I would be honored to refer you to our sect's leaders," Gu Yunyue said.

Yu Menghan's eyes lit up at the proposal, and she chimed in, "Master's right. If you can join our Cold Flame Sect, I'm sure Sister Le'er will also benefit immensely."

Han Li turned to Liu Le'er, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Liu Le'er looked back at him with a pair of wide and innocent eyes, seemingly unsure of exactly what was happening.

"If I'm not mistaken, your aura seems to be rather unstable, which indicates that you're carrying some sort of injury, Fellow Daoist Han. I just so happen to have a Sharp Watch Pill with me, a vastly renowned healing medicine in the Spirit Domain Realm," Gu Yunyue continued in a meaningful voice.

Given that two of the Heavenly Ghost Sect's Core Formation cultivators had been slain here, one of which was the descendant of a Deity Transformation cultivator, there was a very good chance that they would be intercepted by powerful foes from the Heavenly Ghost Sect on the way back to the Cold Flame Sect.

Han Li was a complete mystery to her, but she was certain that he would be a strong ally if he were willing to accompany them.

Han Li stroked his chin in contemplation for a moment, then suddenly turned to Liu Le'er. "What do you say, Le'er? Are you willing to come to the Cold Flame Sect with me?"

Given Gu Yunyue's cultivation base, Liu Le'er's identity as a demonic fox was naturally no secret to her.

However, by searching Daoist Master White Stone's soul earlier, Han Li had learned that even though there was some severe segregation that existed between humans and demons in the Spirit Domain Realm, it was quite common to see some powerful cultivators in large sects with demons by their side, so there shouldn't be any issues taking Liu Le'er to the Cold Flame Sect.

Liu Le'er took a glance at Gu Yunyue, then looked at Yu Menghan before replying in a timid voice, "I'll do whatever you say."

"Don't worry, no one will dare to pick on you as long as I'm around," Han Li reassured with a smile as he gently patted her head.

"I know you'll protect me," Liu Le'er replied as a wide smile appeared on her face.

"Then I'll have to trouble you to refer me to your sect, Celestial Maiden Gu. Would you be able to give me the Sharp Watch Pill now?" Han Li asked as he turned to Gu Yunyue.

"Of course!" Gu Yunyue was elated, and she flipped a hand over to produce a white jade vial without any hesitation before handing it over to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the jade vial, then removed the lid before taking a slight whiff and giving a nod.

A faint smile appeared on Gu Yunyue's face upon seeing this.

At this point, the survivors of the Yu Family were already done packing, and aside from all of the manor's valuable items, they had also brought out several horse-drawn carriages.

Daoist Master White Stone and the others also made their way over to Han Li.

"Senior Han, I..." Daoist Master White Stone seemed to want to say something, but was rather hesitant about how to proceed.

"Just focus on protecting the Yu Family, and don't worry about anything else. Also, I have something that I need you to do for me..." Han Li's voice trailed off here, but his lips were still moving, and he communicated something to Daoist Master White Stone through voice transmission.

Daoist Master White Stone faltered slightly upon hearing what Han Li had to say, then nodded in response.

Meanwhile, Yu Menghan made her way over to Gu Yunyue's side, then said, "Master, the city gates have all been locked, so I'll have to trouble you to take them out of the city."

Gu Yunyue nodded in response, then swept a sleeve through the air to conjure up a large cloud of white mist that carried everyone into the sky.

The survivors of the Yu Family had never experienced something so ethereal, and they hurriedly grabbed onto the carriages beside them, while some of them cried out in surprise and alarm.

The white cloud flew out of the city in the blink of an eye, then landed gently on the official road outside the city.

"Mother, Auntie..." Even though Yu Menghan was already prepared for this separation, she was still overcome by emotions and embraced her family tightly.

Her mother and her other close relatives also had tears in their eyes as they told Yu Menghan to look after herself.

Only after a long while did they reluctantly part with one another.

Under the protection of the four elders, the survivors of the Yu Family headed east, and they quickly disappeared into the night.

Yu Menghan looked on with a blank expression as her family faded into the distance, and only after a long while did she withdraw her gaze.

After giving Yu Menghan a moment to collect herself, Gu Yunyue swept a hand through the air to summon a white spirit ark. "We need to set off as well."

The spirit ark was around 40 to 50 feet in length, and it had a rather interesting design, with a body that resembled a crescent moon. Its surface was riddled with azure spirit patterns that were giving off faint spiritual power fluctuations, and it was clearly no ordinary ark.

Han Li held onto Liu Le'er's hand as he stepped onto the spirit ark, and Yu Menghan took a deep breath before also following suit.

Gu Yunyue released an incantation seal onto the spirit ark, and it immediately began to glow with white spiritual light before rising up into the air and flying away into the distance as a streak of white light.

Chapter 21: Nascent Soul Transformation

Inside the spirit ark, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed with his back leaning against a wall, while Liu Le'er was seated obediently beside him, inspecting her surroundings with an intrigued expression while also occasionally taking glances at the rapidly receding scenery outside.

Gu Yunyue was standing outside, controlling the spirit ark while also speaking with Yu Menghan in a low voice.

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li gently exhaled as he slowly opened his eyes, and his expression was rather grim.

Following his awakening, he discovered that he was no longer able to absorb the world's origin qi into his body, so it was impossible for him to recover his magic power through cultivation. He had only recently awakened, and he was stunned by the revelation of his memory loss, so he didn't get a chance to examine this matter.

He had just attempted to absorb the world's origin qi, and he discovered that it was still to no avail.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a white jade vial, and as soon as it was opened, he was immediately greeted by an extremely rich medicinal scent that struck him with a sense of reinvigoration.

He tipped out an azure pill from the vial, holding it up to his eye between two of his fingers for closer examination.

"So this is a Sharp Watch Pill. I hope it'll actually do something," Han Li murmured to himself, then swallowed the pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

Liu Le'er knew that Han Li wasn't to be interrupted during this process. She could see that Yu Menghan had already finished her conversation with Gu Yunyue and was making her way toward her, so she stood up and made her way over to another corner of the ark before taking a seat to speak with Yu Menghan.

Moments later, the pill gradually began to take effect, and Han Li's eyebrows suddenly twitched slightly as a gentle surge of warmth slowly emerged from his dantian, then made its way throughout his body along his meridians.

After circulating the energy throughout his body once, he immediately felt far more comfortable, and the sense of emptiness in his body was also beginning to fade. At the same time, a slight hint of magic power was generated in his dantian, and even though it was only a tiny amount, it was still a very encouraging turn of events.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes as he examined what was taking place inside his body, then flipped a hand over to produce around a dozen more pills.

Aside from the ones that he had taken from Daoist Master White Stone, there were also some pills that had been left behind by Qi Minghao and the gray-robed man. Almost all of them had the effect of treating injuries and recovering magic power, but there was a great variance in the quality of the pills, most of them were far inferior to that Sharp Watch Pill.

Han Li picked up one of the pills before swallowing it, then slowly closed his eyes again.

However, moments later, his eyes suddenly sprang open, and a perplexed look appeared on his face. He then picked up another pill before swallowing it as well.

Once again, he reopened his eyes only a brief moment later with a rather uncertain gaze.

The two pills that he had just taken had failed to produce any effect. He was unable to sense any changes taking place in his body, nor was he able to generate any more magic power.

A grim look appeared on his face as he swallowed the pills in his hand one after another.

Soon, all that was left was a thumb-sized pill of a dark golden color.

This was a pill of quite a high caliber, comparable to the Sharp Watch Pill, and it was presumably the pill that Qi Minghao had been reserving for life-threatening situations.

Han Li took an expressionless glance at the pill, then tossed it into his own mouth.

This time, he wasn't disappointed. The golden pill quickly took effect after being devoured, transforming into a wisp of spiritual power that flowed into his dantian, increasing his magic power slightly once again.

Only then did Han Li's expression ease slightly.

As long as his body was still receptive to pills, it wouldn't be a difficult task for him to recover his magic power. As for why the other pills hadn't yielded any effect, that was most likely because they were of too low a caliber to make any difference in his body.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out in his head.

"Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Han. It looks like there's hope yet for you to recover your magic power."

"It hardly matters if I can't produce any magic power of my own," Han Li replied with his spiritual sense.

"It's still better than nothing. With each shred of magic power that you recover, you and I will be closer to returning to the Immortal Realm," Mo Guang said.

"That's true, but I'm afraid it's most likely not going to be so easy," Han Li replied.

"If pills work, then what about spirit stones?" Mo Guang asked.

"I was just about to try that," Han Li replied with a smile.

He flipped a hand over to produce several azure spirit stones of different sizes, and as he closed his hands around them, they immediately began to give off azure light.

Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan couldn't help but have their attention drawn to the azure light that had suddenly appeared in Han Li's direction, while Gu Yunyue displayed no reaction as she stood at the front of the ark.

Azure spiritual power began to slowly flow from the spirit stones, but after circling over Han Li's palms for some time, the spiritual power suddenly became murky and indistinct.

Moments later, the azure light gradually dissipated, vanishing into thin air.

Han Li released the spirit stones, which had become completely dull and devoid of luster, and he fell into deep thought with a perplexed look on his face.

"What's going on? It appears you're unable to absorb power from spirit stones, either." Mo Guang's voice rang out in his mind again.

Han Li was silent for a moment before replying, "Perhaps just like those pills, these spirit stones are of too low a quality and don't contain sufficiently pure spiritual power to be converted into magic power in my body."

Mo Guang was silent for a moment, then said, "In that case, you should be able to return to your former peak as long as you have sufficient high-grade pills and top-grade spirit stones."

Han Li heaved a long sigh, then replied in a rather frustrated manner, "It's not that simple. It's still yet to be seen whether top-grade spirit stones will even be effective for me. Thankfully, my body and spiritual sense foundation are decently stable, so even if I'm unable to absorb the world's origin qi, I'll still be able to recover slowly on my own."

"You're far too modest, Fellow Daoist Han. If the foundation of your body and spiritual sense can only be considered to be decently stable, then no one would be able to claim to have a strong foundation. Seeing as we've already identified a way forward, I can only wish you luck in your recovery," Mo Guang said before falling silent.

Han Li heaved another faint sigh. None of the storage bags that he had picked up contained any top-grade spirit stones. Otherwise, he would've tested them out right away.

He carefully examined the magic power in his body to find that it was only equivalent to what would be found in a mid-Nascent Soul cultivator. If he wanted to continue to make improvements in this area, he would either need to regain the ability to absorb the world's origin qi or take high-grade pills for magic power recovery.

With that in mind, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he directed his spiritual sense deep into his own dantian to examine his internal condition.

His entire dantian seemed to be enshrouded within a boundless cloud of mist, and there was a layer of faint golden light at the heart of the mist, resembling a yellow lantern in the night.

Han Li projected his spiritual sense into the mist, upon which he saw a miniature golden figure that was glowing brightly. The figure was seated in the mist, and it was completely identical to Han Li in appearance. It was none other than his nascent soul.

The nascent soul wore a calm expression, and its eyes closed while its arms were hanging by its sides, seemingly in a state of slumber.

His inability to absorb the world's origin qi had to have something to do with the state of his nascent soul. Back when he first awakened, he had used his spiritual sense to examine his nascent soul, only to find that his spiritual sense was unable to enter his nascent soul, nor was he able to rouse it from its slumber.

If it weren't for the fact that there was still a faint spiritual connection between himself and the nascent soul, he would almost be led to believe that it didn't even belong to him.

A catalog of secret techniques flashed through Han Li's mind, and in the end, he made a hand seal, upon which the magic power that had just been generated in his dantian converged before forming a faint silver rune, which slowly drifted toward the nascent soul's body.

A string of dull thumps rang out, and as soon as the silver rune made contact with the nascent soul's skin, it immediately disintegrated into bursts of silver light.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but he wasn't too surprised. He immediately switched to a different secret technique, summoning a series of white threads of light that slowly converged toward the nascent soul from all directions.

Several hours later, Han Li's eyes sprang wide open, and he had to take a sharp breath to swallow back the blood that was threatening to gush out of his throat.

Just now, he had used his Spirit Refinement Technique [1] to try and forcibly inject his spiritual sense into his nascent soul, but a burst of terrifying power had suddenly emerged from the nascent soul, repelling his spiritual sense and magic power, thereby resulting in secret technique backlash.

Thankfully, his physical body and spiritual sense were sufficiently powerful for him to survive the ordeal. If an ordinary cultivator had been in his place, there was a very good chance that they would've been reduced to a true imbecile by the spiritual sense backlash.

After that series of experimentation, Han Li had used up some of the magic power that he had regained, almost dropping back down to the early-Nascent Soul Stage, and that was rather disheartening for him.

[1]. Refer to RMJI for information on the Spirit Refinement Technique.

[Back]

Chapter 22: Windcloud Duo

While Han Li was pondering possible solutions to his problems, Gu Yunyue was able to sense Han Li's magic power fluctuations, which he was unable to conceal due to the secret technique backlash that he had suffered earlier, and her heart jolted slightly at the discovery.

"So he's at the mid-Nascent Soul Stage!" she murmured to herself, and after a brief hesitation, she turned and approached Han Li.

Han Li temporarily set aside his train of thought upon seeing this and rose to his feet.

"It seems like the Sharp Watch Pill was effective for you. With that, I presume you've at least mostly recovered from your injuries," Gu Yunyue said with a warm expression.

"Indeed. You have my gratitude, Fellow Daoist," Han Li replied.

"You're more than welcome, Fellow Daoist Han. Once you join our sect, you'll receive additional spirit pills as well," Gu Yunyue said.

She seemed to be quite eager to win over Han Li, as evidenced by the fact that she was initiating a constant stream of conversation in an attempt to get on friendlier terms with Han Li.

Through their conversation, Han Li was able to learn quite a bit about the Spirit Domain Realm.

His understanding of this realm was still only limited to the knowledge of Daoist Master White Stone, who was only a Core Formation cultivator, so he was naturally receiving different information and insights from a Nascent Soul cultivator like Gu Yunyue.

All of the questions that Gu Yunyue raised about Han Li's past were met with rather ambiguous responses, and Gu Yunyue quickly refrained from asking such questions as it was clear to her that Han Li didn't wish to share too much about himself.

"By the way, would you be willing to tell me about the Cold Flame Sect, Fellow Daoist Gu? My current knowledge of the sect is only limited to some rumors that I've heard," Han Li suddenly said.

Gu Yunyue was rather taken aback by this question, but she immediately replied, "Even if you hadn't asked me, I would've gotten to this topic sooner or later. Our Cold Flame Sect is a renowned sect of the Spirit Domain Realm. Up to this point, its history has spanned in excess of 1,000,000 years, and there are hundreds of thousands of disciples in our sect.

“Setting aside all of the Core Formation and Nascent Soul Stage disciples, we have dozens of Deity Transformation and Spatial Tempering Stage elders, three Body Integration Stage powerful beings, and a Grand Ascension Stage patriarch."

A proud look appeared on Gu Yunyue's face as she spoke about her sect, and Han Li's heart stirred slightly after hearing her description.

The Cold Flame Sect was indeed a very powerful sect. With a Grand Ascension Stage patriarch, the sect was comparable in power to a major race in the Spirit Realm.

"Furthermore, the founder of our sect, Patriarch Cold Flame, ascended to the Immortal Realm over 1,000,000 years ago, and even to this day, our sect is still able to communicate with our immortal founder through special means.

“He would occasionally bestow upon us some spirit pills and cultivation arts from the Immortal Realm, thereby giving us an even greater advantage over other sects. You're definitely making a wise decision by joining our sect, Fellow Daoist Han," Gu Yunyue said with a smile.

Han Li's expression finally changed slightly upon hearing this.

It came as quite a surprise to him that the Cold Flame Sect had a backer in the Immortal Realm, and that the sect's founder was still able to communicate with them even after his ascension.

He had never heard of anything like this back in the Spirit Realm, so it appeared that things in the Spirit Domain Realm were truly vastly different from the circumstances in the Spirit Realm.

A pleased look appeared on Gu Yunyue's face at the sight of Han Li's reaction, and she fell silent with a faint smile.

"I didn't think that the Cold Flame Sect would be this powerful. No wonder it's such a dominant force in the Spirit Domain Realm. May I ask what the Heavenly Ghost Sect is like?" Han Li asked.

Gu Yunyue's smile faded, and a serious look appeared on her face as she replied, "The Heavenly Ghost Sect is roughly comparable with our Cold Flame Sect, and they also have a founder who has ascended to the Immortal Realm. Aside from our two sects, there's another sect by the name of the Origin Realm Temple, which also has a backer in the Immortal Realm, and those three sects rank alongside one another, standing at the pinnacle of the Spirit Domain Realm."

Han Li stroked his chin in a contemplative silence for a while, then asked, "Theoretically, the sects are ranked alongside one another, but practically speaking, I'm sure there must be a power hierarchy. How do the three sects compare with one another?"

"The three sects are roughly evenly matched in power, but the Heavenly Ghost Sect has a far longer history than our Cold Flame Sect and the Origin Realm Temple. Throughout its history, there have been three cultivators who have ascended to the Immortal Realm from the Heavenly Ghost Sect, so it's slightly superior in terms of overall power. As for our Cold Flame Sect and the Origin Realm Temple, there's not much that separates us," Gu Yunyue replied.

It seemed that in reality, the Heavenly Ghost Sect was far more powerful than the Cold Flame Sect, but she was unwilling to admit it.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly in contemplation, and he became rather interested in the Cold Flame Sect.

Seeing as the Cold Flame Sect was able to communicate with an immortal, it had to possess a great deal of exceptional resources. Perhaps he would be able to find a way to awaken his nascent soul there.

He enquired about some more matters regarding the Cold Flame Sect before ending the conversation and sitting back down to meditate again.

A short while later, traces of azure light gradually surfaced over his body, but his aura was then quickly subdued before vanishing entirely, making it impossible to detect any magic power fluctuations from him.

Gu Yunyue had returned to the front of the ark, but she couldn't help but be amazed once again after noticing the changes in Han Li's magic power fluctuations.

The sky gradually brightened, and as the spirit ark pierced through the cloud and mist, a majestic mountain range appeared up ahead.

The mountains were extremely steep and dark red in color, making the mountain range resemble an enormous red forest when viewed from a high altitude.

Gu Yunyue was quite relieved to see the red mountain range up ahead.

This mountain range was known as the Red Coral Mountain Range, and it sat on the border of the Prosperous Nation.

On the way here, she had intentionally taken a winding route to avoid the areas where Heavenly Ghost Sect scouts were prevalent, and now that they had made it to this point, they were surely in a far safer situation.

However, as a safety precaution, Gu Yunyue still elevated the spirit ark slightly so that it was able to conceal itself within the clouds up above.

It wasn't a particularly cloudy day, so the clouds in the sky were rather sparse, but traversing through them still provided more cover than nothing.

Yu Menghan and Liu Le'er gradually grew accustomed to traveling on the ark, and they were no longer so afraid. They stood up to look at the beautiful scenery around them, pointing out things that they found interesting to one another, and occasionally giggling when they caught sight of something that caught their fancy.

The mountain range down below quickly receded into the distance, and shortly thereafter, a plain appeared in the distance up ahead, instilling Gu Yunyue with a further sense of reassurance.

"Look out!"

Han Li had been meditating with his eyes closed this entire time, but all of a sudden, his eyes abruptly sprang open.

Both Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan faltered slightly upon hearing this urgent warning.

Gu Yunyue's expression also changed drastically as she immediately made a hand seal, blasting a thick beam of white light out of each of her palms that vanished into the spirit ark.

The spirit ark instantly began to glow brightly as it drew to an abrupt halt, then shot back at an incredible speed.

Right at this moment, one of the white clouds up ahead suddenly turned as black as ink, then transformed into a gargantuan, ghostly face. The sinister ghostly face opened its mouth before chomping down viciously, but it was unable to strike its target as the spirit ark had already retreated to a safe distance away.

A faint cry of surprise rang out from within the ghostly face, following which it collapsed into a black cloud, atop which stood a pair of men.

On the left was a hunch-backed elderly man with a heavily-wrinkled face. He had several strands of sparse yellow hair on his head, and he appeared to already have one foot in the grave.

On the right was a hideous young man with a long face and a large mouth, as well as a pair of squinty little eyes that were giving off a vicious gleam.

Both of them were wearing black robes with a sinister ghostly head design embroidered upon them, and the spiritual pressure that they were exuding indicated that they were both at the Nascent Soul Stage.

Just like Gu Yunyue, the long-faced young man was also at the mid-Nascent Soul Stage, while the hunch-backed elderly man was already at the late-Nascent Soul Stage.

"You're the Windcloud Duo!" Gu Yunyue exclaimed as a grim look appeared on her face.

Chapter 23: Battle

"I didn't think that you would know of us, Fellow Daoist Gu Yunyue. This is truly an honor." The hunch-backed elderly man's voice was extremely unpleasant, like pieces of rusty metal scraping against one another, striking the listener with a sense of discomfort.

The long-faced young man remained silent as his gaze slowly roamed over Han Li and the others, and, as he caught sight of Yu Menghan and Liu Le'er, his eyes lit up slightly as he extended his tongue out of his mouth to lick his thick upper lip.

Liu Le'er hurriedly ducked behind Han Li upon seeing this, and Yu Menghan was also quite disturbed to see this.

As for Gu Yunyue, she was feeling a little flustered. She had guessed that the Heavenly Ghost Sect wouldn't be willing to let things slide, but she didn't think that their pursuers would reach them so quickly, nor did she expect to be hunted by such a notorious pair.

However, as a cultivator with plenty of battle experience under her belt, she quickly regained her composure as she said in a cold voice, "Why are you attacking me on the border of the Prosperous Nation? Are you trying to instigate a war between our two sects?"

"Why ask a question that you already know the answer to? I'm sure you're already well aware of why we're here. We've received orders from Elder Qi to capture the perpetrator who killed his grandnephew, and that girl with the Yu surname," the hunch-backed elderly man cackled as his gaze crept over to Han Li and Yu Menghan.

Han Li was completely unfazed to hear this, but Yu Menghan's complexion immediately paled.

Gu Yunyue gave a cold harrumph and offered no response, but she was scrambling to think of a way out of this situation.

"There's no bad blood between us, Fellow Daoist Gu. As long as you're willing to hand over those two, we can let you go. What do you say?" the hunch-backed elderly man asked.

Gu Yunyue was someone of quite a lofty status in the Cold Flame Sect, so if possible, they wanted to avoid a conflict with her.

A cold look appeared on Gu Yunyue's face as she replied, "Fellow Daoist Han is a guest elder of our sect, while Yu Menghan is an inner court disciple. If I were to hand them over, our Cold Flame Sect would be regarded as the butt of all jokes in the cultivation world!"

"Alright, we gave you a chance! If you have a death wish, then we're more than happy to send you on your way!" the hunch-backed elderly man said in a cold voice.

The long-faced young man had already grown tired of waiting, and as soon as it became clear that a peaceful outcome was out of reach, he immediately sprang into action, sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a vast expanse of gray flames.

The gray flames instantly converged to one spot at his behest, forming a fiery gray vortex.

A fiery ghostly claw the size of a house reached out of the vortex, grabbing at Gu Yunyue and the others.

Gu Yunyue was already prepared for this, and she stomped a foot down onto the spirit ark, upon which it began to glow brightly once again as it shot back in a flash.

At the same time, she raised a hand to release a black longsword, which flew through the air as it transformed into a streak of black light that was 70 to 80 feet in length. The sword struck the palm of the fiery ghostly claw, only for a metallic clang to ring out.

Gu Yunyue was rather taken aback by this, and she immediately made a hand seal, upon which the streak of black light shrank to less than half its original size, but it had become far brighter and more piercing.

The black sword pierced through the fiery ghostly claw before emerging from the other side.

The ghostly claw instantly exploded into countless balls of fire, and the flaming vortex in the sky also dissipated.

An unnatural flush appeared on the long-faced young man's cheeks, and he threw up a mouthful of blood.

He let loose a furious roar as his eyes turned bright red, and he flipped a hand over to produce a black scroll.

A vast expanse of murky gray light then erupted out of his body, forming a smokescreen that made it impossible for anyone on the outside to see what he was doing.

At the same time, the hunch-backed elderly man also stomped a foot onto the ground, and a burst of inky-black light erupted out of his body as he released his enormous late-Nascent Soul Stage spiritual pressure.

Gu Yunyue's expression changed slightly as she withdrew her black longsword, and it circled around above her head as she intensely scrutinized her two assailants with her spiritual sense.

At this point, the spirit ark had already retreated to over 1,000 feet away, and only then did it come to a rest.

"Fellow Daoist Han, these two are extremely powerful and established cultivators of the Heavenly Ghost Sect. If the situation goes sour, take Menghan and Le'er and escape. I'll hold them off to the best of my abilities," Gu Yunyue hurriedly said to Han Li through voice transmission.

Even though she had caught the long-faced young man off guard and emerged as the superior party in that exchange, she knew that she was no match for the hunch-backed elderly man. As for Han Li, she didn't know the extent of his powers, so even if they were to join forces, there was no guarantee that they would be able to hold off their two opponents. Hence, her immediate thought was to flee.

Han Li offered no response as he stood on the spot, looking as if he hadn't even heard her.

Right at this moment, a sinister voice rang out beside Gu Yunyue. "Did you think you can get away?"

Gu Yunyue's heart jolted upon hearing this, and all of a sudden, the black light around the hunch-backed elderly man suddenly exploded, while his body transformed into a gray skeleton.

Gu Yunyue faltered slightly upon seeing this, and a hint of surprise also flashed through Han Li's eyes.

Immediately thereafter, violent spatial fluctuations erupted in the air above the spirit ark, following which a beam of inky-black light shot out without any warning, and the hunch-backed elderly man was standing right within the black light.

He raised his hands, and a giant golden pagoda that was over 100 feet tall appeared in front of him out of thin air amid a flash of golden light, then came crashing down viciously toward the spirit ark.

A burst of terrifying pressure descended from above, and the spiritual light on the surface of the spirit ark rippled in an unstable manner, looking as if it were on the verge of collapse.

Gu Yunyue gave a muffled groan as she made a rapid series of hand seals, casting a string of incantation seals into the black longsword above her head.

The black longsword trembled violently, releasing countless sword projections that swept toward the golden pagoda.

A string of violent explosions rang out as the countless sword projections struck the giant pagoda in rapid succession, only to be shattered upon impact without leaving so much as a single mark on the pagoda itself.

However, the speed of the pagoda's descent was slowed down.

Gu Yunyue took advantage of this opportunity to release a burst of silver light out of her hand. It was a silver handkerchief that rapidly expanded while radiating dazzling silver light.

A projection of mountains and rivers appeared on the surface of the handkerchief, and it was giving off astounding spiritual qi as it positioned itself beneath the giant pagoda, further slowing its descent.

Gu Yunyue's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and a cold look appeared in her eyes as she switched to a different hand seal.

The black longsword immediately began to glow with dazzling black radiance while swelling drastically in size, transforming into a giant black sword that was 50 to 60 feet in the blink of an eye before hurtling toward the hunch-backed elderly man at an incredible speed.

A cold smile appeared on the elderly man's face as he released an incantation seal, and the base of the golden pagoda opened up with a resounding boom, revealing a black hole.

Blinding golden light erupted out of the hole to form a giant golden halo, which released a burst of terrifying suction force that sucked in everything within a radius of several hundred feet.

The giant black sword immediately stopped cold in its tracks, then flew toward the hole at the base of the golden pagoda, unable to resist the suction force.

Gu Yunyue was struggling desperately to stabilize the giant sword, but to no avail, and after just two or three seconds, the giant sword was completely sucked into the golden pagoda.

Gu Yunyue's heart sank as her spiritual connection with the black longsword was completely severed.

The golden light radiating from the giant pagoda became even brighter, and it continued to descend amid a burst of loud rumbling.

The surface of the silver handkerchief began to collapse downward, and under the enormous suction force released by the giant golden pagoda, the mountain and river projections on its surface began to warp, looking as if it were about to be sucked into the pagoda as well.

Gu Yunyue hurriedly made a hand seal, then thrust both hands toward the handkerchief and rapidly injected her magic power into it.

Bright silver light radiated from the mountain and river projections on the surface of the handkerchief, and it was finally stabilized again.

Right as the hunch-backed elderly man raised his hand to continue his attack, a loud boom suddenly rang out in the distance as the gray light around the long-faced young man exploded.

A black scroll was hovering before him, and it was none other than the one that he had summoned earlier, except at this moment, it was already unfurled. There were countless ghostly entities drawn on the scroll's surface, and it was radiating piercing black light.

"Stand down, Brother! I'm going to punish this bitch for hurting me and make her wish she was dead!" the long-faced young man roared as he glowered at Gu Yunyue with a resentful expression.

Chapter 24: Crushed

The hunch-backed elderly man raised an eyebrow upon hearing this, and he briefly stopped what he was doing, but his gaze remained fixed on Gu Yunyue.

At the same time, the long-faced young man flipped a hand over to produce a black dagger, using which he sliced viciously into his own arm.

Blood gushed out of the gash, forming a cloud of dense blood mist that fused into the black scroll.

The black qi emanating from the scroll instantly became significantly denser, and gusts of fierce Yin wind were swept up all around it amid the sound of ghastly howls, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

A pair of fierce ghostly entities leaped out of the scroll, then swelled drastically to around 40 to 50 feet in size.

The two ghostly beings had ape-like upper bodies that were covered in short green fur with sharp white fangs that protruded out of their mouths. Each of them had a pair of thick and strong ape arms with fingers that were tipped with sharp crimson claws that were each around a foot in length, while their lower bodies were enshrouded in black mist, appearing to have no physical form.

The gusts of Yin wind around the scroll became even fiercer, and black qi surged as one ghostly being flew out after another.

In the blink of an eye, over 100 ghostly beings had appeared.

Most of them were at the Foundation Establishment Stage, but there were also five or six of them that were clearly far more massive than the other ones, and they were giving off Core Formation Stage auras.

"Kill them!" the long-faced young man cackled as he stabbed a finger in Gu Yunyue's direction.

The ghostly beings roared in unison as they swarmed the spirit ark with ferocious might.

Gu Yunyue's expression changed drastically as she patted the storage bag on her waist to release four streaks of white light, which descended around her before transforming into four humanoid jade puppets, each of which was around 10 feet tall. The puppets were clad in suits of armor, and each of them was holding a large white flag that was glowing with bright spiritual light.

With a wave of the flags in their hands, dazzling white radiance emanated from the bodies of the puppets before quickly joining together to form a white array that encompassed the entire spirit ark within.

As soon as the array took shape, the army of ghostly beings swarmed onto it, surrounding it from all directions.

The ghostly beings roared ferociously as they attacked the white array with all their might.

In particular, the Core Formation Stage ghostly beings were blasting bursts of green light into the array with devastating power, causing it to tremble violently.

Gu Yunyue hurriedly made a hand seal before releasing bursts of white light onto the four puppets, and only then was the array gradually stabilized.

Meanwhile, the long-faced young man himself also flew over to the white array, and he chanted an incantation as a vast expanse of gray fire emerged on his body again, forming a sea of fire that was over 100 feet in size.

He then made a grabbing motion with both hands, and two small balls of fire detached themselves from the sea of flames before transforming into a pair of fiery spears that were several dozen feet in length.

With a wave of his arms, the two fiery spears shot forth like lightning, flying through the air with a sharp screeching sound before striking the white array with tremendous force.

Two resounding booms rang out as the fiery spears exploded, but the white array also trembled violently, and Gu Yunyue also shuddered as her face paled slightly.

The long-faced young man cackled with glee as he hurled one fiery spear after another into the array.

The white array continued to tremble violently, and it was originally around 70 to 80 feet in size, but it was shrinking rapidly and was quickly reduced to less than 30 feet in size.

Gu Yunyue's face became paler and paler, and her body began to tremble from overexertion as a faint sheen of sweat appeared on her forehead.

The hunch-backed elderly man burst into raucous laughter at the sight of the terrible state that Gu Yunyue was in, and he patted the storage bag on his waist to release 12 streaks of black light, which were revealed to be 12 bone tridents.

The bone tridents expanded rapidly while inky-black flames rose up on their surface, and they gave off a bone-chilling aura as they came hurtling down toward the white array.

They were here on Qi Xuan's orders, so the one who killed Gu Yunyue would naturally be rewarded handsomely.

Gu Yunyue was already a spent force, and the hunch-backed elderly man was taking full advantage to try and land the killing blow.

The long-faced young man was furious to see this, but the hunch-backed elderly man was a superior cultivator to him, so he could only begrudgingly accept this.

A hint of despair surfaced in Gu Yunyue's eyes upon seeing this.

However, right at this moment, a figure rose up into the air from the spirit ark, flying through the white array to arrive outside it in the blink of an eye. It was none other than Han Li.

He moved left and right through the air, conjuring up several afterimages that quickly fused as one, and the 12 bone tridents somehow vanished in the blink of an eye.

The hunch-backed elderly man's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, following which his expression changed drastically.

As it turned out, all 12 of the bone tridents had been caught in Han Li's grasp, and as he rubbed them between his hands, the black flames on the tridents were completely snuffed out.

He took a glance at the tridents before casually stowing them away in an expressionless manner, as if he had just done something completely unremarkable.

"You... You..." The hunch-backed elderly man was both shocked and furious to see this.

As soon as the ghostly beings surrounding the array detected Han Li's aura, they immediately abandoned the array and pounced toward him, letting loose excited roars as they did so.

"What a nuisance!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he sped into the army of ghostly beings as an indistinct azure shadow.

In the face of the azure shadow, all of the ghostly beings in its path were like waves crashing into rocks, exploding violently into countless pieces.

In the blink of an eye, all of the ghostly beings had been slain with incredible ease.

The long-faced young man was utterly astonished as he looked on with wide eyes.

All of a sudden, Han Li appeared in front of him before throwing a vicious punch, and the long-faced young man didn't even get a chance to cry out before his body exploded into scraps of flesh and blood, and not even his nascent soul managed to survive.

The hunch-backed elderly man was horrified to see this, and he hurriedly swept a sleeve through the air to release hundreds of green flying needles. Each needle was around a foot in length and as thin as a strand of hair, with green flames burning on their surface.

The thin needles screeched through the air as they sped toward Han Li, and at the same time, green flames erupted out of the elderly man's body as he fled into the distance, even abandoning the golden pagoda in his desperation to get away.

Han Li remained completely still on the spot as he opened his mouth before taking a deep breath.

A burst of enormous suction force took shape in the air before him, and the entire space buzzed incessantly as all of the flying needles were caught by the suction force before flying into Han Li's mouth.

The needles crunched between his teeth as he chewed briefly, then tipped his head back slightly to swallow everything.

Gu Yunyue's mouth gaped open slightly upon seeing this, and she was completely rooted to the spot.

From the perspective of Yu Menghan and Liu Le'er on the spirit ark, all they saw was a frenzied flurry of activity. Before they had even figured out what had happened, one of their two powerful assailants had been killed, while the other was desperately fleeing the scene, and they were no less shocked than Gu Yunyue.

Meanwhile, Han Li cast his gaze toward the fleeing elderly man, and golden light flashed from his arm as he threw a punch in that direction with an indifferent expression.

A golden fist projection that was around the size of a human head instantly appeared behind the hunch-backed elderly man, and it was flying several times faster than he was.

The hunch-backed elderly man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he hurriedly released a layer of black light around his entire body, right before he was struck by the golden fist projection with devastating force.

The green flames around him exploded violently, but only a pile of bones fell out of the sky.

At the same time, a burst of spatial fluctuations several dozen kilometers away, and a vast expanse of black light appeared out of thin air before the hunch-backed elderly man stumbled out of it.

He took a horrified glance behind him, then opened his mouth to release a burst of green light, which enveloped his body in a layer of green flames before he continued to flee into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's spiritual sense had already been released, so he was well aware of where the hunch-backed elderly man was. However, right as he was about to lash out again, he suddenly lowered his head to look at the azure light around his body, which had clearly become dimmer than before.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he decided against pursuing the elderly man. Instead, he swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light that drew the long-faced young man's storage bag to him, then descended back onto the spirit ark.

He had relied mostly on the power of his physical body during that battle, but he had still expended a great deal of magic power.

Chapter 25: Lu Ya

"Brother Rock!"

Liu Le'er hurriedly rushed toward Han Li upon his return, and there was a concerned look on her face.

She had never witnessed a battle between such powerful cultivators before, and even though Han Li seemed to have secured victory with ease, she still couldn't help but fear that perhaps he had sustained some injuries in the process.

Han Li gave her a warm smile to reassure her, then stowed the storage bag in his hand away.

Without the support of the hunch-backed elderly man's magic power, the giant pagoda's golden radiance quickly faded, and it rapidly shrank before descending from the sky.

With a wave of her hand, Gu Yunyue drew the golden pagoda into her grasp, then took a glance at Han Li, and only after confirming that he had no intention of taking the pagoda for himself did she dare to stow it away into her storage bag.

The golden pagoda was clearly quite a powerful treasure, and its ability to trap other treasures would make it an extremely useful trump card for her in future battles. However, the Windcloud Duo had been defeated by Han Li, so it was only right that this treasure belonged to him. Thankfully, he seemed to have given her silent permission to take the treasure.

Gu Yunyue took a moment to compose herself, then made her way over to Han Li. "Thank heavens you're here with us, Fellow Daoist Han. I knew you were no ordinary cultivator, but I still severely underestimated your powers."

Even though she looked quite calm and collected on the outside, the awe and veneration hidden deep in her eyes didn't escape Han Li's notice.

Even if she had faced the long-faced young man on her own, she knew that there was definitely no way that she would've been able to kill him as easily as Han Li did, inflicting such a heavy blow that even his nascent soul had been unable to escape. On top of that, there was also another late-Nascent Soul Stage enemy present, making Han Li's feat even more remarkable.

"They were trying to kill me, so I naturally had to deal with them," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

A faint smile appeared on Yu Menghan's face upon hearing this, but as she cast her gaze upon Han Li, there was also a hint of awe and veneration in her eyes, intermingled with some other complex emotions.

In her eyes, her master was an unfathomable powerful being. Her father had to treat Daoist Master White Stone with the utmost respect, yet even Daoist Master White Stone didn't dare to step out of line in the slightest in Gu Yunyue's presence. However, Han Li had just displayed incredible power that was far beyond even Gu Yunyue's reach.

To her, Han Li was a massive mystery, and even though she was standing by his side, she felt as if they were separated by a vast galaxy.

"I thought we'd be safe from the Heavenly Ghost Sect after leaving the Prosperous Nation, I wasn't expecting them to come after us so quickly," Gu Yunyue sighed.

"That's only to be expected. After all, we're currently still within the Heavenly Ghost Sect's territory," Han Li replied with a nonchalant expression, not appearing worried in the slightest.

"As soon as we enter our Cold Flame Sect's territory, we should be free from our pursuers," Gu Yunyue replied with a nod, but her expression suddenly stiffened slightly, and she glanced at Han Li with a perplexed look in her eyes.

It was only for an instant, but her peculiar gaze didn't escape Han Li's notice.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he was feeling rather frustrated. During the battle that had just taken place, he had only briefly unleashed a layer of protective spiritual light over his body, yet his magic power had plummeted from the mid-Nascent Soul Stage to the early-Nascent Soul Stage.

Gu Yunyue had most likely sensed the change in his aura, but he naturally wasn't going to bother to explain anything to her.

……

Inside a dark secret chamber deep within a certain cave abode in the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

There were around a dozen lit torches on the walls of the secret chamber, and the yellow flames of the torches were casting countless shadows all over the entire secret chamber.

Right at the center of the secret chamber was a round stone table, in front of which sat a thin elderly man with a head of white hair and a mismatching black beard. He was wearing an ochre robe, and he had one hand resting on the stone table, while his other hand was gently tapping his knee in a rhythmic manner.

He had a very pronounced nose and a pair of deep-set eyes that were staring absentmindedly forward. There was a contemplative expression on his thin and wrinkly face, which was illuminated by the light of the burning torches.

Directly in front of him was a copper mirror roughly the size of a human head hovering in mid-air. The mirror was displaying the visage of a hunch-backed elderly man. It was none other than the surviving half of the Windcloud Duo.

He already had a hunched back to begin with, and he was hunched over even further at this moment. His head was virtually buried against his chest, and he didn't dare to look up at all.

"So what you're saying is that not only did the two of you fail to bring back the people I wanted, one of you died in the process?" the thin elderly man asked.

His voice was extremely deep and coarse.

The hunch-backed elderly man shuddered, then hurriedly replied, "Please forgive me, Martial Uncle Qi. Our enemy was simply far too powerful! In the beginning, he seemed to have intentionally concealed his aura so that he appeared to be no different from a mortal, but in the instant that he entered the battle, he suddenly became a mid-Nascent Soul cultivator.

“He managed to take my 12 bone tridents before I could even see what he was doing, and after that..."

Before he had a chance to finish, he was interrupted by the thin elderly man. "So his cultivation base was inferior to yours, yet he was able to take your treasures with ease?"

"Th... That's right. Not only that, but his physical body is also extremely powerful. Compared with him, the ghostly entities in my junior martial brother's Myriad Ghost Scroll may as well have been made from mud and twigs! All of them were destroyed on contact, and he even ate my Bone Devouring Yin Needles!" the hunch-backed elderly man replied with a hint of lingering fear in his voice.

The thin elderly man fell silent upon hearing this, seemingly having fallen into deep thought again.

The hunch-backed elderly man still didn't dare to raise his head, and the fear in his heart was further fueled by the thin elderly man's prolonged silence. He couldn't help but fall to his knees as he said in a trembling voice, "I'm telling the truth, Martial Uncle Qi! I'm not exaggerating the story at all!"

The thin elderly man remained silent, and only after a long while did he speak again. "Judging from what you've told me, that man is most likely a powerful body cultivator. Cultivators of that nature are extremely rare, and they are indeed too powerful for you to handle. I'll take care of matters from here, you don't need to play any further part in this."

With that, he casually swept a sleeve through the air, and the image of the hunch-backed elderly man on the copper mirror instantly vanished.

"So what if you're a high-grade body cultivator? I'm still going to tear you from limb to limb for killing Hao'er!" [1] the thin elderly man spat through gritted teeth as a vicious look appeared on his face.

Sometime later, his gaze returned to the copper mirror, and he chanted an incantation before making a hand seal, then pointed a finger at the mirror.

The surface of the mirror began to ripple like water, following which another image emerged.

The image depicted a well-built middle-aged man standing in mid-air above a lush forest, and he stroked his short beard as he said with a smile, "It's been quite some time since we last saw each other, Brother Qi. What business do you have with me today?"

"I won't bore you with small talk today, Brother Lu Ya. I have a favor to beg of you," the thin elderly man said with a serious expression.

The middle-aged man could see that the thin elderly man was in no mood to be joking around, so he also adopted a serious expression as he asked, "What is it?"

The thin elderly man took a deep breath, then gave the middle-aged man a recount of everything that had happened, starting with the death of Qi Minghao.

"How dare he go after one of your descendants? He deserves to die 1,000 deaths!" Lu Ya harrumphed coldly after hearing the story.

"I have some matters to attend to in the sect at the moment. I know that you're near the Prosperous Nation right now, so I'm hoping you can go after Hao'er's killer in my stead and exact revenge on him," the thin elderly man said.

Lu Ya was silent for a moment, then mused, "Body cultivators are far more powerful than normal cultivators, but it's extremely difficult for them to advance in their cultivation and break through bottlenecks. The fact that this man has been able to reach such a high level in body cultivation indicates that he must be no ordinary cultivator..."

The thin elderly man took a meaningful glance at Lu Ya, then replied, "According to one of my disciples, he's a guest elder that the Cold Flame Sect is planning to take in, but he still hasn't officially joined the sect yet, so you don't need to worry. If you can kill him for me, you can have my Origin Spirit Pill as repayment."

A hint of elation flashed through Lu Ya's eyes upon hearing this, but he quickly disguised it, then said, "In that case, you can count on me, Brother Qi."

A thought suddenly occurred to the thin elderly man, and a sinister look appeared on his face as he said, "By the way, spare that girl with the Yu surname for now. If possible, bring her to me alive."

Lu Ya faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response.

[1]. In Chinese, it's common to take the last character of a person's name and add 儿(er) at the end as an affectionate pet name, which is what's happening here, with Qi Minghao before referred to as Hao'er. Some of you may remember that Nangong Wan was sometimes referred to as Wan'er by Han Li in RMJI, and that follows the same principle.

[Back]

Chapter 26: Persistent Enemies

In the sky above a desert tens of thousands of kilometers away from the Prosperous Nation's border, a spirit ark that was enshrouded in white light was flying rapidly toward a certain direction.

It was a bright and sunny day with clouds that resembled clumps of cotton drifting lazily through the sky. It was a truly beautiful and relaxing sight to behold, but none of the people on the ark were in the mood to be appreciating the scenery.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes tightly shut at the tail-end of the ark, and there was a layer of faint golden light roaming over his body.

Liu Le'er was seated right next to Han Li with green light surging over her body, and she was clearly also cultivating.

Gu Yunyue and Yu Menghan were standing at the head of the ark, and the latter was occasionally turning around to cast her gaze toward the other end of the ark with a complex look in her eyes. Meanwhile, Gu Yunyue was controlling the ark with a faint smile on her face, and she seemed to be in high spirits.

Two days had already passed since they were last attacked, and during that time, they hadn't encountered any more danger. As they approached the Cold Flame Sect, they were drawing closer and closer to safety.

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li's brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and he opened his eyes, following which the golden light on his body quickly faded.

During these past few days, he had attempted several more methods to try and remove the seal on his nascent soul, but he had made no progress at all and expended quite a bit of magic power in the process.

Even though he had managed to find two pills of a similar caliber to the Sharp Watch Pill in the long-faced young man's storage bag, for some reason, they had no effect on him at all.

It seemed that his condition was far more complex than he had anticipated.

He shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then cast his gaze toward Liu Le'er.

Her aura had clearly become significantly more powerful than before, and she was showing signs of breaking through to the late-Foundation Establishment Stage. This was all thanks to another vial of pills that Han Li had found in the long-faced young man's storage bag.

Han Li gave a pleased nod and didn't interrupt her cultivation. Instead, he stood up and made his way over to the side of the spirit ark before casting his gaze outward.

Gu Yunyue approached him with a smile and said, "All we need to do is travel west from here, and we'll be able to reach the sect in no more than half a month. Once we arrive, our sect will be sure to organize a top-tier cave abode for you so you can recover from your injuries."

Yu Menghan was following along behind her in silence.

"I'll be in your care then, Fellow Daoist," Han Li replied with a nod.

Gu Yunyue was just about to say something else when a burst of faint rumbling suddenly rang out up ahead.

The three of them turned toward the direction where the sound was coming from, and they discovered that there was a vast expanse of darkness on the horizon. Several massive tornadoes were extending directly up into the heavens, sweeping from side to side, and thunderous rumbling was ringing out incessantly from the tornadoes, while the entire sky was enshrouded under a suffocating layer of yellow sand.

Gu Yunyue's brows furrowed slightly as she released an incantation seal, and the spirit ark drew to a halt.

Liu Le'er was roused from her cultivation as a result, and she made her way over to Han Li's side with a curious expression.

"It looks like nothing more than a sandstorm. Is there a problem?" Han Li asked.

"The desert that we're currently in is known as the Yellow Billow Desert, and sandstorms are very rare here, but in the case that a sandstorm does arise, it'll quickly spread across the entire desert and rage on for around a month without rest," Gu Yunyue replied.

"Why don't we just travel directly through it? The sandstorm may encompass the entire desert, but surely it won't have any impact on us," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Of course the sandstorm is of no concern to us, but there's a type of ancient insect known as the Flying Sin Ant that resides in this desert. Normally, they rest beneath the sand in hibernation, but they always come out during sandstorms. One or two of these flying ants naturally pose no threat, but they often appear in vast numbers, and they're incredibly fast.

“On top of that, they're capable of releasing a corrosive mist that's capable of eroding the spiritual natures of all treasures unless they've been refined using devilish arts. Hence, even high-grade cultivators find them to be a huge headache to deal with, and getting caught in a swarm of those flying ants could be quite troublesome," Gu Yunyue explained with a grim expression.

Han Li was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then asked, "What if we fly around this desert?"

At the moment, his magic power was a limited resource, and he didn't want to have to waste it here.

Gu Yunyue considered the question for a moment before replying, "It'll probably extend our journey by over a month."

Han Li fell silent as he stroked his chin in contemplation.

Gu Yunyue was also watching Han Li in silence, clearly waiting for him to make a decision on how to proceed.

All of a sudden, Mo Guang's voice rang out in Han Li's mind. "There's no need to worry about those flying ants, Fellow Daoist Han. Just leave them to me."

"Oh? You have a way to deal with them?" Han Li asked internally.

"Flying Sin Ants are a type of ancient insect born from a mixture of underground baleful yin energy and the resentment of deceased spirits, so they share some similarities with Heavenly Devilish Monarchs like myself.

“I didn't think that they would exist in the Spirit Domain Realm as well. These ants are indeed quite difficult to deal with, but they have a natural fear of sound-based devilish attacks. I may have lost most of my abilities, but even in my current state, dealing with these mere flying ants won't be an issue at all," Mo Guang said in an assured voice.

Han Li considered the situation briefly before making a decision. "Alright, then we'll be counting on you if we encounter those Flying Yin Ants in the desert."

"We're both in the same boat here, so I naturally have to do my part," Mo Guang said before falling silent.

"Going around the desert will take too long, so let's go straight through the sandstorm. If we encounter those Flying Yin Ants, I have a way to deal with them," Han Li said to Gu Yunyue.

Gu Yunyue faltered slightly upon hearing this. "Are you sure, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"Do you not trust me, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li asked with a faint smile.

"I have no intention of doubting you, Fellow Daoist Han. In that case, let's proceed," Gu Yunyue hurriedly replied, then wasted no further time with words as she made a hand seal.

The spirit ark began to glow brightly, releasing a white protective barrier before plunging directly into the sandstorm up ahead.

In the next instant, the surroundings dimmed significantly, and there was nothing in sight in all directions aside from boundless yellow sand that was being carried by fierce gusts of wind, which were blowing viciously against the spirit ark's protective barrier.

The ark immediately began to sway slightly, and in response, Gu Yunyue switched to a different hand seal, releasing a burst of white light that vanished into a certain part of the ark in a flash.

As a result, all of the spirit patterns engraved onto the surface of the ark immediately lit up, and the white protective barrier instantly became several times brighter. The ark itself was also stabilized, and it continued onward.

Initially, Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan were rather concerned by the sight of the ferocious sandstorm outside, but as time passed, it became clear that there was no way that the sandstorm would be able to break through the spirit ark's protective barrier. Hence, their concerns were put at ease, and they began to marvel at the rare scenery outside the white light barrier.

Gu Yunyue was controlling the spirit ark, carefully maneuvering it so that it avoided the tornadoes up ahead, and the speed of the ark's advance wasn't hampered by much.

Soon, they had already been traveling through the sandstorm for several hours, and thankfully, they were yet to encounter any Flying Sin Ants.

Han Li was standing at the head of the ark with a calm expression and his hands clasped behind his back, but a hint of blue light suddenly flashed through his eyes as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction up ahead.

Gu Yunyue immediately noticed the slight change in Han Li's expression, and she asked, "What is it, Fellow Daoist Han?"

"Looks like we have trouble, Fellow Daoist Gu," Han Li replied as he turned to her with a faint smile.

Gu Yunyue faltered slightly upon hearing this, unsure of what Han Li was referring to.

Right at this moment, one of the tornadoes up ahead suddenly moved directly toward the spirit ark.

This tornado was particularly thick, and it extended all the way up into the heavens. Even before it arrived, the spirit ark was almost swept up by the ferocious gusts of wind that it was releasing.

Gu Yunyue's expression changed drastically upon hearing this, and she had no time to ponder what Han Li had just said as she quickly stomped a foot down onto the ark.

The flying ark immediately began to glow brightly as it sped forward rapidly, instantly covering a distance of close to 1,000 feet, allowing it to just barely evade the tornado.

However, before Gu Yunyue had a chance to catch her breath, the ground around the ark suddenly fell away, and pillars of yellow light erupted into the sky.

These pillars of yellow light instantly intertwined with one another to form a huge yellow array in the blink of an eye.

In particular, the array that had appeared on the ground was extremely complex and over 1,000 feet in size.

Gu Yunyue was naturally quite alarmed to see this.

All of a sudden, the surrounding scenery took on a drastic change, and they were transported into a glittering and translucent world. They were surrounded by a series of mountains, and the sky and the ground were shimmering with yellow light.

A burst of enormous spiritual pressure compressed toward the spirit ark from all directions, and countless cracks quickly appeared on the white protective barrier around the ark, looking as if it were going to crumble away at any moment.

Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan immediately let loose cries of alarm upon seeing this.

In contrast, Han Li remained as calm as ever as he reached out a hand to summon a small copper bell, which swelled to several dozen feet in size before descending onto the spirit ark, encompassing Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan beneath it.

The yellow bell was a defensive treasure that Han Li had found in the long-faced young man's storage bag, and it was perfect for this situation.

Almost at the exact same moment, the white light barrier around the spirit ark was shattered, and an enormous burst of pressure descended upon the ark.

The spiritual light around Han Li and Gu Yunyue's bodies wavered slightly, but they were able to bear the pressure without much difficulty.

The spiritual light radiating from the yellow bell also flickered erratically for a moment before returning to normal again.

"Could it be that the Heavenly Ghost Sect has sent more people after us?"

Gu Yunyue was doing her best to maintain her composure, but judging from the immense pressure being released by the array, she could tell that it definitely couldn't have been erected by a normal Nascent Soul cultivator, and that was making her feel a little panicked.

"The Heavenly Ghost Sect sure is persistent!" Han Li chuckled.

Chapter 27: Carrying the Five Mountains, Crushing the Five Ghosts

As soon as Han Li's voice trailed off, the surrounding space suddenly underwent a change.

A series of giant yellow rocks the size of millstones emerged out of thin air, and there were around 20 to 30 of them. They were positioned tightly next to one another, forming a watertight encirclement around the spirit ark.

Gu Yunyue's heart jolted slightly upon seeing this, and before she had a chance to do anything, the surfaces of the giant rocks flashed with dazzling light, and they began to spin rapidly while crashing toward the spirit ark.

Gu Yunyue was greatly alarmed to see this, and she immediately made a hand seal, upon which a streak of black light rose up into the sky from her body, then instantly swelled drastically in size, transforming into a giant black sword that was over 100 feet in length.

The giant sword swiveled around as it released a vast expanse of black light, which took on the form of a dragon with a long tail trailing behind it as it struck the nearest rock.

A resounding boom rang out, and the giant sword shattered the rock with great difficulty, but as a result of the impact, the sword itself was also sent flying back, flipping end over end, and the radiance that it was giving off had also completely faded.

Gu Yunyue shuddered violently, and she stumbled back several steps before steadying herself as a stunned look appeared on her face.

The power of that single giant rock in free fall was comparable to an all-out attack from a Nascent Soul cultivator, and she couldn't help but shudder internally at the sight of the 20 to 30 translucent giant rocks that were rapidly approaching from all directions.

However, right at this moment, Han Li's voice rang out beside her.

"Focus on protecting those two and leave the rest to me."

Before she had a chance to reply, Han Li had already risen up from the spirit ark with golden light glowing from his hands, and he spun around as he threw punches at the air all around him.

A string of resounding booms rang out in all directions as all of the giant yellow rocks were struck by a burst of tremendous force almost at the exact same time, then exploded into countless rock fragments that rained down from the sky.

"So you really are a body cultivator." A cold harrumph rang out, but it was impossible to determine where the voice was coming from.

Gu Yunyue hurriedly inspected her surroundings, trying to find the owner of the voice.

Meanwhile, a hint of derision appeared in Han Li's eyes, and he abruptly turned around before flicking a finger through the air, unleashing a burst of azure sword qi that shot forth like lightning before striking a certain corner of the translucent yellow world, exploding upon impact.

The air there rippled violently, and a burly man dressed in black stumped out into the open.

The man had a very sturdy build with a short beard on his square face, which was currently etched with shock.

The burly man's expression quickly returned to normal, and he asked, "I didn't think that you would also be a sword cultivator. It's quite remarkable that you were able to see through my illusory array as a mere Nascent Soul cultivator. Based on that alone, I'm sure you're not just some nameless cultivator. Who are you?"

"It doesn't matter who I am. A dead man like you doesn't need to know too much," Han Li chuckled coldly.

"What a joke! I was only putting a fraction of this array's power on display, don't think that you've got the better of me! I'm going to crush you to a pulp with this next attack!" The burly man was infuriated by Han Li's provocation, and he made a hand seal, upon which yellow ripples surged over his body, and he vanished into thin air once again.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

This array was quite an intricate construction, and the burly man had most likely concealed himself somewhere deep within it. To Han Li's surprise, he was no longer able to detect the burly man even with his spiritual sense.

However, he then gave a cold harrumph as golden light appeared all over his entire body. His plan was to destroy the array with brute force, leaving the burly man with nowhere to hide.

However, right at this moment, an unexpected turn of events suddenly unfolded.

The entire sky abruptly darkened, and five enormous creatures with black qi surging around their bodies emerged, surrounding the spirit ark from five different directions.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and piercing blue light flashed through his eyes.

Beneath the black qi were five giant black ghosts, each of which was around 300 to 400 feet tall. If it weren't for the curved horns growing on their heads, they would be the spitting image of apes that had been significantly enlarged. Their bodies were covered in short black fur, and their mouths were filled with sharp fangs, while their eyes were bright red in color. They were extremely fearsome to behold, but their expressions were quite blank and vacant.

Each of the giant ghosts was holding a miniature black mountain.

Compared with these five ghosts, Han Li was made to appear as tiny as an ant.

Gu Yunyue's expression changed drastically upon seeing this.

Every single one of these five giant ghosts was giving off an aura that was superior to hers, and a layer of cold sweat instantly appeared on her forehead.

As for Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan, they were unable to withstand the combined spiritual pressure being released by the five giant ghosts, and they had fallen unconscious on the spot.

The five giant ghosts let loose a collective deafening roar, and a vicious gleam flashed through their bright red eyes as they swung their ape arms violently to hurl the five miniature mountains that they were holding through the air.

The miniature mountains glowed brightly with spiritual light, and they swelled rapidly in size as soon as they left the hands of the giant apes, expanding to over 1,000 feet tall in the blink of an eye as they crashed directly toward Han Li and the spirit ark.

Even before the giant mountains arrived, an asphyxiating sense of pressure had already descended upon the spirit ark, and the space around the ark was buzzing incessantly as gusts of fierce wind were instantly swept up.

Gu Yunyue was almost unable to suppress the urge to cry out in horror, and all she could do was summon a series of treasures in a panicked frenzy, conjuring up several layers of light barriers of different colors around herself and the two unconscious young women on the ark.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and golden light flashed from his palms as he extended his hands nonchalantly toward the oncoming mountains.

A string of five deafening booms rang out in rapid succession, and incredibly powerful shockwaves surged through the air one after another.

The entire yellow space began to buzz loudly while warping violently, and finally, it reached a breaking point, shattering with a dull thump.

With the yellow space destroyed, the environment reverted back to the desert, and countless bursts of yellow light scattered erratically in all directions.

The formidable shockwaves were released upon the desert, proliferating outward in all directions, causing the surrounding sandstorm to churn violently.

Even though the yellow space had been destroyed, it was only an illusion to begin with, and the glowing yellow array on the ground was still standing.

The five giant ghosts were also still hovering in mid-air, but their expressions had become vacant and aloof again.

The burly man emerged out of thin air, and a pleased smile appeared on his face.

In the face of these five ghosts, even a late-Deity Transformation cultivator would definitely struggle immensely unless they possessed a powerful spirit treasure.

However, in the next instant, his smile abruptly stiffened, and his eyes widened as he looked down with an incredulous expression.

As it turned out, the five enormous mountains had been stacked in a pile on top of one another, and Han Li was standing casually in mid-air beneath the base of the fifth mountain, casually supporting it with one hand as if he were carrying nothing more than five feathers.

As for the spirit ark beneath Han Li and the three women on it, they were completely unscathed.

Before the burly man had a chance to react, Han Li exhaled nonchalantly, releasing a burst of white energy out of his mouth, and the five giant mountains were blown away like leaves in the wind.

The surfaces of the mountains flashed with black light, and they rapidly shrank back to their original size.

Han Li casually flicked his fingers through the air, and the five miniature mountains were instantly sent flying toward the burly man at an incredible speed, reaching him in the blink of an eye.

The burly man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and dazzling black light erupted from his body as he plummeted rapidly toward the ground, just barely evading the five miniature mountains.

All of a sudden, Han Li's body blurred, and he appeared in front of the five mountains in wraith-like manner, and he casually reached out again to stop the mountains cold in their tracks.

He then swiveled around before kicking two of the miniature mountains with his feet, and the two mountains instantly descended from above like a pair of shooting stars, flying close to twice as fast as they had been when they were launched through the air earlier.

The two miniature mountains flashed with black light as they abruptly expanded once again, swelling to over 1,000 feet tall in the blink of an eye, and the whistling sound that they produced as they flew through the air was also heightened into a terrifying rumble.

One of the mountains was crashing toward the array down below, while the other was hurtling toward the burly man.

A resounding boom rang out as the former struck the yellow array with devastating force.

The array immediately began to glow with dazzling radiance in an attempt to resist, but the astonishing power imbued within the giant mountain crushed its resistance with ease, and it instantly exploded into countless bursts of light.

With the array destroyed, the spirit ark was instantly freed, and it was carried away far into the distance by a gust of fierce wind.

Meanwhile, the other mountain was hurtling rapidly toward the burly man, catching up to him before he had even landed on the ground.

The burly was greatly alarmed by this, and he opened his mouth to expel a mouthful of blood essence. His entire body was instantly enshrouded in a layer of crimson light, and he transformed into a burst of serpentine spiritual light that sped through the air, boosting his speed by severalfold.

The second giant mountain crashed into the ground, and vast volumes of sand erupted in all directions.

In the instant that the giant mountain struck the ground, the streak of serpentine spiritual light flew over the ground, appearing over 1,000 feet away in a flash. The burly man was encompassed within the streak of light, and his entire body was already drenched in cold sweat.

Before he had a chance to catch his breath, a dark shadow suddenly appeared over him, and he looked up to see another giant mountain rapidly descending upon him. At this point, it was already too close for him to evade.

Chapter 28: Alarmed

The burly man let loose a desperate cry as he swept his hands through the air, releasing two bursts of light, one yellow and one black.

It was a pair of treasures, one of which was a black cane, while the other was a large yellow seal with countless runes flashing on its surface, and both of them hurtled directly toward the giant black mountain.

The two treasures were giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations, and it was clear that they were the burly man's trump cards.

He made a hand seal before letting loose a thunderous roar, and two enormous bursts of light appeared, one yellow and one black, and they were able to slow down the descent of the giant black mountain.

The burly man took advantage of this opportunity to flee back in retreat.

However, the two bursts of light only managed to resist for a brief moment. The burly man had only just managed to fly over 100 feet away when the giant mountain crushed the two bursts of light, then slammed into the ground, causing sand to erupt in all directions once again.

The burly man flew out of the sand, but he was no longer moving as quickly as before. His face was as pale as a sheet, and half of his body was drenched in blood, while his left arm was hanging limply by his side.

Even though he had reacted very quickly, the giant mountain was far too fast, and he was still grazed by it in the end, resulting in severe injuries.

The burly man threw up a large mouthful of blood as he fell onto the ground with a horrified expression. However, he then immediately gritted his teeth and flipped a hand over to produce a white talisman. Countless densely packed runes were inscribed onto the talisman's surface, and it was giving off powerful spatial fluctuations.

The burly man quickly chanted an incantation, mustering up all that remained of his magic power to try and activate the talisman.

However, right at this moment, another massive shadow appeared over his head, and yet again, he was faced with a falling mountain, this one descending at an even more alarming speed than the previous three mountains.

The burly man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this. He needed some time to activate this spatial talisman.

In his desperation, he hurriedly made a strange hand seal, and black light erupted from his body to form a black array.

All of a sudden, the five giant ghosts that had been standing in mid-air just a second ago appeared around him, forming a protective encirclement.

The eyes of the five ghosts flashed with crimson light, and they roared in unison as they swept their enormous claws through the air, unleashing a series of black claw projections that sped toward the base of the black mountain.

As soon as the claw projections struck the giant mountain, they were instantly shattered, and the downward momentum of the mountain was hampered slightly, but it was still crashing down with tremendous force.

The five ghosts roared in unison as black qi surged over their bodies, and the muscles on their bodies bulged, particularly those on their arms and legs.

They reached up with their thick, musclebound arms to resist the giant mountain with no regard for their own lives.

As soon as their arms came into contact with the giant mountain, they were instantly shattered by the enormous impact. However, the five ghosts were still roaring valiantly as they resisted the mountain with their bodies, refusing to take a single backward step.

The giant black mountain struck their bodies with ferocious might, and a sickening grinding sound rang out as blood and flesh flew in all directions.

The giant mountain was finally stopped.

The upper bodies of the five ghosts had been completely destroyed, but they were still standing with their feet buried deep in the desert sand, resembling five enormous pillars that were supporting the giant mountain.

The burly man heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, and he hurriedly injected all of his remaining magic power into the white talisman.

The talisman began to glow with white light, and he was ecstatic to see this.

However, right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out as the final mountain came crashing down, landing on the fourth mountain.

A burst of terrifying force descended from above, and what remained of the five ghosts' bodies instantly exploded into dust.

The burly man felt the air constrict around him, rendering him completely immobile.

The two giant mountains then came crashing down upon him, and his body was crushed into a pile of mincemeat before he even had a chance to cry out.

All of a sudden, a burst of golden light shot out of the sand beneath the giant mountain, then sped away rapidly into the distance.

Han Li focused his gaze on the streak of golden light to find that it was a miniature golden figure that was only around three inches tall. Its appearance was identical to that of the burly man, except its hair was completely disheveled, and it wore a horrified expression as it flew toward the northwest, clutching a silver storage bracelet tightly to its chest.

It was none other than the burly man's nascent soul!

"Go!"

Han Li made a grabbing motion, then with a casual flick of his wrist, he sent a streak of black light flying toward the burly man's nascent soul at an incredible speed.

Meanwhile, Gu Yunyue had only just managed to stabilize the spirit ark, and she just so happened to cast her gaze toward Han Li's direction. She heard a sharp screeching sound in her ear, but her eyes were unable to follow the trajectory of the streak of black light.

In the next instant, a resounding boom rang out in the distant sky, and the burly man's nascent soul exploded into a ball of golden light.

A black palm-sized object also fell out of the sky, and it was nothing more than a piece of normal iron essence.

As for the burly man's silver storage bracelet, it was drawn into Han Li's grasp with a casual wave of his hand. He then flew over to the five scattered mountains, shrinking them back down to their miniature forms and stowing them away before returning to the spirit ark.

All the while, Gu Yunyue was staring blankly at him as if she were looking at a complete stranger.

Earlier in her panicked state, she didn't get a chance to try and identify the burly man. However, thinking back to the cultivation arts and secret techniques that he had unleashed, she was able to identify him as an early-Deity Transformation Stage elder of the Heavenly Ghost Sect by the name of Lu Ya.

He was particularly adept in the art of manipulating ghosts, and it was said that over a decade ago, he was able to hold his own in battle against two Origin Realm Temple cultivators of the same cultivation base.

Despite all of his accolades, he had been slain by Han Li with ease, and this had already exceeded the boundaries of Gu Yunyue's comprehension.

It had finally become clear to her that there was no comparison whatsoever between her and Han Li, and she was utterly astonished.

After a long while, Gu Yunyue finally returned to her senses, and she asked with a wry smile, "Fellow Daoist Han, are you really only a Nascent Soul cultivator?"

The awe and veneration in her eyes were clear to see.

"I'm sure you can tell that for yourself, can't you, Fellow Daoist Gu?" Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"I'm naturally able to discern the level of your magic power fluctuations, but your prowess in battle far exceeds what should be possible for a Nascent Soul cultivator! Even among all of the Deity Transformation Stage elders of our sect, I can't think of any who would be capable of slaying other Deity Transformation cultivators so easily," Gu Yunyue sighed.

"My only advantage is that I possess a physical body slightly more powerful than most, I wouldn't dare to compare myself with the powerful elders of the Cold Flame Sect," Han Li replied with a shake of his head, then spoke no further on the subject.

Instead, he directed his gaze toward Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan, who were still laying on the ground in an unconscious state, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure spiritual light that passed over the two.

Both of the young women slowly awakened, but as they opened their eyes, they were a little disoriented.

As a Foundation Establishment cultivator, Liu Le'er quickly recalled what had just happened, and she sat bolt upright with an alarmed expression.

"Brother Rock! You..."

"Don't worry, everything's fine now. We can continue onward," Han Li said in a gentle voice, looking as if nothing had happened.

……

"Peak Master, according to the message that Martial Niece Gu just sent back, that vagrant cultivator with the Han surname definitely isn't just some ordinary Nascent Soul cultivator. Who could've thought that she would run into such an interesting character on this trip?"

Inside a conference hall within a certain mountain in the Cold Flame Sect, a burly man with a coarse and rugged appearance was speaking to a middle-aged man in a scholarly robe.

The middle-aged man was clean-shaven and was wearing an azure robe, holding an ancient azure scroll in his hands, giving him the appearance of an elegant and refined scholar.

"The fact that he was able to kill an early-Deity Transformation cultivator with the power of his physical body alone indicates that he's clearly a high-grade body cultivator," the azure-robed man replied with a nod.

"In any case, it's certainly great news that the Heavenly Ghost Sect has lost one of its Deity Transformation Stage elders. I must say, I'm very interested in this vagrant cultivator," the burly man chuckled with a hint of triumph in his eyes.

A faint smile also appeared on the azure-robed man's face upon hearing this, and he said, "In that case, I'll get you to greet him in person once he arrives. I'm sure you know what needs to be done."

"Yes," the burly man replied.

Chapter 29: Spiritflame Mountain Range

At the same time, in a certain cave abode, a thin elderly man wearing an ochre robe was situated on the main seat gently blowing into a cup of tea that he was holding in his hand.

In front of him was a middle-aged man with a pair of narrow eyes, standing with his head lowered slightly and a respectful look on his face.

"Given how much time has passed, Lu Ya should be done on his end," the thin elderly man mused.

"There's no chance that anything could go wrong under Elder Lu's watch. Only someone of such a lofty status as yourself would be able to request such a favor from Elder Lu," the middle-aged man said in a respectful voice.

"Out of all of my descendants, Hao'er is the only one who possesses the aptitude to be destined for great things, yet to think that he would die such a premature death! That bastard should be killed thousands of times over for what he's done!" the elderly man said in a furious voice as he slammed down his teacup.

"Look on the bright side, Patriarch. Once Yu Menghan is captured, you'll be well on your way to attaining full mastery of your cultivation art," the middle-aged man hurriedly consoled.

The fury on the elderly man's face eased slightly, and he said, "Come to think of it, she's partially to blame for Hao'er's death as well, but I'll spare her for now, seeing as she possesses a constitution that's useful to me."

As soon as his voice trailed off, his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he cast his gaze toward the gates of his cave abode.

Moments later, the sound of footsteps rang out, and a young female servant appeared at the cave abode's entrance, then extended a respectful bow as she declared, "Elder Qi, Elder Mo has come to see you."

Before the elderly man had a chance to reply, a cold male voice rang out from outside the cave abode.

"To think that you're still in the mood to be sipping tea in your cave abode at a time like this. I must say, your composure is very remarkable, Elder Qi."

Immediately thereafter, a middle-aged man in a black robe with a tall hat on his head appeared outside the entrance.

Qi Xuan raised an eyebrow at the sight of the man, and he gestured for the servant to leave before asking, "What business do you have with me, Mo Chen? Unless I'm mistaken, I don't believe we arranged a meeting at this time."

Instead of answering Qi Xuan's question, Mo Chen raised one of his own. "Elder Lu Ya's soul badge suddenly cracked not long ago. Do you have anything to say about that, Elder Qi?"

"What did you say?" Qi Xuan immediately sprang to his feet with a stunned expression.

"According to those who last saw Elder Lu, he went to intercept a group of people at your request, and that was what led to his death. May I ask who you requested him to intercept, Elder Qi?" Mo Chen asked in a cold voice.

"That's impossible! How could a pair of Nascent Soul cultivators possibly have been a match for Lu Ya?" Qi Xu was absolutely incredulous.

"Elder Lu Ya was an early-Deity Transformation cultivator, yet not only was he killed, even his nascent soul was unable to escape. Am I supposed to believe that you had no idea at all about how much danger you were placing Elder Lu in? I hope you haven't made a powerful enemy for the sect all for your own selfish vendettas. In any case, I'll have to ask you to come with me on a trip to the Enforcement Hall, Elder Qi," Mo Chen said in a cold voice.

……

Several days later, Han Li's group finally emerged from the Yellow Billow Desert.

Along the way, they were attacked by several swarms of Flying Sin Ants, but they were easily taken care of by Han Li through Mo Guang, and they encountered no further pursuers from the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

Furthermore, given that Han Li was able to slay a Deity Transformation cultivator so easily, Gu Yunyue was not surprised at all to see that Han Li was able to deal with the Flying Sin Ants as well.

The consecutive days of travel had left Yu Menghan and Liu Le'er feeling rather exhausted, and they were cuddled up together, sleeping soundly on one side of the spirit ark.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed at the tail-end of the spirit ark with his brows slightly furrowed and a rather peculiar look in his eyes. In front of him seven or eight vials of different colors and materials, all of which had been completely emptied.

"How did it go, Fellow Daoist Han?" Mo Guang's voice rang out in his mind.

"Most of these pills came from that Deity Transformation cultivator, and there's no lack of pills of a decently high caliber among them, but not a single one has had any effect on me," Han Li sighed.

During the previous battle, he was able to kill his opponent with his immense physical strength and the help of those five mountains, so he hadn't expended much magic power, but it was still naturally a problem that he was unable to increase his current reserves of magic power.

"What about the top-grade spirit stones?"

"I can't absorb them, either," Han Li replied with a wry smile, spreading open his hand to reveal a spirit stone that had already become completely devoid of luster.

"It seems that only certain special pills will have an effect on you," Mo Guang mused.

"Perhaps. So far, only that Sharp Watch Pill and that golden pill I found in Qi Minghao's storage bag have been effective. Once we get to the Cold Flame Sect, I'm going to get another Sharp Watch Pill and study it thoroughly. Perhaps I'll be able to find out the underlying reasons then," Han Li replied as he absentmindedly stroked the small vial that he wore around his neck.

……

Half a month later, a spirit ark sped through the air above a lush mountain range.

There was one man and three women on the ark, and they were none other than Han Li's group.

"This Spiritflame Mountain Range is the entrance to our Cold Flame Sect," Gu Yunyue introduced with a smile as she swept her gaze over the forest down below.

"The spirit veins are very stable, and there's a vast abundance of spiritual qi. This is indeed a fantastic place," Han Li mused with a nod of approval.

Yu Menghan was ecstatic to hear this, but after looking around, a puzzled look appeared on her face as she turned to Gu Yunyue.

Liu Le'er was holding onto the side of the spirit ark, leaning her body over the edge to inspect her surroundings, but she couldn't see any signs of a sect amid the lush greenery, either, and she couldn't help but ask, "Brother Rock, I can also sense that the spiritual qi here is very abundant, but I don't see any sect."

"All major sects are concealed by powerful arrays. We are currently situated outside the array, which is equivalent to standing outside the walls of a city, so we naturally can't see what's inside," Han Li replied with a smile.

Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan didn't fully understand this concept, but they still nodded in response.

"Fellow Daoist Han, please wait for a moment while I inform the sect of our arrival," Gu Yunyue said.

She flipped a hand over as she spoke, producing a palm-sized golden badge with a flame design etched onto its surface.

A burst of light emerged on the badge, and the flame design suddenly began to sway as if it were an actual flame.

A streak of light shot forth from the badge, flying directly into the mountain range down below.

Moments later, a burst of ripples suddenly spread through the air below the spirit ark, and a semi-spherical golden light barrier that was barely visible slowly emerged.

The entirety of the Spiritflame Mountain Range, which stretched for several hundred kilometers, was completely encompassed within the light barrier.

"As expected of one of the most dominant sects in a realm," Han Li remarked with a hint of approval in his voice.

Liu Le'er and Yu Menghan were both gripping onto the edge of the spirit ark, looking down with awe and amazement in their eyes.

Beneath the golden light barrier were countless palaces and pagodas interspersed throughout the lush forest.

Some of the buildings were situated individually atop sheer cliffs, while others were connected together in a cluster. Some were positioned in canyons and gorges, while others were built halfway up mountains.

At the center of the entire mountain range were around a dozen mountains that were far taller than all of the other ones, and there was white mist and purple qi rising up from those mountains. It was clear just from a glance that those peaks were particularly abundant in spiritual qi.

"This place is beautiful!" Yu Menghan couldn't help but exclaim.

Liu Le'er also nodded eagerly in agreement.

Gu Yunyue was clearly in a very good mood following their return to the sect, and she turned to Han Li with a smile as she said, "Fellow Daoist Han, Elder Luo is already waiting for us on Cloudrise Peak. Let's go see him right away."

Han Li nodded in response.

Right as the spirit ark passed through the light barrier, he felt a burst of spiritual sense sweep over his body, and he presumed that it belonged to the aforementioned Elder Luo.

After Han Li and the others officially entered the Cold Flame Sect, Liu Le'er took a curious glance upward to find that the light barrier had already disappeared, and all that was left to be seen were the pristine blue sky and the drifting white clouds.

The spirit ark flew toward the center of the mountain range, then descended onto a lush mountain peak that extended all the way up into the clouds.

At the foot of that mountain was a spacious white plaza, where an imposing man was standing, casting his gaze toward the spirit ark from afar.

The man had a set of rugged features and was wearing an ochre robe with a black belt around his waist, accentuating the outline of his pronounced pectoral muscles. Judging from the aura that he was giving off, he was a Deity Transformation cultivator.

Chapter 30: Raising the Land

After stowing the spirit ark away, Gu Yunyue made her way toward the burly man as she extended a respectful curtsey. "I pay my respects to Martial Uncle Luo."

"Thank you for your hard work, Martial Niece Gu. You must be Fellow Daoist Han, right?" the burly man asked as his gaze fell upon Han Li.

"That's correct," Han Li replied.

"My name is Luo Jun. Peak Master Nangong wanted to welcome you in person today, but there were some matters that he had to attend to, so I had to take his place. I hope you won't mind, Fellow Daoist Han," the burly man said with a smile.

"Of course not," Han Li replied with a smile.

Luo Jun's gaze then fell upon Yu Menghan, and his eyes lit up slightly as he remarked, "This must be your new disciple, right, Martial Niece Gu? She's quite a good find!"

"Junior Yu Menghan pays her respects to Elder Luo," Yu Menghan hurriedly said as she extended a curtsey.

"As long as she works hard in her cultivation, I'm certain she'll surpass me someday," Gu Yunyue said with a pleased smile.

After that, Luo Jun greeted Liu Le'er as well, and a strange look appeared on his face once he learned that she and Han Li referred to one another as brother and sister, but he offered no comment on the matter.

Having witnessed Han Li's power on the way here, Liu Le'er was no longer as anxious and uneasy in the presence of unfamiliar human cultivators. She was confident that as long as Han Li was with her, no one would be able to touch her.

Luo Jun's gaze returned to Han Li, and he said, "Fellow Daoist Han, not only were you able to kill a Deity Transformation Stage elder of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, you've also ensured a safe return to the sect for Martial Niece Gu. Given your powers and the contributions you've already made to the sect, we would be honored to accept you as a guest elder.

“There are around a dozen cave abodes for guest elders currently available for you to select from. Do you have any special requirements or requests that you'd like to raise?"

"Truth be told, I'm currently carrying some injuries, so it would be ideal if I could have a more peaceful and secluded cave abode to aid in my rest and recovery. Aside from that, I'm also somewhat familiar with the art of pill refinement, so it would be even better if I could have a cave abode in close proximity to a plot for spirit farmland," Han Li replied in an unhurried manner.

Luo Jun faltered slightly upon hearing these requests, following which his brows furrowed slightly as he said, "That might be a problem. Out of the remaining cave abodes, there are several that are quite peaceful and secluded, but unfortunately, none of them have any adjacent plots of spirit farmland.

“On top of that, most of the spirit farmland on Cloudrise Peak are looked after by our disciples, and the majority of those plots of land are situated on some sloped areas that receive the most sun exposure during the day, and I can't say they're very peaceful areas."

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and it seemed that he was grappling with a dilemma.

Luo Jun could see the change in Han Li's expression, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he suggested, "How about this? Choose a plot of spirit farmland that you like, and I'll get some disciples to construct a brand new cave abode on that plot of land right away. What do you think, Fellow Daoist Han?"

Han Li was silent for a moment, then suddenly chuckled, "There's no need for that. If there are no available cave abodes with adjacent plots of spirit farmland, then I can just carry a plot up there myself. Is that something that's allowed, Elder Luo?"

Gu Yunyue and Yu Menghan both faltered slightly upon hearing this, unsure of exactly what Han Li was proposing.

Meanwhile, Liu Le'er was snuggled up close to Han Li's side, inspecting her surroundings with an intrigued expression, paying no heed to the ongoing conversation.

Luo Jun clearly wasn't expecting such a response from Han Li, and he burst into laughter as an intrigued look appeared on his face. "So instead of conforming to the land, you're going to make the land conform to you! How bold of you, Fellow Daoist Han! Of course that's within the rules. Please come with me."

Thus, Luo Jun led Han Li and his group to a valley halfway up the mountain. There were several plots of spirit farmland in the valley that had been clearly separated, amounting to a total of around an acre in area, and there were some servants toiling away as they tended to the farmland.

"Fellow Daoist Han, these plots of spirit farmland once belonged to a guest elder who perished unexpectedly during an outing several years ago. In the wake of his passing, I've been looking after these plots of spirit farmland. If they catch your fancy, then you can do with them as please," Luo Jun said as he casually gestured toward the valley. up ahead.

"Thank you, Elder Luo." Han Li's gaze roamed over the valley as a hint of a smile appeared on his face.

For some reason, Luo Jun couldn't help but feel a sense of unease upon seeing this.

Han Li strode forward as he took a deep breath, then leaned down and raised his fist before slamming it into the ground.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire valley trembled violently, and a crater had been smashed into the ground by his fist. It wasn't a very large crater, but it was so deep that its bottom was entirely out of sight.

Yu Menghan swayed unsteadily, and if Gu Yunyue hadn't caught her, she would've fallen onto the ground.

Liu Le'er's also swayed slightly before hurriedly steadying herself.

Most of the servants who were working on the plot of farmland were Qi Refinement cultivators, and they had no idea what was happening. All of them cried out in alarm as they hurriedly fled the valley.

Meanwhile, Luo Jun was watching Han Li in silence.

Han Li made his way around the plots of spirit farmland as he strode into the valley, throwing a punch into the ground once every several hundred feet.

During the subsequent span of around 15 minutes, resounding booms rang out incessantly across the entire valley, and Han Li made a full lap of the valley before returning to the original spot that he had set off from.

Despite the manual labor that he had just completed, Han Li wasn't showing any signs of exertion at all, much to Luo Jun's amazement.

Without any further ado, Han Li crouched down before plunging his hands straight into the ground beneath him.

He then raised his arms violently, and the valley rumbled incessantly as a rift was instantly torn into the ground, gradually extending outward from Han Li's hands.

The rift connected all of the craters that had been punched into the ground by Han Li, ultimately the entire plot of spirit farmland in the valley.

Only now did Liu Le'er realize what Han Li was doing, and a look of admiration surfaced in her eyes as an excited flush appeared on her cheeks.

Gu Yunyue's mouth gaped open in shock, but she was unable to utter even a single word.

One final burst of rumbling rang out as the entire plot of spirit farmland was uprooted and lifted vertically upward.

From afar, it would appear as if the plot of spirit farmland were hovering in mid-air.

Yu Menghan's jaw had already dropped straight to the ground at this astonishing sight.

"Let's go check out my new cave abode, Elder Luo," Han Li said as he turned to Luo Jun with a nonchalant smile.

Luo Jun looked at the uprooted plot of spirit farmland and the severely ravaged valley, and he had no idea how to feel about this.

He had thought that at the very most, Han Li would've only chosen one of the plots of spirit farmland, then moved it using some type of treasure or secret technique, and it never occurred to him that he would uproot the entire plot of spirit farmland with the power of his physical body alone!

However, he had authorized Han Li to do as he pleased, so he naturally couldn't say anything now. Thus, he could only give a wry smile as he led the way up the mountain.

Han Li carried the enormous plot of spirit farmland and wandered over Cloudrise Peak for over an hour before finally selecting a cave abode that was situated in a peaceful corner near the peak of the mountain.

Chapter 31: Trade Valley

Han Li casually smashed a giant crater that was around an acre in area into the secluded cave abode, then placed the plot of spirit farmland into it, and Lu Jun couldn't help but burst into raucous laughter upon seeing this.

"Your extraordinary strength has far exceeded my expectations, Fellow Daoist Han! I have truly been humbled!"

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Luo. Now that you've finished examining my abilities, it's time that we discuss some official matters, is it not?" Han Li asked with a hint of a smile on his face.

A sheepish smile appeared on Luo Jun's face upon hearing this, and he cleared his throat in a slightly awkward manner as he replied, "I had no such intentions, Fellow Daoist Han. There's not too much that needs to be said. You don't need to do anything to become a guest elder of our sect, and every year, our sect will assign you 50,000 spirit stones and some pills to support your cultivation.

“However, the pill assignment window for this year has already passed, so you'll have to wait for next year. This is your badge, it contains a map of our sect and some information on all of our sect's peaks. This is this year's spirit stone allotment of 80,000 spirit stones. The additional 30,000 spirit stones are a welcoming gift from Peak Master Nangong."

Luo Jun pulled out a shimmering golden badge and an azure storage bag as he spoke, then offered them to Han Li.

A complex look appeared in Gu Yunyue's eyes as she cast her gaze toward Han Li. The benefits that Luo Jun had just described were normally reserved only for Deity Transformation Stage elders, but given the power that Han Li has displayed, no one could argue that he was unworthy of such treatment.

"Thank you, Elder Luo. By the way, are Sharp Watch Pills allocated yearly by the sect or are there some other avenues through which they can be obtained?" Han Li asked as he accepted the badge and the spirit stones.

"Sharp Watch Pills are occasionally allocated by the sect. They're great for treating injuries, but they don't have much use when it comes to cultivation base advancement. Some disciples will trade them in our sect's internal markets, but most of them are traded very quickly, so they're not easy to obtain," Luo Jun replied.

"It looks like I'll just have to try my luck then," Han Li said with a thoughtful expression.

Luo Jun didn't linger much longer, and he departed with Gu Yunyue and Yu Menghan after exchanging some more small talk with Han Li.

Following Luo Jun's departure, Han Li activated all of the restrictions within the cave abode, then led Liu Le'er on a tour. He arranged a bedroom for her to rest in, then departed from the cave abode.

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li appeared in a valley several kilometers away from Cloudrise Peak.

There was a white stone plaque situated at the entrance of the valley, upon which were engraved the words "Trade Valley" in large red characters. Beneath the plaque was a wide stone street that extended into the valley.

This Trade Valley was none other than the internal market that Luo Jun had referred to earlier, and even before entering the valley, Han Li could already hear the chaotic commotion one would normally expect to hear in a busy market.

Han Li paused momentarily at the entrance of the valley, then continued onward, and by the time he arrived under the plaque, most of the valley was laid out before him.

Most of the streets in the valley sloped upward, and all of the shops were also constructed in a way that followed the terrain of the valley. All types of flags were hanging outside the shops, and it looked no different from a normal market.

At the moment, it was just past noon, and there were countless people entering and exiting the shops in the market, presenting a lively and bustling sight to behold.

Han Li chose a pill shop at random before walking into it, but shortly thereafter, he emerged in an expressionless manner before proceeding to the next shop.

He visited five or six large pill shops in a row, but didn't encounter even a single Sharp Watch Pill. Only in one of the shops was he informed that they had recently received one such pill, but that was two months ago, and it had been traded away on the same day.

After close to half a day, Han Li traversed through almost the entire market, but still had nothing to show for his efforts.

After emerging from yet another pill shop, Han Li didn't continue deeper into the valley. Instead, he made his way toward a secluded corner in an unhurried manner, then suddenly swiveled around before casting a cold gaze toward a nearby tree.

"You've been following me almost the entire time I've been in this valley. Do you have some business with me?"

"Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist. It's all just a misunderstanding."

A gray-robed elderly man emerged from behind the tree before making his way over to Han Li with a sheepish expression.

The man's hair and beard were all completely white, yet he had an extremely youthful, childlike face, presenting a rather peculiar contrast to behold.

Han Li could sense that the man was a Deity Transformation cultivator. "A misunderstanding?"

The elderly man's expression remained unchanged as he calmly explained, "I am Gao Bulin, an elder of Sunset Peak. I just so happened to overhear that you were searching for a Sharp Watch Pill, and that's why I've been following you briefly."

"The Sunset Peak? If I recall correctly, that peak is specifically dedicated to the pill refinement masters of the sect, right? Could it be that you have a Sharp Watch Pill in your possession?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Hehe, I do indeed have a Sharp Watch PIll, and I intend to trade it, but I'll have to see if you have anything that I need," Gao Bulin replied with a smile as he took a glance at the storage bag on Han Li's waist.

"What are you looking for, Elder Gao?" Han Li asked.

"There's no hurry. I still don't even know your name yet, Fellow Daoist," Gao Bulin said, displaying no urgency to proceed with the trade.

"I am Han Li, a guest elder of the Cloudrise Peak. Can we get back to business now?" Han Li asked with a calm expression.

"A guest elder of Cloudrise Peak? You must possess some remarkable abilities, Fellow Daoist. I'm completely unable to discern your cultivation base! But I digress. I am looking for Glacial Yin Water, Blue Crystal Sand, Heavenly River Starstone, or a Lanling Flower or Inkfragrance Herb over 3,000 years old.

“Do you have any of those things, Fellow Daoist Han? If you have any one of them, I'd be more than willing to trade my Sharp Watch Pill to you," Gao Bulin said as he stroked his long beard.

"Surely you jest, Elder Gao. Every single one of those things is extremely rare. If I had those things, I would be asking for far more than just a Sharp Watch Pill," Han Li said.

Gao Bulin's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and a sheepish look appeared on his face.

"I suggest you make some more realistic requests, Fellow Daoist. Otherwise, I'd be willing to purchase the pill from you using spirit stones as well," Han Li continued.

Even though he hadn't found any Sharp Watch Pills thus far, he had managed to sell some of the materials, ingredients, and pills that he had previously obtained for a decent sum of spirit stones. In addition to the spirit stones that Luo Jun had given to him, he had a small fortune at his disposal. Of course, the few top-grade spirit stones that he had obtained weren't being factored into those calculations.

Gao Bulin hesitated momentarily upon hearing this, then conceded, "Alright, in that case, I'll do you a favor and trade my Sharp Watch Pill for spirit stones. I'll take two top-grade spirit stones for my Sharp Watch Pill. What do you say?"

"You're asking for way too much, Elder Gao! Sharp Watch Pills may be quite rare in this market, but even the highest asking price shouldn't exceed 600,000 spirit stones!" Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly with displeasure.

"I don't think I'm asking for too much. After all, you're referring to the prices in our sect's internal market. If a Sharp Watch Pill were to go on auction outside of the sect, it would fetch a far higher price," Gao Bulin countered in an unhurried manner.

Han Li was silent for a moment, then asked, "How about this? I don't have any of the things that you listed earlier, but I have some other precious materials and ingredients in my possession. Are you interested?"

"If you're only referring to some common treasures, then there's no need to bring them out, Fellow Daoist Han. It would be much more convenient to just use spirit stones," Gao Bulin said with a smile.

"I have an Azure Underworld Crystal, a Myriad Yin Spirit Trapping Array Scroll, and a Yin Soul Zoysia. Do any of those things catch your interest?" Han Li asked.

Those were all things that he had found in Lu Ya's storage bag, and they were precious items, but they weren't very useful to him.

A hesitant look appeared on Gao Bulin's face, and only after some contemplation did he reply in a reluctant voice, "I have some use for a Yin Soul Zoysia, but it has to be at least 1,000 years old, and the Sharp Watch Pill is yours if you can throw in an extra 300,000 spirit stones on top of that."

Han Li immediately turned to depart upon hearing this, not hesitating in the slightest.

"Fellow Daoist Han, please wait!"

Gao Bulin's calm facade instantly fell away at the sight of Han Li's sudden departure.

Han Li naturally wasn't serious about leaving, and he willingly obliged, stopping in his tracks. However, instead of making his way back to Gao Bulin, he merely turned around to look at him from where he was.

Gao Bulin hurriedly made his way over to Han Li, then said with a sheepish smile, "Don't be in such a hurry to leave, Fellow Daoist Han, the price is still negotiable. Would you be able to let me see the Yin Soul Zoysia that you have in your possession?"

Han Li didn't waste any time with words as he flipped a hand over to produce a wooden box that was around half a foot in length, then opened the lid of the box by a sliver. Gao Bulin immediately released his spiritual sense to inspect the contents of the box, and a hint of surprise appeared on his face before quickly fading.

Chapter 32: Pill Reversal Art

"You're a lucky man, Fellow Daoist Han. That Yin Soul Zoysia has to be at least 2,300... no, 2,400 years old. It's more than enough to exchange for a Sharp Watch Pill," Gao Bulin said.

"I want two Sharp Watch Pills for this Yin Soul Zoysia," Han Li demanded in an implacable voice.

A wry smile appeared on Gao Bulin's face upon hearing this. "But I only have one of these pills, Fellow Daoist Han."

"Perhaps I would believe you if you were an elder from another sect, but you can't expect to convince me that an elder of the Sunset Peak like yourself is unable to offer me at least two Sharp Watch Pills. If it's too much to ask, then I can afford to keep waiting. I'm sure I'll find a seller eventually," Han Li said in an unhurried voice.

Gao Bulin's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and this time, he was truly grappling with a dilemma. After pondering the situation for quite some time, he finally conceded, "Deal!"

Han Li accepted a white jade box that was handed to him by Gao Bulin, and a pleased smile appeared on his face after he inspected the box's contents with his spiritual sense.

The scent of different medicinal ingredients emanating from Gao Bulin's body served as confirmation to Han Li that he was indeed a pill refinement master.

For others, a spirit medicine that was over 2,000 years old was perhaps extremely rare, but it naturally wasn't much in Han Li's eyes, and it was far less useful to him than these two Sharp Watch Pills.

Gao Bulin brought the wooden box under his nose and took a long whiff, then exhaled with a satisfied expression before gleefully stowing the box away in his storage bag. He then invited Han Li to visit him at Sunset Peak when he had some free time before quickly departing.

After completing the trade, Han Li didn't immediately leave the market. Instead, he continued to make his way through the valley, trading most of his spirit stones for high-grade pills of a similar caliber to the Sharp Watch Pill, and only after that did he depart from the valley before traveling back to the Cloudrise Peak.

After returning to his cave abode, Han Li saw Liu Le'er sitting on her own in the hall, staring absentmindedly into the distance with her chin resting on her hand.

"What are you thinking about, Le'er?" Han Li asked as he made his way over to Liu Le'er before taking a seat in front of her.

Only then did she notice that Han Li had returned, and she immediately called out in an elated voice, "Brother Rock!"

"Why are you daydreaming here on your own?" Han Li asked with a gentle smile.

"I was just thinking to myself that ever since I met you, my life has felt like a dream," Liu Le'er replied with a serious expression.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this before an amused smile appeared on his face.

"If this is a dream, then I really hope that I never wake up. Aside from mama and dada, you treat me better than anyone else in the world. I want to be by your side forever, Brother Rock," Liu Le'er said in a low voice as tears began to well up in her eyes.

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then suddenly raised his hand and joined his index and middle fingers together before pressing them against Liu Le'er's glabella.

Liu Le'er was quite startled by this, but she didn't recoil.

"Close your eyes," Han Li instructed in a gentle voice.

Liu Le'er immediately did as she was told without any hesitation, closing her eyes tightly.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he also closed his eyes before chanting an incantation.

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li opened his eyes.

At this point, Liu Le'er's face had already turned slightly pale, and there was a faint sheen of sweat on her forehead.

Han Li withdrew his fingers as he said, "Alright, you can open your eyes now."

Liu Le'er's eyelashes fluttered slightly as she slowly opened her eyes, then cast a puzzled gaze toward Han Li.

"I just implanted a cultivation art by the name of 'Illusory Spirit Cicada Transformation' into your mind. I picked up this high-grade demonic cultivation art some years ago, and it's perfect for a demonic fox like yourself to cultivate," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Liu Le'er closed her eyes to sense the newly implanted cultivation art in her mind upon hearing this, but she still looked rather perplexed.

"I'll continue to do my best to protect you, but if I'm not by your side for some reason, you need to be able to protect yourself as well. At the very least, you need to be able to keep yourself safe until I get to you," Han Li explained with a serious expression.

Liu Le'er thought about this momentarily before nodding in response with a serious look of her own. "I'll be sure to work hard on this cultivation art!"

Han Li gave a pleased nod in response.

……

In a certain conference hall on Cloudrise Peak, Luo Jun extended a respectful bow toward the scholarly-robed middle-aged man sitting on the main seat.

"As expected, Han Li really is a high-grade body cultivator. I've already arranged a place for him to stay, and no one from the other peaks has been made aware of his arrival. As for Martial Niece Gu, I've already issued a reward to her as you instructed, and she's been told not to tell anyone about Han Li's exploits in slaying that Deity Transformation Stage elder of the Heavenly Ghost Sect."

Peak Master Nangong nodded in response. "Good. The fact that he was able to slay a Deity Transformation cultivator as a Nascent Soul cultivator indicates that he must possess an exceptionally powerful body. I'm sure he's going to be extremely useful to our peak in the future. Make sure to look after him and satisfy any requests he may have as much as possible."

"Yes," Luo Jun replied.

"You can go now," Peak Master Nangong said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

Luo Jun extended a respectful bow before departing.

Following Luo Jun's departure, Peak Master Nangong sat in silence with his eyes closed for a short while, then rose to his feet and made his way toward the back of the hall.

……

Han Li was naturally oblivious to the conversation that had taken place between Luo Jun and Peak Master Nangong.

At this moment, he was seated with his legs crossed in a secret chamber of his cave abode, and there were around a dozen containers, such as jade vials and jade boxes, placed on the table in front of him.

He was holding a small red vial, and he pulled out the stopper before tipping out a crimson pill. A strong medicinal aroma immediately spread through the air, and after a brief inspection, Han Li took the pill before closing his eyes to examine his internal condition.

Moments later, he reopened his eyes with tightly furrowed brows.

The red pill was comparable in caliber to the Sharp Watch Pill, but it had no effect on him whatsoever.

Han Li wasn't surprised by this, and he picked up a second vial before tipping out a yellow pill that he promptly swallowed.

The pill melted as soon as it entered his stomach, but there still wasn't any magic power generated.

A short while later, Han Li opened his eyes before picking up a third vial.

Soon, most of the pills on the table had already been tested, but none of them had proven to be effective, and there was only a purple jade box and an azure porcelain vial left on the table.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face, and he was beginning to feel rather frustrated.

It seemed that finding pills that would have an effect on him was going to be far more difficult than he had imagined. However, the good thing was that he was now part of a major sect, and based on his current understanding of the Spirit Domain Realm, this was a realm with an abundance of cultivation resources, so as long as he put his mind to it, there was surely progress to be made.

With that in mind, he picked up the purple jade box from the table, then plucked out a gray pill between his fingers before tipping his head back to swallow it.

This time, a hint of elation finally appeared on Han Li's face.

He could feel wisps of magic power emerging from the pill before circulating throughout his meridians and entering his dantian, slightly increasing his magic power reserves.

The gray pill was far less effective than the Sharp Watch Pill, but it was still very encouraging that he had managed to find another pill that he could use for magic power restoration.

As for the pills in the azure porcelain vial, sure enough, they were also completely ineffective.

Han Li exhaled as he pulled out another gray pill from the purple jade box and held it at the center of his palm.

This pill was called the Dark Cloud Pill, and it was supposed to have restorative properties, but it was more suited to cultivators using water-attribute cultivation arts, and its intended effect was quite different from that of the Sharp Watch Pill.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li suddenly rose to his feet, then exited the secret chamber before making his way outside.

He stopped while passing by Liu Le'er's bedroom, and even through the door, he could still sense the spiritual qi surging inside the room, clearly indicating that she was cultivating diligently.

He gave a pleased nod before continuing onward, quickly arriving in the pill refinement room.

This pill refinement room wasn't very large, only around 40 to 50 feet in size, and the ground was a dark azure color. At the center of the room was a cylindrical mound that was around half a foot tall, upon which was engraved an array consisting of many dark red patterns.

At the center of the array was a black hole that contained a lit flame, and a scorching aura was emanating from within it.

A pill furnace that was around half the height of a grown human was sitting on the mound, giving off wisps of spiritual qi.

Han Li swept his gaze over the room, then took a seat on a cushion beside the pill furnace before releasing an incantation seal with a wave of his hand.

The red array immediately lit up, following which a burst of bright red groundfire erupted out of the black hole to envelop the pill furnace.

First, Han Li cleaned the inside and outside of the pill furnace in an expert fashion. He then flipped a hand over to produce the Dark Cloud PIll before tossing it into the pill furnace.

The groundfire began to move at his behest as he made a hand seal, splitting up into eight independent flames that surged into the pill furnace, and soon, a strong medicinal scent began to waft through the air.

As Han Li continued to make hand seals, the medicinal aroma suddenly became less pronounced.

His expression remained unchanged as he continued to go through a series of hand seals, and close to an hour passed by in the blink of an eye.

At this point, the medicinal aroma wafting out from the furnace had almost completely faded, and it had been replaced by another aroma that seemed to be a rather chaotic culmination of many types of different scents.

All of a sudden, Han Li stopped what he was doing as he released a final incantation seal, and the flame beneath the furnace was instantly snuffed out.

He swept a hand through the air to remove the furnace's lid, and the Dark Cloud PIll inside had already disappeared, having been replaced by a small mound of colorful powder.

Han Li inspected the small mound of powder briefly, then carefully released a burst of green light that carried the powder out of the furnace.

The green light shuddered slightly, and countless thin threads that resembled thousands upon thousands of tiny hands reached into the powder.

Soon, the small mound of powder was split up into around a dozen portions, each of which was of a different color.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then carefully split the powder up into around a dozen small jade boxes that he had already prepared in advance.

The secret technique that he had just used was called the Pill Reversal Art, and it was quite a rare secret technique that he had obtained by chance back in the Spirit Realm. The secret technique allowed him to reverse-refine and break down pills.

The creator of the secret technique had tried to use it to break down other people's pills in order to extrapolate the refinement methods for those pills.

Unfortunately, he failed in the end. The Pill Reversal Art ultimately still had its limits, and it was only able to help one identify the ingredients used in a pill, but was unable to yield the actual pill refinement method.

Han Li had been quite intrigued by the secret technique, and he was a pill refinement master himself, so he decided to record it, but this was the first time that he had ever used it.

Thankfully, the Dark Cloud Pill was only a Nascent Soul Stage pill, so it wasn't of a very high caliber. Otherwise, he may not have been able to successfully break it down on the first try.

Chapter 33: Quintessential Purple Qi

Han Li set the jade boxes containing the different powders aside, then swept a hand through the air to release another incantation seal, activating the pill furnace array once again. After that, he pulled out another pill, and this one was a Sharp Watch Pill.

After a brief hesitation, he tossed the Sharp Watch Pill into the pill furnace and unleashed the Pill Refinement Art again.

Close to an hour later, the Sharp Watch Pill was also split up into around a dozen different types of ingredients that were stored into jade boxes.

He placed the ingredients of the two pills together before conducting a thorough examination.

A short while later, a faint smile appeared on his face.

Most of the ingredients used for these two pills were completely different, but there was a type of blue crystalline powder used in both pills that was identical in both color and form, so it was clear that it was the same type of ingredient.

However, the Sharp Watch Pill contained much more of this ingredient than the Dark Cloud Pill did.

Both types of pills had an effect on him, and while the blue powder wasn't necessarily confirmed to be the sole effective ingredient, it was definitely something worth exploring.

Han Li gently dipped the tip of his finger into the blue powder before taking a whiff, then placed it into his mouth for a taste, and his brows slowly furrowed slightly.

Ever since the beginning, his cultivation journey had been closely intertwined with the art of pill refinement. Regardless of whether it was in the Human Realm or the Spirit Realm, he was at least somewhat familiar with all of the pill refinement ingredients that the two realms had to offer, and he even had some knowledge of the pill refinement ingredients of other realms. However, he had no idea what this blue powder was.

Perhaps this is something unique to the Spirit Domain Realm?

After pondering the issue to himself for a while, Han Li suddenly rose to his feet before promptly departing from his cave abode.

At this point, it was already quite dark outside.

Azure light flashed from his body as he flew through the air, and moments later, he descended in front of a certain cave abode on Sunset Peak several dozen kilometers away.

The cave abode was situated in quite a secluded location with barely anyone around.

Han Li quickly inspected his surroundings, then made his way to the entrance of the cave abode before flipping a hand over to produce a voice transmission talisman, which he whispered a message into before sending it flying through the air.

The voice transmission talisman flew into the cave abode as a streak of white light, and moments later, the gates of the cave abode swung open amid a burst of rumbling.

"Please pardon my intrusion, Elder Gao," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Not at all! I didn't think we would meet again so soon, Fellow Daoist Han. Please come in." Gao Bulin emerged with a wide smile before inviting Han Li into the cave abode.

Gao Bulin's cave abode was clearly larger than Han Li's, but the furnishings were quite simple, and a strong medicinal aroma was wafting throughout the entire cave abode.

"I won't waste any more of your time than necessary, Elder Gao. I came here because I wanted to ask you something," Han Li said in a direct and straightforward manner after taking a seat.

Gao Bulin faltered slightly upon hearing this, then prompted, "Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a jade box that contained the blue powder, then offered it to Gao Bulin. "Do you recognize this ingredient, Elder Gao?"

Gao Bulin accepted the jade box before taking a close look. He then dipped a fingertip into the powder before placing it onto his tongue, and he raised an eyebrow as he took a meaningful look at Han Li.

"Looks like I came to the right person," Han Li said with a smile.

"You did indeed make the right decision to come to me. However..." Gao Bulin's voice trailed off here as a suggestive smile appeared on his face.

Han Li immediately flipped a hand over to produce a high-grade spirit stone, which he tossed at Gao Bulin.

Gao Bulin gleefully accepted the spirit stone, and his smile grew even wider as he elaborated, "This is powderized Cloud Crane Herb. Upon reaching a certain age, the Cloud Crane Herb is used as one of the main ingredients for several types of high-grade pills produced in our sect, and it's an extremely rare ingredient.

“On top of that, this powder seems to have been processed through certain means, and I was only just barely able to identify it thanks to the familiarity with all types of ingredients that I've developed through years of pill refinement."

Han Li nodded in response, then asked, "I see... Would you be able to tell me about the medicinal properties of this Cloud Crane Herb?"

A suggestive grin reappeared on Gao Bulin's face, as he gave Han Li a sly look.

Han Li tossed another high-grade spirit stone at him.

Gao Bulin happily accepted the spirit stone, then said, "The Cloud Crane Herb is also known as the Chameleon Herb. The herb turns white at 100 years old, blue at 1,000 years old, red at 3,000 years old, dark red at 10,000 years old, and purplish-red at 30,000 years old or above.

“The most remarkable property of this herb is its ability to absorb the energy of the rising sun and produce a wisp of quintessential purple qi upon reaching 100 years old. Not only is quintessential purple qi something that's absolutely required for cultivating several types of incredibly powerful cultivation arts, it can also be directly converted into quintessential spiritual power, which can cleanse one's essence and enhance one's constitution.

“The older a Cloud Crane Herb is, the purer the quintessential purple qi it contains becomes, and effects of that quintessential purple qi naturally become more incredible as a result."

"Where can this Cloud Crane Herb be found?" Han Li asked.

"This herb can only grow in a set of very specific conditions, and as far as I'm aware, it can only be found in a few places, virtually all of which are under the control of the major sects in our realm. At the moment, almost all specimens over 1,000 years old are in the possession of the major sects, and they're almost impossible to find outside of that," Gao Bulin replied.

After hearing what Gao Bulin had to say, Han Li had already gotten the answers that he wanted. It was most likely the case that this quintessential purple qi was the key to his magic power recovery.

"Aside from the Sharp Watch Pill, what other pills are refined using the Cloud Crane Herb?" Han Li asked.

This time, Gao Bulin didn't ask for any further financial compensation as he replied, "Aside from the Sharp Watch Pill, small amounts of the herb are also used in the Dark Cloud Pill. In addition to that, the Spirit Nurturing Pill and the Void Origin Pill also contain small amounts of Cloud Crane Herb of a young age, but the quintessential purple qi that those pills contain is virtually negligible."

After parting ways with Gao Bulin, Han Li made another trip to the Trade Valley and spent a top-grade spirit stone to purchase a few of each of the pills that Gao Bulin mentioned. In addition to that, he also purchased several Cloud Crane Herbs in the hundreds of years old before returning to Cloudrise Peak.

Inside the secret chamber of his cave abode, Han Li was seated on a cushion , and placed in front of him were the pills and the Cloud Crane Herbs that he had just purchased.

He opened a white porcelain vial before tipping out a Dark Cloud Pill that he promptly swallowed. A surge of warmth quickly rose up from his dantian as traces of spiritual power were released by the pill, gradually converting into magic power that was stored in his body.

This was naturally an encouraging development, and he picked up a Cloud Crane Herb before placing it into his mouth, then chewed a few times before also swallowing it.

Roughly 10 minutes later, his dantian began to warm up again, and wisps of magic power flowed into his dantian before being stored again.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he could finally confirm that this quintessential purple qi was indeed the key to his magic power recovery.

After a day and a night, he had devoured most of the pills and Cloud Crane Herbs that he had purchased, and as a result, his cultivation base had recovered to the late-Nascent Soul Stage.

He was ecstatic to see this, yet right as he was about to devour all of the remaining pills, his expression suddenly stiffened slightly.

The medicinal power in his body that was still yet to be converted was finally converted into magic power that converged toward his dantian, but his dantian was already like a filled tank of water, unable to hold any more magic power.

All he could do was watch as the superfluous magic power lingered momentarily in his dantian, then dissipated into nothingness.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh, and he knew that this most likely had something to do with the condition that his nascent soul was in. In his current state, any further consumption of pills was most likely only going to be a waste.

He would have to wait for his physical body and spiritual sense to recover further before he could investigate the cause behind the condition that his nascent soul was in.

At the moment, he was unable to increase his magic power through cultivation, and he could only recover to the late-Nascent Soul Stage through the use of pills, so his top priority now was to enhance the rate of recovery of his physical body and spiritual sense.

With that in mind, he was rather unsure of how to proceed, and his brows furrowed slightly as he fell into deep thought.

Moments later, a thought suddenly seemed to have occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to produce the guest elder badge that he had received from Luo Jun.

He injected his spiritual sense into the badge, and a map of the Cold Flame Sect that was formed by golden lines of light appeared before his eyes.

His gaze roamed over the map for a moment before finally settling on a building on the Sage Gathering Peak, which was annotated with the words "Scripture Library" in small text.

Chapter 34: Theft

Halfway up the Cloudrise Peak, a young disciple in a white robe was making his way up the mountain path.

Right as he raised his foot and was about to tread onto the next step, a blur suddenly flashed through his eyes, and he was instantly rooted to the spot, while his spiritual sense had also become murky and indistinct.

Immediately thereafter, an imposing young man appeared beside him, and it was none other than Han Li.

"Tell me about the scripture library," Han Li said in a peculiar voice as he looked into the young man's eyes with blue light flashing in his own eyes.

The white-robed disciple's eyes were completely glazed over, giving him a dazed appearance as he replied, "The scripture library is situated on the Sage Gathering Peak, and it's split up into the inner library and the outer library. The outer library is open to all disciples and elders, while the inner library is accessible only to inner court disciples and elders."

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but a thoughtful look had appeared in his eyes.

The scripture library was a vital location in the sect, so it was undoubtedly guarded extremely tightly.

In order to exchange for resources from the library, not only did the disciples and elders of the sect have to issue large sums of spirit stones, they also had sect contribution points deducted as well.

Sect contribution points were a measure of the degree of contributions that inner sect disciples and elders had made to the sect, and they were generally earned by completing missions assigned by the sect. The more difficult a mission was, the greater the number of contribution points awarded. Without sufficient time to accumulate contribution points, it was impossible to earn enough to exchange for high-grade cultivation arts and secret techniques.

As a result, many people tried to pursue shortcuts.

There had been no lack of vagrant cultivators with ulterior motives who had agreed to become guest elders of the Cold Flame Sect in order to sneak into the scripture library to steal cultivation resources, but all of them had been caught with no exceptions, and the fate that they suffered was not enviable, to say the least.

The defenses of the scripture library were watertight, and there were no holes to be exploited.

According to the white-robed disciple, there were Spatial Tempering Stage elders stationed in the scripture library at all times, and the establishment was patrolled at all hours of the day. There were also countless powerful restrictions set up there, making it impossible for the average cultivator to even get close to the scripture library.

Han Li considered the information that he had received for a moment, then tapped a finger against the white-robed disciple's glabella before vanishing on the spot in a wraith-like manner.

At this point, the white-robed disciple's foot had been suspended in mid-air for quite some time, and only now did he take the step.

As a result, he almost stumbled and fell onto his face.

After steadying himself, he massaged his slightly numb calf, then looked around with a confused expression before shaking his head in a perplexed manner and continuing up the mountain.

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li appeared on the Sage Gathering Peak.

He stood at the foot of a huge cypress tree as he cast his gaze toward a two-story tall pavilion in the distance.

The pavilion was roughly 90 feet tall with eight faces forming a regular octagon, but there was only a single entrance, and that was on the south-facing wall.

There were many types of complex defensive arrays engraved onto the roof of the pavilion, and two groups of patrolling cultivators were constantly surveying the area.

After observing for some time, a contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face, and he abruptly vanished from the spot in a flash.

That night.

There was a large bluestone hall situated in a valley deep in the Cold Flame Sect, and the area was being patrolled by as many as seven or eight groups of disciples. All of the groups were led by Deity Transformation cultivators, so it was clear that this was an extremely important place.

One of the patrol groups flew silently through the entrance of the valley. The group was led by an azure-robed man, and he was yawning in a rather weary manner.

Right at this moment, another patrol group flew past several hundred feet away, traveling in a different direction.

The azure-robed man pursed his lips in discontent upon seeing this.

The Heavenly Talisman Hall was an extremely important location in the Cold Flame Sect, but in his opinion, it was completely overkill to have so many disciples patrolling the area at night.

Not only was the all situated in a very secretive location, it was entirely enshrouded under a powerful protective array, so it was preposterous to think that anyone could infiltrate the area.

Of course, he didn't dare to voice these objections. Instead, he made a voice transmission to the disciples behind him, telling them to be on their guard as they flew into the valley.

Right at this moment, a thunderous boom suddenly rang out from a hall not far away from the azure-robed man, followed by a flash of purple lightning before everything immediately fell silent again.

The azure-robed man faltered slightly upon seeing this.

"Who's there?"

"Someone's breaking into the Heavenly Talisman Hall!"

Cries of alarm rang out from the disciples behind the azure-robed man, and at this point, the azure-robed man himself had also returned to his senses, flying down as quickly as he could to arrive outside the hall in the blink of an eye.

"Who goes there? Surrender yourself right now!" the azure-robed man roared as he grabbed onto a treasure with one hand while sweeping his other hand through the air, upon which the disciples behind him immediately dispersed to surround the hall.

The other disciples also arrived on the scene in a flash, and soon, all of the patrolling teams were assembled, amounting to over 100 cultivators that surrounded the hall in a watertight encirclement.

The interior of the hall remained completely dark and silent.

All of the halls here were enshrouded under restrictions, keeping all spiritual sense at bay.

The leaders of the patrol groups exchanged a series of uncertain glances with one another, unsure of whether they should rush in or not.

As patrolling disciples, they had no right to set foot into the hall.

"What's going on here?" A streak of white light shot forth before arriving outside the hall, revealing itself to be a white-haired elderly man.

"Master Fan, someone's broken into the Heavenly Talisman Hall! We're considering entering the hall to capture the perpetrator, but according to the rules, we don't have the right to enter the hall," one of the patrol groups' leaders hurriedly reported.

The white-haired elderly man was furious to hear this. "Are you an idiot? Now's not the time to be following rules! Hurry up and go in!"

He immediately rushed into the hall as he spoke, and most of the patrol groups' leaders quickly rushed in with him, but two of them remained outside.

Upon reaching the entrance of the hall, the white-haired elderly man was surprised to find that the restrictions on the gate were completely unharmed.

This was quite a perplexing sight, but there was no time for him to ponder the situation, and he immediately pulled out a badge, which released a burst of white light that fell upon the gate.

The gate flashed momentarily before swinging open.

Everyone immediately rushed into the hall, and the white-haired elderly man released an incantation seal, upon which dazzling white light instantly appeared all over the hall, illuminating the entire scene.

The layout of the hall was very simple with only around a dozen white jade shelves in the room, so it was a simple matter to take stock of what, if anything, had been lost.

There were a few black scorch marks on the ground, but there wasn't a single person to be seen.

Could it be that the perpetrator has already gotten away?

The leaders of the patrol groups couldn't help but exchange a few bewildered glances.

The azure-robed man was also in the hall, and his eyes were wide with incredulity.

He had been right beside the hall at the time of the incident, and his gaze had been focused on the building the entire time, so it was downright unfathomable to him how the perpetrator could've possibly escaped.

All of a sudden, the white-haired elderly man rushed over to one of the white jade shelves, and his face paled significantly. "Argh! The Heavenly Shadow Rock and the Moon Gazing Herb are all gone!"

All of these white jade shelves were laden with ingredients and materials, and all of them were enshrouded under restrictions, but the restrictions near two of the shelves had been broken, and those shelves were missing a large number of items.

"The Flowing Billow Wood and Ironheart Feather have been taken as well!" the elderly man cried as he rushed over to another shelf with a distraught expression.

The leaders of the patrol groups also wore grim expressions.

"Conduct a search! Deploy all of the patrolling disciples! We must capture the perpetrator!" the white-haired elderly man roared in a furious voice.

The theft that had taken place in the Heavenly Talisman Hall stirred up a massive commotion in the Cold Flame Sect, and countless night patrol disciples were deployed to search for the perpetrator.

The search wore on all the way until the morning, upon which many outer court disciples were also woken up and ordered to join the hunt.

An exhaustive search was conducted throughout the entire Spirit Flame Mountain Range, but not a single trace of the perpetrator was found.

The higher-ups of the sect were quickly alerted to the incident, and a late-Spatial Tempering Stage elder who was adept at tracking was sent to the Heavenly Talisman Hall. After an investigation, he concluded that the perpetrator had fled the scene using some type of lightning teleportation array, and he hadn't left any traces behind, making it impossible to track him down.

The late-Spatial Tempering Stage elder was powerless to do anything, and there was no way that any of the Body Integration Stage grand elders would get involved with something so minor, so Master Fan of the Heavenly Talisman Hall was forced to call off the hunt.

Even though the incident seemed to have blown over on the surface, there was naturally no way that the sect would let something like this pass so easily.

There were no signs of a break-in in the protective array around the entire Spirit Flame Mountain Range, so the perpetrator had to still be somewhere in the mountain range, and the Cold Flame Sect had sent out powerful cultivators to continue the hunt in secret.

In the wake of such an incident, the defenses in all parts of the Cold Flame Sect were bolstered by severalfold.

Chapter 35: Getting Away with It

Three days passed by in the blink of an eye.

That night, at the scripture library of the Cold Flame Sect.

Ever since the Heavenly Talisman Hall incident, the number of people patrolling the scripture library had been doubled.

In a dense forest several thousand feet away from the pavilion, an indistinct silver figure appeared. Under the cover of the night, it was impossible to make out the figure's facial features.

The figure raised his head to look up at the octagonal pavilion that was the scripture library, and a moment later, he flipped a hand over to produce a light purple talisman, which he adhered to his own body.

The purple talisman instantly exploded silently into several indistinct runes that resembled tadpoles, revolving around the figure momentarily before vanishing into his body.

A burst of purple mist abruptly rose up around the figure, instantly devouring him and causing him to vanish on the spot.

The figure naturally hadn't actually disappeared. Instead, he had taken on an insubstantial form as he drifted directly toward the scripture library, paying no heed at all to the patrols in the area.

The patrols were constantly surveying their surroundings, and their spiritual sense was also sweeping through the area incessantly, but they completely failed to detect the figure.

Before long, the figure had already reached the entrance of the scripture library.

It was quite late at night, and the scripture library's doors were already shut. The wide stone doors of the scripture library were flashing occasionally, clearly indicating that there were restrictions applied to them.

The figure chanted an incantation as he made a hand seal, then opened his mouth to release a cloud of barely visible azure qi that drifted into the doors.

If the cloud of azure qi were to be enlarged by several hundredfold, one would be able to see that it was comprised of countless tiny runes. These tiny runes instantly seeped into the restrictions on the stone doors upon contact, and a large hole seemed to have been corroded into the restrictions, allowing the figure to fly through in a stealthy manner.

Without the restrictions in place, the stone doors posed no obstacle at all, and the figure flew through in a flash.

The restrictions on the doors flashed ever so slightly before instantly returning to normal.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the patrolling cultivators outside had no idea that anything was amiss.

The figure entered the scripture library, arriving in a circular hall.

The hall was extremely large, roughly 200 to 300 feet in size, and there were around a dozen paths leading deeper into the scripture library from the hall.

At the very end of the hall was a winding black staircase that led upward.

The figure quickly inspected his surroundings, then flew silently toward one of the paths.

The path wasn't very long, and he quickly arrived at the end, reaching a stone chamber.

Just like the doors of the scripture library, the doors of this stone chamber were also bolstered by a white restriction.

Above the door was a white jade plaque, upon which were inscribed the words "Cultivation Arts".

A hint of elation flashed through the figure's eyes upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a cloud of azure qi. Once again, the azure qi corroded a large hole into the white restriction, allowing the figure to fly through without any impediment.

Beyond the stone door was a huge stone chamber that housed hundreds of bookshelves, every single one of which was enshrouded under a red light barrier.

All of the bookshelves were split up into several grids, and each grid contained a jade slip.

There were labels beside each grid denoting the cultivation art contained in the jade slip that was stored in the grid.

The figure casually made his way over one of the bookshelves, then opened his mouth to release a burst of azure qi that corroded a large hole into the red light barrier around the bookshelf. After that, he drew several jade slips into his grasp with a wave of his hand, then injected his spiritual sense into them.

Moments later, his brows furrowed slightly as he casually tossed the jade slips back onto the bookshelf.

The jade slips contained various Core Formation and Nascent Soul Stage cultivation arts, but none of them seemed to have caught the figure's fancy.

The figure continued to make his way through the stone chamber. Soon, he had examined every single one of the jade slips on the bookshelves, and he shook his head in a display of disappointment.

He immediately departed without any hesitation, quickly passing through the stone door before returning to the same hall from before.

From there, he went down another path, and at the end of that path was yet another stone chamber.

There was another plaque above this chamber, and this plaque read "Arts".

The figure quickly dispelled the restrictions on the door of this stone chamber before entering.

A short while later, he returned once again before going down a third path.

Over two hours passed by in the blink of an eye, and all of the dozen or so paths had been explored by the figure, but his brows were still tightly furrowed, indicating that he hadn't found what he was looking for.

The figure drifted over to the black staircase at the very end of the hall, and after taking a glance upward, he slowly flew up the staircase.

The staircase wasn't very long, and he quickly reached the top, upon which he arrived before a huge stone door that was several dozen feet wide.

There was a figure seated with their legs crossed on each side of the door.

The one on the left was a portly man wearing a purple kasaya, and he seemed to be a monk. As for the figure on the right, he was a tall and thin man with a sickly, yellow complexion.

Neither of them had a particularly remarkable physical appearance, but the vast auras that they were giving off indicated that they were both Spatial Tempering cultivators.

The two of them were meditating with their eyes closed, completely oblivious to the fact that there was an intruder present.

The figure took a glance at the pair of Spatial Tempering cultivators, then quickly directed his gaze toward the stone door behind them.

Light rippled like water over the surface of the stone door, giving off colorful refractions, and it was clear just from a glance that this restriction was far more powerful than the ones on all of the other stone chambers.

Given the context clues, the inner library of the scripture library was most likely beyond this stone door. The inner library was home to the Cold Flame Sect's best cultivation resources, and it seemed that it was not going to be an easy task to break through this restriction.

The figure's eyes narrowed slightly as he waited for a moment, then began to advance again, arriving directly in front of the stone door, where he was less than 10 feet away from the two Spatial Tempering cultivators.

Right at this moment, the portly monk on the left raised an eyebrow, and he opened his eyes before quickly inspecting his surroundings.

"What is it, Brother Lingxi?" the thin man on the right asked as he also opened his eyes.

"Nothing," the portly monk murmured in response as he turned back to take a glance at the door of the inner library.

He hadn't actually detected anything substantial. Instead, he had felt something rather vague and indescribable, and that feeling had stemmed from a certain secret technique that he had cultivated in the past.

However, the success rate of this secret technique was quite low, and given all of the restrictions imposed on this place and the fact that there were two Spatial Tempering cultivators constantly stationed here, it was extremely implausible that anyone would've been able to infiltrate the inner library without being detected. In fact, even a Grand Ascension Stage being would've most likely struggled to pull off such a feat.

With that in mind, the monk slowly closed his eyes again.

The thin man merely brushed it off as a false alarm upon seeing this, and he also closed his eyes to meditate.

Throughout this process, the figure remained completely still on the spot, and only after the two Spatial Tempering cultivators had closed their eyes again did he release a powerful burst of spiritual sense that quickly encompassed the entire door, forming a protective barrier.

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a burst of azure qi that fell upon the rippling restriction on the door.

The restriction immediately began to shimmer and warp as if it were resisting the azure qi, and it was releasing magic power fluctuations in the process, but the two Spatial Tempering cultivators were completely oblivious to this outside the spiritual sense barrier.

The figure made a hand seal, and the azure qi instantly began to expand and shrink, constantly changing forms to combat the rippling restriction. As a result, an area that was around five feet in size was opened up at the center of the restriction.

The figure immediately took advantage of the opening, flying into the stone door in a flash.

The process seemed to have been a complex and convoluted one, but in reality, it had only taken one or two seconds from the moment he broke through the restriction to the instant that he flew through the stone door, and only after that did the spiritual sense barrier silently dissipate.

The portly monk's eyebrows twitched slightly, and he opened his eyes again before quickly turning his gaze toward the stone door of the inner library.

The restriction on the surface of the stone door was rippling incessantly, and it wasn't displaying any signs of abnormality.

However, even though the sense of foreboding that had just welled up in his heart had only appeared for a flash before vanishing, it still planted a seed of doubt in his heart.

"Did you notice something, Brother Lingxi?"

At this point, his companion seemed to have also noticed that something wasn't quite right, and hurriedly rose to his feet, turning back to take a glance at the stone door, then closed his eyes again to release his enormous spiritual sense throughout the entire area.

"Did you sense anything just now, Brother Qingtao?" the portly monk asked as he made his way over to the stone door before conducting a careful inspection.

The thin man opened his eyes, then shook his head as he replied, "Surely it's nothing unless someone was able to travel hundreds of kilometers away from the scripture library in just two or three seconds, or they were able to break through this Glazed Dark Water Array set up by Patriarch Cold Flame to access the inner library."

He hadn't managed to catch anything with his spiritual sense just now.

"Neither of those options sound possible. It must've just been my imagination," the portly monk said with a wry smile.

Even for the Grand Ascension Stage supreme elder of the Cold Flame Sect, it would've been rather implausible for them to break through the Glazed Dark Water Array before restoring it to its original condition in just two or three seconds.

Chapter 36: Theft

While the two Spatial Tempering cultivators were still speculating about what was happening, the figure had already appeared in a black hall.

The hall wasn't very large, only around 200 to 300 feet in size, and there was a thick white jade pillar standing at its center. There were countless runes inscribed upon the surface of the stone pillar, and gentle yellow light was radiating from the top of the pillar, forming a dome-shaped yellow light barrier that encompassed a certain area.

Around a dozen red stone cabinets could be seen within that area, but it was impossible to see what was inside the cabinets, giving them a rather mysterious air.

The figure remained on the spot as he carefully inspected the yellow light barrier up ahead with blue light flashing in his eyes.

Moments later, he swept a hand through the air, releasing dozens of bursts of black light, which were quickly revealed to be a series of black array flags that landed around the yellow barrier in an orderly fashion.

Immediately thereafter, he made a hand seal, and pillars of black light erupted out of the array flags before coming together in mid-air, forming an even larger black light barrier that completely encompassed the entire yellow barrier beneath it.

The yellow light barrier already took up close to half of the space within the hall, and the black light barrier encompassed virtually the entire hall.

The figure then opened his mouth to release a burst of azure qi that landed upon the yellow light barrier, attempting to bypass it just as he had done with all of the previous restrictions.

However, in an unexpected turn of events, the azure qi had only just corroded a palm-sized hole into the light barrier when the surface of the light barrier suddenly began to glow brightly, releasing countless bursts of yellow light that enveloped the cloud of azure qi.

At the same time, the runes on the white jade pillar at the center of the light barrier lit up in unison, and the yellow light barrier flashed brightly as countless dazzling threads of yellow light appeared, wrapping themselves around the cloud of azure qi before constricting viciously.

The azure qi was instantly sliced into countless shreds that quickly dissipated, following which the yellow light also receded, and the hole in the light barrier sealed over again.

The figure's expression remained completely unchanged upon seeing this, seemingly not very surprised by this outcome. After scrutinizing the white jade pillar for some time, he flipped a hand over to produce around a dozen more array flags of different colors.

With a casual flick of his wrist, all of the array flags spread through the area, hovering in mid-air to form a strange ovular array that seemed to be completely random and erratic, but there was far more to the array than met the eye.

As the figure continued to cycle through a series of hand seals, black light flashed from his hands incessantly, and the dozen or so array flags also began to glow with light of different colors as they struck the yellow light barrier like a series of javelins, driving their way in like nails to encircle an area that was around 10 feet in size.

The surface of the yellow light barrier flashed wildly as it resisted the advance of the array flags, and at the same time, a burst of powerful magic power fluctuations surged through the air. However, these fluctuations would instantly vanish as soon as they made contact with the black light barrier, unable to spread any further beyond that.

The figure chanted a complex incantation, and the dozen or so array flags flashed brightly as they sped up drastically, finally completely embedding themselves into the light barrier.

In the next instant, the yellow light on the surface of the light barrier in the section encircled within the array flags quickly dimmed.

The figure immediately released another burst of azure qi out of his mouth, and this time, the weakened light barrier was unable to offer any resistance, and most of it was eroded away in the blink of an eye.

However, the runes on the white jade pillar suddenly began to flash brightly, and the rest of the yellow light barrier outside the encircled area also glowed with dazzling radiance. An enormous outpouring of yellow light emerged, surging toward the area encircled by the array flags like a violent wave, but the array flags managed to keep the turbulent yellow light firmly at bay.

Fierce magic power fluctuations proliferated through the air, only to be contained by the black light barrier. However, the magic power fluctuations on this occasion were incredibly fierce, and the black light barrier began to buzz and tremble incessantly, seemingly on the verge of being overwhelmed.

Thankfully, it only took around two or three seconds before a large hole was eroded into the section of the yellow light barrier encircled by the array flags.

The figure immediately flew through the hole in the light barrier, landing near the white jade pillar before opening his mouth to release a cloud of dense black qi. The black qi enveloped the jade pillar, and at the same time, he made a hand seal before releasing a string of black incantation seals onto the pillar.

The black qi quickly spread over the jade pillar, staining all of the runes on its surface black.

The light glowing from the jade pillar quickly dimmed, and the fierce light surging over the yellow light barrier also slowly receded. Soon, everything was back to normal.

With a wave of the figure's hand, the dozen or so array flags flew out of the light barrier before returning to his grasp, and they were promptly stowed away.

Immediately thereafter, the figure flipped a hand over to produce a stack of yellow array flags, which shot forth as around a dozen streaks of light that struck the yellow light barrier from the inside.

These array flags flew into the light barrier before vanishing without encountering any resistance.

The entire yellow light barrier rippled momentarily before returning to normal, and the large hole that had been corroded into its surface also quickly sealed over again.

Only then did the figure direct his attention toward the dozen or so stone cabinets positioned around the jade pillar.

Every single one of the stone cabinets was enshrouded within a dark red light barrier.

The figure made his way over to one of the stone cabinets, then opened his mouth to release a burst of azure qi onto the light barrier without any hesitation. The affected area of the light barrier instantly began to ripple violently, and the red light quickly began to fade, looking as if it were about to be snuffed out imminently.

Right at this moment, specks of white light appeared on the surface of the red light barrier, and the red and white lights intertwined to keep the azure qi at bay.

At the same time, the deafening sound of a huge gong being struck rang out deep within the hall.

The space around the figure rippled slightly, and he seemed to have been caught off guard by this.

However, in the next instant, he immediately began to chant an incantation while making a series of hand seals, and the cloud of azure qi immediately began to churn violently, taking on various different forms to attack the red and white restriction, but no matter what form the azure qi took on, it was still unable to break through.

All of a sudden, the figure dispelled the cloud of azure qi in a decisive manner with a wave of his hand. He then joined his index and middle fingers together before pressing them against his glabella, and a black rift suddenly split open there before widening to reveal an inky-black eyeball.

Black runes emerged within the eyeball, and a beam of black light around as thick as a human finger shot out before striking the restriction around the stone cabinet in a flash.

In the face of the beam of black light, the red and white restriction was instantly punctured before shattering with a dull thump.

At the same time, a burst of enormous spiritual sense erupted out of the figure's glabella before splitting itself up into around a dozen portions, each of which entered a jade slip before rapidly inspecting its contents.

With the strike of that gong, all of the restrictions outside the scripture library instantly began to flash wildly while a piercing alarm rang out.

"Someone's broken into the scripture library!"

"Who would dare to do that? They must have a death wish!"

"Could it be the same bastard that broke into the Heavenly Talisman Hall two days ago?"

A series of furious voices rang out as one figure after another converged toward the scripture library from all directions.

With the precedent set by the Heavenly Talisman Hall incident, the patrols didn't hesitate at all, informing the sect's higher-ups of the situation while the most powerful patrol group leaders among them instantly charged into the scripture library.

Lights appeared all over the Cold Flame Sect in the night, and a chaotic commotion erupted.

The first people to react were actually the two Spatial Tempering cultivators at the entrance of the inner library.

As soon as the alarm was raised, the two of them immediately sprang to their feet with furious expressions.

Someone had snuck into the inner library right under their noses!

Could it really have been a Grand Ascension cultivator?

That same thought immediately occurred to both of them, but this wasn't the time to be pondering such matters. Each of them quickly summoned a jade talisman, but one was of a crescent shape, while the other was ovular in form.

The two jade talismans were placed together to form a complete circle, which was immediately adhered to a certain part of the stone door.

The rippling restriction on the door quickly vanished, and the stone door swung open, following which the two of them immediately flew in without any hesitation.

Both of them faltered slightly at the sight of the black light barrier before them.

In a state of urgency, the portly monk quickly made a decision, gritting his teeth as he flipped a hand over to produce a round mirror.

He made a hand seal, and gray light flashed from the mirror before it released a thick beam of gray light, which struck the black light barrier with a deafening boom.

The light barrier churned violently as large ripples surged over its surface, but it wasn't immediately destroyed.

At the same time, the thin man summoned four azure flying swords, which circled around briefly in the air before transforming into four azure lotus flowers.

Countless streaks of azure sword qi erupted out of the four azure lotus flowers, all of which struck the black light barrier.

Finally, the black barrier was unable to withstand the assault and was torn apart to reveal the scene within.

"Stop!"

The two Spatial Tempering cultivators were quite relieved to see the indistinct silver figure within the light barrier, but at the same time, they were also furious and embarrassed.

The figure was only giving off a Nascent Soul aura!

However, the figure paid no heed to the two Spatial Tempering cultivators. He had just finished inspecting the contents of the jade slips in one of the stone cabinets, and he quickly moved on to another one.

Another beam of black light shot out of his glabella to shatter the restriction around that stone cabinet, following which he calmly released his spiritual sense again to glean the contents of the jade slips in the cabinet.

Chapter 37: Escape

"How dare you!"

"Surrender now and we'll grant you a swift and painless death!"

The portly monk and his companion were furious, and the former flipped a hand over to produce a yellow jade badge, which he thrust forward with venom.

A beam of yellow light shot out of the surface of the jade badge, landing on the yellow light barrier in a flash.

The light barrier instantly parted down the center to create a path that was around 20 feet wide.

The two Spatial Tempering cultivators instantly flew in, charging toward the figure inside.

Right at this moment, the figure suddenly raised a hand, chanting an incantation as he pointed a finger forward.

A beam of black light erupted out of his fingertip before striking the white jade pillar at the center of the hall.

All of the runes on the jade pillar instantly lit up, as did the yellow light barrier, and it released countless bursts of yellow light that struck the two Spatial Tempering cultivators like lightning while they were still in mid-air.

As a result, both of them instantly felt as if they had fallen into a swamp. Their body weight increased by several hundredfold in the blink of an eye, and it became extremely difficult to even raise a hand.

"The array has been tampered with!" the thin man exclaimed in shock.

"Who are you? How are you able to manipulate this array?" the portly monk interrogated in a furious voice.

The figure completely ignored them as his spiritual sense quickly read through the jade slips, and at the same time, he made a string of hand seals without pause, casting a series of incantation seals onto the white jade pillar.

The yellow light instantly began to ripple before revolving around the pair of Spatial Tempering cultivators, forming a pair of yellow vortexes that completely bound them.

The two of them struggled with all their might, frantically unleashing attacks to strike at the yellow vortexes that they were trapped within, but no matter what they did, they were completely powerless to escape.

Their fury and frustration were growing by the second, but there was nothing that they could do. This yellow restriction was set up to keep out enemies, but somehow, it was being used against them.

Right at this moment, seven or eight figures flew in front outside, all of whom were Deity Transformation Stage patrol group leaders.

They were momentarily stunned by the sight that they were greeted by, but they quickly returned to their senses, summoning a series of treasures to attack the yellow restriction in an attempt to rescue the pair of Spatial Tempering cultivators.

"Stop! Don't attack!" the portly monk exclaimed in an alarmed voice.

However, it was already too late. Seven or eight treasures struck the yellow vortexes, causing them to tremble violently.

However, at the same time, a series of millstone-sized bulges appeared on the yellow vortexes, and seven or eight tentacle-like bursts of light shot out in a flash, wrapping themselves around the Deity Transformation cultivators before dragging them into the vortexes in the blink of an eye.

These patrol group leaders possessed far inferior cultivation bases to the Spatial Tempering cultivators, so they were naturally completely immobilized as well.

"Damn it!" the portly monk roared in frustration.

"Have you notified the sect of the situation here?" the thin man asked in an urgent voice.

"The sect... has already... been notified..." Even speaking was difficult for the Deity Transformation Stage patrol group leaders.

The expressions of the two Spatial Tempering cultivators eased slightly upon hearing this, and they turned their attention back to the figure.

The figure was still breaking restrictions one after another before rapidly reading through the contents of the jade slips in the stone cabinets. He was doing so with astounding speed and efficiency, and he had already read through most of the jade slips in the room.

The two Spatial Tempering cultivators were desperate to intervene, but there was nothing that they could do aside from watch helplessly from within the confines of the yellow restriction.

"Who dares to infiltrate the scripture library?"

Right at his moment, a thunderous roar rang out from outside, causing the air within the entire hall to tremble violently, and even the yellow restriction was swaying slightly in the face of the powerful soundwaves.

The eardrums of the cultivators trapped in the yellow restriction were ringing loudly, but ecstatic looks had appeared on all of their faces.

The figure stiffened slightly upon hearing this voice, then cast his gaze outside, following which the vertical black eye in his glabella began to glow brightly.

Several beams of black light shot forth in a flash, shattering the restrictions of the three remaining stone cabinets at the same time.

Almost at the exact same moment, a red-haired giant of a man came barreling in through the entrance.

The man was over 20 feet tall and was built like a steel wall. He was wearing a crimson robe that was burning with scorching flames, and the entire hall was instantly plunged into what felt like a lava pit.

Judging from the aura radiating from the man's body, he was a Body Integration Stage powerful being.

"Die!"

The red-haired man cast his gaze toward the figure, and his eyes were practically burning with fury.

With a sweep of his hand, he sent a massive burning sword flying through the air, and the sword swelled to several hundred feet in size mid-flight before striking the yellow light barrier with devastating might.

A vast expanse of yellow light emerged in an attempt to oppose the giant sword, but it didn't even manage to make contact with the sword before it was torn apart by the flames burning on the blade of the sword.

The giant flaming sword struck the yellow barrier with ferocious might, and countless cracks instantly appeared on its surface, but it was able to withstand the attack without completely shattering.

Right at this moment, the figure swept a hand through the air, releasing a burst of suction force that drew all of the jade slips in the three stone cabinets into his grasp before being stowed away.

The red-haired man was furious to see this, and he immediately made a hand seal, upon which the giant flaming sword swelled to twice its original size, and the flames on its surface sprang up to several dozen feet.

The yellow light barrier was completely shattered with a dull thump, and the two Spatial Tempering cultivators and the Deity Transformation Stage patrol group leaders were finally freed.

The giant flaming sword faltered momentarily, then continued to crash down toward the figure.

All of a sudden, the figure raised his head, and dazzling light erupted out of the vertical eye in his glabella. Countless back runes surfaced within the eye, and a thick pillar of black light was blasted straight into the giant sword.

A dull thump rang out as the pillar of black light exploded, and most of the flames on the giant sword instantly dissipated.

At the same time, ripples surged through the surrounding space, immobilizing the sword in mid-air, thereby preventing its fall.

"That's the Law Destruction Eye!" the red-haired man exclaimed. [1]

The figure made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and a burst of purple lightning appeared over his body before quickly spreading to form a lightning array around him. Dazzling light flashed within the array amid a rumbling thunderclap, and the blurry figure within the array had become even more indistinct.

"You're not getting away!"

The red-haired man's fury was growing by the second, and all of a sudden, flames rose up on the giant sword again as it abruptly split itself into two.

A fiery sword projection that was comparable in size to the giant sword came crashing down, traveling several times faster than the giant sword itself as it struck the lightning array.

A resounding boom rang out as dazzling red light erupted in all directions alongside bursts of violent shockwaves.

The two Spatial Tempering cultivators shuddered violently, and they were forced to take several backward steps before finally managing to steady themselves. As for the Deity Transformation Stage patrol group leaders, their legs instantly gave out from under them, causing them to fall to their knees, and the protective spiritual light around them was flickering like a candle in the breeze.

The red light dissipated, revealing a deep trench that had been slashed into the ground, but the figure had already vanished.

Everyone exchanged a series of bewildered glances before turning to the red-haired man, who wore a furious expression.

Meanwhile, at the center of the secret chamber in Han Li's cave abode.

There was a large purple array engraved onto the ground, and arcs of electricity were surging throughout the array. Han Li's eyes were tightly shut, and he was seated beside the array with his eyes closed.

All of a sudden, a burst of dazzling light appeared in the array, and a resounding thunderclap rang out, following which a humanoid figure enshrouded in black qi emerged.

Han Li's eyes immediately sprang open, and a hint of elation appeared on his face as he cast an incantation seal.

The black qi around the figure quickly faded, revealing a shimmering silver-armored warrior that had been summoned from a talisman.

Half of the silver-armored warrior was destroyed, and its aura was fading in and out of existence, seemingly about to be snuffed out at any moment.

With a wave of Han Li's hand, around 20 to 30 jade slips flew out of the armored warrior's body before landing in his grasp.

He stowed the jade slips away, then pressed a finger against the armored warrior's glabella.

Black light flashed from the armored warrior's glabella, following which an egg-sized black bead flew out from within with a burst of silver energy slowly flowing within it.

At the same time, the light on the armored warrior's body faded, and it disintegrated into a tattered silver talisman and a purple talisman, both of which drifted down through the air at the same time.

The silver talisman was none other than the Armor Origin Talisman, while the purple one was the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman, both of which had been refined using the materials that Han Li had stolen from the Heavenly Talisman Hall several days ago. [2]

Unfortunately, the Armor Origin Talisman was already too severely damaged for further usage.

[1]. For more on the Law Destruction Eye, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1180: Fire Spirit Threads and the Law Destruction Eye.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on the Armor Origin Talisman and the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman, refer to RMJI Chapter 1472: Two Talismans and Chapter 1306: High Zenith Invisibility Talisman, respectively.

[Back]

Chapter 38: A Glimmer of Hope

Han Li quickly stowed the two talismans away, then sat down with his legs crossed and held the black bead between his thumb and index finger before pressing it against his own glabella.

The silver qi within the bead immediately began to seep out wisp by wisp, circling around his glabella momentarily before vanishing into it.

If one were to look closely, one would discover that this silver qi was actually comprised of countless tiny characters that were even smaller than the tiniest of mosquitoes. These were all of the cultivation arts and secret techniques that the Armor Origin Talisman puppet had gleaned from the scripture library earlier.

Even with Han Li's unfathomably powerful spiritual sense, it was impossible to absorb such an enormous amount of content all at once.

However, he was in no hurry, and he had plenty of time to spend on this.

Time slowly passed by, and Han Li continued to sit as still as a statue for three days and three nights.

Only on the morning of the fourth day did he slowly open his eyes, upon which his brows furrowed slightly.

Some of these scriptures were quite remarkable, presenting incredible ideas and concepts that even he couldn't help but be in awe of, but none of them fit his current needs.

He shook his head as he stowed the black bead away, then swept a sleeve through the air, upon which 30 to 40 jade slips appeared on the ground. These were the jade slips that the Armor Origin Talisman puppet had taken right before its departure from the scripture library.

He swept his gaze over these jade slips with a slightly disheartened expression, hoping that he would find something useful among them.

With that in mind, Han Li picked up one of the jade slips before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

Another whole day passed by, and as Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense from the final jade slip, there was a clear look of disappointment in his eyes.

These jade slips all contained advanced and profound cultivation arts and secret techniques, but there was still nothing that was useful to him.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face. He had gone to great lengths to secure these resources, stirring the entire sect up into a frenzy in the process, but it had all been for nothing.

He shook his head as he prepared to destroy all of the jade slips.

Even though he had already examined the jade slips and confirmed that none of them had any tracking restrictions applied to them, it was already clear that the Spirit Domain Realm contained some things that he was unfamiliar with, such as quintessential purple qi. As such, there was no guarantee that there were no measures applied to these jade slips that were undetectable to him, so it was better to be safe than sorry.

All of a sudden, a surprised look appeared on Han Li's face.

All of the jade slips had been reduced to a pile of dust, but there was a completely unremarkable yellow jade slip among them that was completely unharmed.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he picked up the jade slip before inspecting it closely with an intrigued expression.

The power that he had just unleashed would've been enough to completely destroy even a piece of iron essence, yet this jade slip was completely unscathed.

After some inspection, Han Li discovered that there was nothing remarkable about the jade slip. It was made from normal jade, and he had inspected its contents earlier to find that all it contained was a cultivation art suitable for Spatial Tempering cultivators.

Han Li inspected the jade slip for a moment longer before applying some squeezing force through his fingers.

A faint sheen of luster that resembled starlight suddenly appeared on the surface of the jade slip, keeping his power at bay.

His eyes lit up slightly as he relaxed his grip again, and the faint sheen of light also vanished.

It seemed that there really was something special about this jade slip.

He could sense that the starry sheen wasn't a tracking restriction.

Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip again with the idea that perhaps there was something special about the cultivation art that it contained, but once again, he was unable to discover anything of note.

He read through the contents of the cultivation art from top to bottom three to four times, and he even tried cultivating it, but he still failed to find any hidden secrets.

"Could it be that I'm mistaken?" Han Li murmured to himself.

However, he was still unwilling to give up, and he released an enormous burst of spiritual sense out of his glabella, completely enveloping the jade slip before carefully inspecting it inch by inch.

The starry sheen immediately surfaced on the jade slip again, and it was giving off a devouring force that was eating away at Han Li's spiritual sense.

Immediately thereafter, a speck of golden light appeared on the jade slip's surface.

Han Li was initially quite alarmed by this, but his alarm quickly turned into elation, and instead of withdrawing his spiritual sense, he allowed the jade slip to devour it as it pleased.

As time passed, an astonished look gradually appeared on his face.

The jade slip was like a bottomless pit. It had already devoured close to a fifth of his spiritual sense, yet it still wasn't satisfied, and at this point, the speck of golden light had already grown to the size of a broad bean.

At the moment, his spiritual sense was only at around 10% of its peak, but due to the cultivation arts that he practiced, it was still comparable to that of the average immortal, yet this jade slip had managed to devour a huge chunk of it.

It was going to take quite some time to recover this spiritual sense, but after some brief contemplation, Han Li decided to continue with the process.

Moments later, an astonishing scene ensued.

More and more golden light began to appear on the jade slip, filling its entire surface before gradually forming a golden diagram of the Big Dipper.

At the same time, the devouring force being released by the jade slip finally ceased.

Han Li heaved a sigh of relief as he picked up the jade slip with an ecstatic expression, and as he injected his spiritual sense into it again, he couldn't help but be stunned by what he saw.

The contents of the jade slip were also changing, and the previous body of tiny yellow text had disappeared, only to be replaced by large passages of golden text.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this before hurriedly reading through the new text.

Only after a full 15 minutes had passed did he raise his head with an elated look in his eyes.

The new jade slip contained a body refinement secret technique by the name of the Bigger Dipper Origin Arts.

According to information that Patriarch Cold Flame had left in the jade slip, this was not a cultivation art that could be found in the Spirit Domain Realm. Instead, it was an authentic Immortal Realm cultivation art that the patriarch had sent down to the Spirit Domain Realm following his ascension.

What was worthy of note was that the cultivation of this secret technique didn't depend on the spiritual power of heaven and earth. Instead, it involved refining the physical body by drawing the power of starlight into the body.

The cultivation art was split up into seven levels, and with each level that was mastered, he would be able to manifest a profound aperture. After mastering all seven levels, seven apertures would be manifested, allowing one to attain a True Extreme Body, thereby becoming a legendary Profound Immortal.

Given the current state of his nascent soul, he was unable to cultivate using the spiritual qi of heaven and earth, but perhaps he could try to harness the power of starlight.

However, at the end of the cultivation art, Patriarch Cold Flame had specifically left a note, which contained a warning that refining one's body using the power of starlight was going to put them in constant excruciating pain.

Furthermore, this was not an orthodox cultivation art. It could dramatically enhance one's physical body, but it was impossible to elevate one's magic power using this cultivation art. Even if they could master this cultivation art, they would have to pursue the path of becoming a Profound Immortal, which was a far more difficult path than becoming an ordinary immortal. Thus, one was advised not to practice this cultivation art unless they were absolutely certain that they wanted to pursue such an arduous path.

Most importantly, in order to practice this cultivation art, not only was it a prerequisite that one had to already possess a sufficiently powerful physical body, enormous spiritual sense was also required to draw the power of starlight into the body. Hence, the barrier to entry was extremely steep.

Back when Patriarch Cold Flame sent this cultivation art down from the Immortal Realm, he had placed a special restriction on the jade slip so that only those with sufficiently powerful spiritual sense would be able to see the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

Han Li's grip tightened slightly with excitement around the jade slip, and he felt like he could see a glimmer of hope.

The Big Dipper Origin Arts was virtually tailor-made for him. Even though there was a warning that practicing the cultivation art was going to be extremely painful, that didn't discourage him at all.

However, right at this moment, the jade slip in his hand suddenly cracked before transforming into a ball of piercing golden light.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly upon seeing this, and he raised his head to discover a golden figure hovering in mid-air.

The figure was a well-built middle-aged man with a square face that wore a stern expression, giving off a sense of authority and righteousness.

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon seeing this. Having seen a portrait of this man in the sect, he knew that it was none other than Patriarch Cold Flame!

"Fantastic! Looks like my efforts didn't go to waste. Finally, someone has managed to unravel this restriction! Which peak are you a disciple of, and what is your name?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked with a warm smile.

Han Li's mind was racing as he scrambled to fabricate a convincing lie.

It was clear that this was an avatar left behind by Patriarch Cold Flame's spiritual sense, but it still gave him a significant sense of pressure, so it was most likely quite formidable in battle.

Before Han Li had a chance to reply, Patriarch Cold Flame's brows suddenly furrowed slightly, and his voice took a cold turn as he asked, "Why do I not sense the aura of any of our sect's cultivation arts in you? Could it be that you're not an inner court disciple?"

"I am a guest elder who has only recently joined the sect, so I still haven't had a chance to practice any of the sect's cultivation arts yet," Han Li hurriedly replied.

"A guest elder? How did a guest elder like you get your hands on the jade slip containing the Big Dipper Origin Arts?" Patriarch Cold Flame interrogated in a cold voice.

Han Li had no response to this.

Patriarch Cold Flame's gaze then fell upon the pile of powder near Han Li's feet.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon seeing this, but his heart sank ever so slightly.

Chapter 39: Decree

Patriarch Cold Flame swept a hand through the air, releasing a burst of golden light that swept up all of the powder in front of Han Li, forming a ball of faint golden light that hovered before him.

"These are all jade slips that contain cultivation arts and secret techniques of our sect. Why are they all in your possession? Could it be that you broke into the inner library and stole them?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked in a cold voice.

Even though the jade slips had been reduced to powder by Han Li, even the slightest trace of what they had once been was enough for Patriarch Cold Flame to identify them.

A resigned look appeared on Han Li's face, and he sighed, "I can explain, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame."

"How dare you refer to me as an equal to yourself!"

Patriarch Cold Flame was furious, and dazzling golden light abruptly erupted out of his glabella. Countless rippling circles of light swept through the air, instantly forming a golden flower projection that was around 10 feet in size.

As the golden flower slowly revolved, light flashed from its bud, and a near-transparent pillar of golden light was released, hurtling toward Han Li at an incredible speed.

The space in the wake of the pillar of light rippled like water.

Han Li remained on the spot, making no attempt to take evasive action. Instead, he merely raised his head slightly, and a burst of invisible ripples erupted out of his glabella as well to oppose the pillar of golden light.

A dull thump rang out, and the space shuddered violently as ripples surged through the air.

It seemed that the golden pillar of light had crashed into something, and it quickly disintegrated, while the invisible ripples also faded.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and Han Li remained completely unscathed as he stood with a faint smile on his face.

Patriarch Cold Flame shuddered as he exclaimed in an incredulous voice, "Impossible! Are you also an immortal?"

Even though this was only a projection manifested by his spiritual sense, and that wasn't an all-out attack, even a Grand Ascension cultivator definitely wouldn't have been able to withstand the attack so easily, let alone a Nascent Soul cultivator.

This indicated that Han Li's spiritual sense wasn't inferior to his own!

"Will you listen to me now, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame?" Han Li asked in a calm voice.

Patriarch Cold Flame was silent for a moment, and even though he was still rather displeased, he was clearly willing to listen. "Fine. Why don't you tell me why you're here stealing the scriptures of our sect when you've already ascended to become an immortal."

"Due to some unforeseen circumstances, I fell into the Spirit Domain Realm by chance. I bear no ill will toward your sect, but I currently have some injuries, and I do not have the suitable pills to treat those injuries, so I decided to take some of the scriptures of your sect to conduct some research," Han Li explained.

"I see. May I ask which Immortal Region you were originally from, Fellow Daoist?" Despite what he was saying, it was clear from the look in Patriarch Cold Flame's eyes that he didn't completely believe Han Li's story.

"I'm only staying here for now, and I can assure you that I won't do anything detrimental to your sect. As for where I've come from, that's something that I'd rather not share," Han Li replied with a hint of a smile on his face.

Patriarch Cold Flame gave a cold harrumph upon hearing this. An immortal had suddenly appeared in the Spirit Domain Realm, so he was naturally inclined to find out as much about this immortal as possible. However, this was only an avatar formed by a wisp of his spiritual sense, so he couldn't really do anything if Han Li were unwilling to answer his questions.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist. I owe you a favor for this, and in exchange, I can promise you here and now that if the Cold Flame Sect encounters any trouble in the future, I can step in one time to resolve the sect's troubles," Han Li continued in an unhurried voice.

Patriarch Cold Flame was greatly moved by this. "I'll be holding you to that promise, Fellow Daoist."

Even though he had already ascended to the Immortal Realm, he still greatly cherished the Cold Flame Sect, which he had built up from nothing. Otherwise, he wouldn't have gone out of his way to send resources down to the sect.

It seemed that the Cold Flame Sect was a dominant powerhouse in the Spirit Domain Realm with a bright future ahead, but the sect was not truly without its concerns.

Unfortunately, he was in the Immortal Realm, so there wasn't much that he could do to help the sect. However, if he could recruit the assistance of Han Li, then a whole host of possibilities would be opened up.

……

Two days later, on the Holy Fire Peak of the Cold Flame Sect.

There was an elegant tile courtyard situated deep in a misty purple bamboo forest.

The purple bamboo trees in the forest were neatly organized, and the arrangement didn't seem to be remarkable in any way, but in reality, there was a hidden purpose to how everything was positioned.

The position of every single purple bamboo tree corresponded with a node of an array, and this vast sea of purple bamboo formed a unique array.

The purple bamboo planted here also wasn't just bamboo of the ordinary variety. Instead, it was Lungfire Bamboo that was capable of absorbing the power of earthly fire. If one were to inspect these bamboo trees closely, they would discover that there were dark red patterns spread along the surface of the bamboo.

It was exactly because of the existence of this array that this area had the most abundant spiritual qi in the entire Spirit Flame Mountain Range, and it was also the area with the highest concentration of earthly fire.

The small tile courtyard was situated right on the core of the array.

At this moment, there was a purple-robed man seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed, cultivating in the main room inside the courtyard.

The man had a head of shoulder-length hair that was as white as snow, and there was a purple flame insignia on his glabella. There was purple qi revolving all around him, and he appeared to be no more than 30 years of age, but he was giving off an extremely powerful aura.

On a small rosewood table not far in front of him was a gold-plated copper incense burner, protruding out of which were several sticks of lit incense that were releasing wisps of smoke.

The table was situated right next to the wall, upon which a portrait of a middle-aged man that was over three feet in length was hanging.

The lines of the portrait weren't particularly intricate, but they were extremely effective in conveying the aura of the subject. The portrait depicted a man with a square face and a pair of bright and piercing eyes. The man had a very strong build, and even his visage alone was giving off a strong sense of authority and righteousness.

Right at this moment, the white-haired man's eyes suddenly sprang open, and he cast a surprised gaze toward the portrait on the wall.

A burst of peculiar fluctuations suddenly erupted out of the portrait, and a series of ripples spread over its surface. It was as if the subject of the portrait had suddenly sprung to life, and he stepped out of the portrait as if it were a portal leading to another realm.

The white-haired man hurriedly rose to his feet, then fell to his knees, trembling slightly with emotion as he greeted in a respectful voice, "Welcome, Patriarch."

"No need for formalities. I've come to you today with some instructions," Patriarch Cold Flame said with a wave of his hand.

Only then did the white-haired man return to his feet, and he waited with a respectful expression for further instructions.

"I've already heard about the incident that took place at the scripture library some days ago," Patriarch Cold Flame said.

The white-haired man's heart jolted upon hearing this, and cold sweat instantly began to appear on his forehead. He was just about to offer an explanation, but he was cut off by Patriarch Cold Flame. "Leave this matter and do not investigate it any further."

The white-haired man faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he couldn't help but protest, "But Patriarch..."

However, Patriarch Cold Flame raised a hand to cut him off, then communicated something to him through voice transmission.

The white-haired man's expression changed once again upon hearing this, first turning to surprise before switching to elation.

Chapter 40: Inconclusive

That afternoon.

A streak of white light shot through the distant sky before landing on a white jade plaza on the Holy Fire Peak.

The light faded to reveal a clean-shaven middle-aged man.

The man was wearing a scholarly robe, which was flapping around him as he slowly descended, and as soon as he landed on the plaza, he was immediately greeted by a male voice that rang out behind him.

"Brother Nangong."

The middle-aged man turned to discover a man with a black beard wearing a set of daoist robes approaching him from several thousand feet away.

The man didn't appear to be moving very quickly, but there was a trail of afterimages in his wake, and he was able to cover a distance of several hundred feet with each step, arriving in front of the scholarly-robed man in the blink of an eye.

"Let's go together, Brother Zhuang," the scholarly-robed man greeted with a smile.

The daoist priest nodded in response, then cast his gaze toward several streaks of light that were flying through the distant sky, and he remarked, "If I recall correctly, it's been over a decade since such a big fuss has been kicked up about anything in the sect."

These two were none other than Nangong Changshan and Zhuang Ziyou, the masters of the Cloudrise Peak and the Sunset Peak, respectively.

"This most likely has something to do with the recent scripture library incident. I'm afraid we won't be able to escape accountability," Nangong Changshan sighed with a shake of his head.

"I was busy refining some pills at the time, but I did hear mention of the incident, and the circumstances seem rather strange to me... Not only was the perpetrator able to bypass all of the restrictions to enter the inner library, even Elder Huyan was unable to stop him from escaping," Zhuang Ziyou mused with a grim expression.

"It was indeed a rather peculiar incident. I'm sure the supreme elder will elaborate on the matter when we meet him," Nangong Changshan replied with a nod.

As the two were conversing with one another, they had already passed through the plaza and arrived in front of a grand and majestic red palace. Both of them fell silent here, then quickly scaled the staircase before stepping into the palace together.

At the center of the palace was an elevated section that was around three feet above the ground, upon which was an intricately engraved chair. Below this chair were two more rows of chairs that were facing one another, one on the left, and one on the right.

The pillars behind the chairs were all constructed from precious materials with all types of exotic birds and beasts engraved onto their surfaces.

On the chair in the left row situated closest to the main seat sat a red-haired man in a crimson robe. There was a dark look on his face, and he was built like a steel tower, with a musclebound body that gave off an astonishing aura.

Nangong Changshan and Zhuang Ziyou exchanged a glance with one another, then picked a pair of neighboring chairs before sitting down and closing their eyes to meditate.

More and more people continued to enter the palace, and soon, all of the chairs in the hall were occupied.

All of the people present were at the Spatial Tempering Stage, and there wasn't even a single cultivator at or below the Deity Transformation Stage.

However, all of them were wearing rather grim expressions, and they only exchanged the most concise of greetings, seemingly not interested in chatting.

The entire palace was filled with a rather oppressive and solemn atmosphere.

A few minutes after all of the chairs in the palace were occupied, two more figures strode into the palace from the inner hall.

Everyone in the palace immediately rose to their feet, including the red-haired man, and they all extended a collective respectful bow as they greeted in a unified voice, "We pay our respects to the supreme elder and the sect master!"

The one walking at the front was a purple-robed man with hair as white as snow, and he was the Cold Flame Sect's sole supreme elder, Sima Jingming. Accompanying him was an authoritative middle-aged man wearing a tall hat, and he was the master of the Cold Flame Sect, Liu Jingzhu.

Sima Jingming made his way over to the main seat, but instead of sitting down, his gaze slowly swept over everyone present.

His aura was completely subdued, but even though he was only casually standing there, he still gave off an astonishing sense of pressure. Everyone lowered their heads, not daring to look at one another or even breathe too loudly for fear of retribution.

A short while later, Sima Jingming finally began to speak.

"Recently, two incidents of theft have taken place in quick succession at the Heavenly Talisman Hall and the scripture library, and it is for this reason that all of you have been invited here."

His voice wasn't very loud, but it was filled with an indescribable sense of authority.

Everyone involuntarily tensed up slightly upon hearing this, and they were all waiting in silence for the tirade that was surely to come.

However, what Sima Jingming declared next instantly had everyone looking up with stunned expressions.

"I hereby declare that this will be the end of the matter. Cease all investigations with immediate effect."

Everyone was astonished to hear this, and they couldn't help but exchange bewildered glances, wondering if they had misheard the message.

However, no one dared to ask any questions, either.

In the end, it was the red-haired man who broke the silence, and he stepped forward as he cupped his fist in a salute. "Senior Martial Brother Sima, the theft that took place at the scripture library is a major incident. I..."

Before he had a chance to finish, he was cut off by Sima Jingming, who interjected in a cold voice, "Do I need to repeat myself, Junior Martial Brother Huyan?"

With that, he turned and departed from the palace, offering no further explanation, leaving everyone completely perplexed.

At the same time, Sect Master Liu Jingzhu declared, "That concludes the meeting. You can all go now."

After that, he also departed.

A short while later, on the white jade plaza outside the palace.

Zhuang Ziyou was still reeling from the announcement, and he turned to Nangong Changshan as he asked, "We're supposed to just cease all investigations? Are we simply accepting the loss of so many precious scriptures from the scripture library?"

"The loss of the scriptures isn't a big deal. I'm sure our sect will have replicas that can replace them. However, it's going to be a problem if these secret scriptures are leaked to the outside world. The supreme elder must have his reasons for making such a decision, so let's not speculate aimlessly about this," Nangong Changshan replied with a smile.

Despite what he was saying, he was no less perplexed than Zhuang Ziyou.

Not long after that meeting, all of the disciples of the Cold Flame Sect noticed something extremely puzzling, which was that the sect had suddenly ceased all investigations and searches at the Heavenly Talisman Hall and the scripture library.

This naturally created quite a stir among all of the disciples, but all of the peak masters seemed to be very reluctant to speak on the matter.

Thus, what should've been a pair of incidents with far-reaching consequences and implications blew over under inexplicable circumstances with no concrete conclusions reached.

As the perpetrator, Han Li was completely oblivious to everything that had taken place in the sect. He was holed up in his cave abode, studying the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

Prior to this, he had only quickly read through the cultivation art, but the more he studied it, the more he came to realize how profound and ingenious it was, and the more excited he became.

Ever since he began his cultivation journey, he had come into contact with many body refinement cultivation arts. Some of those cultivation arts primarily refined the muscles and tendons, some focused on refining the bones, and there were also some that refined the internal organs, such as the Organ Refinement Origin Arts. [1]

However, the Big Dipper Origin Arts was unique in that it focused on the cultivation of profound apertures.

What were profound apertures supposed to be?

Han Li had no clue, and there were no further elaborations offered in the cultivation art, either. However, judging from the scripture, the cultivation process was extremely profound, and even for him, it had taken a long time to make sense of the process being described.

To put it in simple terms, if one could attain full mastery of this cultivation art, then they would attain physical power comparable with that of the average immortal.

However, at the same time, there were also many caveats.

Firstly, the cultivation process was extremely painful, and for those with insufficient mental fortitude, there was no way that they would be able to last till the very end.

Secondly, it was extremely difficult to draw in the power of starlight. After all, the stars were an unfathomable distance away. As a result, practicing this cultivation art was extremely time-consuming.

Han Li paid no heed to these caveats, and he planned to begin pursuing the cultivation art right away.

First, he made a trip somewhere, only returning the next day, upon which he immediately activated all of the restrictions within the cave abode.

After that, he chose a suitable secret chamber before opening up a large hole in the ceiling, which allowed him to see the sky.

After doing all of that, he sat down with his legs crossed and began to meditate.

Before practicing a cultivation art that had been passed down from the Immortal Realm, he had to prime himself into the optimal condition so that he was best equipped to deal with any circumstances that could arise during the cultivation process.

[1]. For more information on the Organ Refinement Origin Arts, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2339: Organ Refinement Origin Arts.

[Back]

Chapter 41: Heaven Controlling Vial

One night, several days later.

The entire sky was completely clear with not a single cloud in sight. The moon was hanging up in the heavens amid the stars, and there were occasionally shooting stars flashing past.

Inside the secret chamber of his cave abode, Han Li was seated at the center with his legs crossed and his eyes closed. Rays of starlight spilled down through the large hole in the ceiling, basking his entire body in faint silver radiance.

Beneath him, a complex array had been carved into the ground.

The array consisted of seven large star diagrams, each of which was around the size of a cushion . The diagrams were all glowing brightly, and they connected together to form the shape of the Big Dipper.

The array was known as the Big Dipper Energy Gathering Array, and it wasn't actually recorded in the Big Dipper Origin Arts. Instead, it was something that Han Li had adapted from another star array based on his observation of the stars.

All of the stars in the sky appeared to be quite similar, but the powers that they bestowed were completely different. Some leaned more toward the Yin side of the spectrum, while others were more Yang inclined, and there were even some that fluctuated between the two. The Big Dipper Origin Arts drew upon the power of the Big Dipper's seven stars, which were constantly changing to provide a profound and irreplicable source of starpower.

This array had been created by Han Li in accordance with the special properties of the seven stars, and it was able to assist him in harnessing the starpower of the Big Dipper.

At this moment, he was seated on the first star of the Big Dipper constellation in the array.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open, and he swept a hand through the air to release an incantation seal.

The star array beneath him immediately began to revolve, and the seven stars began to glow brightly, with the first one glowing particularly bright. Specks of white light emerged out of thin air, filling the surrounding space to form countless constellation diagrams.

Situated within this sea of stars, Han Li's figure was made to appear rather blurry and indistinct.

He chanted an incantation while making a series of hand seals in accordance with the stipulations of the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

Around 15 minutes later, a burst of astonishingly powerful spiritual sense swept out of his glabella, circling around before forming an invisible vortex above his head.

He then switched to a different hand seal, and the spiritual sense vortex above him spread open, gradually taking on a form that resembled a nebula.

The Big Dipper Origin Arts also appeared in the nebula, and it was resonating with the star array down below.

Han Li raised his head, casting his gaze through the large hole in the ceiling, looking up at the seven stars that were glowing the brightest in the night sky. His gaze then fell upon the Dubhe star, the first star of the Big Dipper, and he began to chant a complex incantation.

The dazzling Dubhe star seemed to flash momentarily, following which boundless starpower came cascading down from it like a silver waterfall, passing through the large hole in the ceiling to encompass Han Li's entire body, enveloping him in surging starpower.

A serious look appeared on Han Li's face.

One's ability to draw upon the power of starlight was dependent on the power of their spiritual sense. His current spiritual sense was comparable to that of an immortal, thereby establishing a strong foundation for practicing this cultivation art, but he still couldn't afford to grow complacent.

He continued to make a series of hand seals to operate the cultivation art, and the starpower around him instantly began to ripple before converging to form countless threads of light that resembled thin needles.

The threads of light were enveloped by his spiritual sense, and they revolved around him momentarily before falling like rain and plunging into his body.

Han Li shuddered violently as he drew a sharp breath, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

These threads of light all had substantial form, and they had pierced into his body like countless swords.

As a result, his entire body was riddled with holes that were bleeding profusely, quickly staining his robes red.

What was even more alarming was that these threads of light were racing erratically throughout his body, slicing at him from the inside like countless tiny blades.

If it weren't for his incredibly powerful physical constitution, he would've already been rolling on the ground in agony.

However, moments later, his brows gradually began to unfurrow. He could sense that the threads of starlight were slowly breaking down into the purest starpower that was seeping into all parts of his body, and that was naturally an extremely encouraging observation.

He took a deep breath, quickly suppressing the pain and elation that he was feeling so he could focus his attention entirely on operating the cultivation art.

More and more starpower fell from the heavens before piercing into his body, then began to work its way through his body in accordance with the cultivation art.

He was still carrying severe injuries that he was unable to recover from due to his inability to absorb the world's origin qi, but with this influx of pure starpower, his body immediately began to eagerly devour the starpower, and his injuries quickly began to heal.

The holes that had been pierced into his body by the threads of starlight also instantly healed, unable to cause any substantial damage to his body.

As the process continued, the agony of constantly being impaled by the threads of starlight was gradually forgotten, and he found himself completely immersed in his cultivation.

Seven days passed by in the blink of an eye.

At the center of the cave abode, Han Li was still seated on the diagram of the first star, and every single fiber of his muscles and tendons was giving off a radiance that resembled starlight, while the same starlight was also beginning to glow from his bones.

What was particularly worthy of note was that there was an extremely eye-catching speck of blue light situated at his lower abdomen.

The speck of blue light was constantly expanding and contracting as if it were breathing, and it was devouring most of the starpower that was drawn into Han Li's body.

At this point, Han Li's expression was completely calm and placid without any signs of pain.

All of a sudden, the starpower around him rippled, and the speck of blue light at his lower abdomen began to radiate dazzling light while churning incessantly.

Immediately thereafter, a profound starlight rune appeared within the blue light.

The rune only appeared for an instant before vanishing into his body in a flash.

Han Li opened his eyes, and an elated smile appeared on his face.

With his incredibly powerful physical body and spiritual sense, he was able to attain complete mastery of the first level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts in just a few days, thereby successfully manifesting his first profound aperture.

However, he still had no plans of coming out of seclusion, and he closed his eyes once again to consolidate his progress.

Several days later, on a clear and picturesque night, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open, and he raised a hand to cease the operation of the Big Dipper Energy Gathering Array. The starpower and the specks of white light around him instantly receded like the tide.

He hurriedly rose to his feet, then made his way over to a dark green vial that was sitting on the ground in front of him, then raised it up to his own eyes for closer inspection.

At this moment, the small vial was completely enshrouded in a layer of green light, and several strange golden runes had appeared on its surface, giving it a rustic appearance.

However, in the next instant, the burst of green light abruptly vanished into the dark green patterns on the vial, but the golden runes remained, bulging slightly out of the surface of the vial.

Han Li gently swayed the vial from side to side, and he could feel a drop of liquid swirling around within the vial.

A faint smile appeared on his face upon seeing this.

Over these past few days, he would always set the vial on the ground in front of him during his cultivation.

At a certain time, a layer of faint white light would always appear on the surface of the vial.

Upon closer inspection, one would discover that the layer of white light consisted of countless tiny specks of white light that were rapidly entering the vial as if they were living creatures until they were completely absorbed.

However, this phenomenon never lasted very long, and it would immediately vanish after a certain hour of the night.

Once every two days, after the vial had absorbed all of the white light, a layer of green light would appear, following which a drop of green liquid would appear in the vial.

Han Li withdrew his gaze as he gently stroked the leaf patterns on the small vial with his fingers. He was doing so with the utmost care and delicacy, as if he were stroking the cheek of a loved one.

As he felt the contours of the vial, he couldn't help but think back to a distant past.

He felt as if he had returned to the Seven Mysteries Sect and that small medicinal farm in the God Hand Valley, where he experimented with the green liquid in the small vial for the very first time. With that memory came the same sense of anxiety and anticipation that he had felt at the time. [1]

He knew that if he hadn't unintentionally discovered that the green liquid in the vial was able to accelerate the maturation of spirit medicines at the time, perhaps he would've never been able to set foot on the path of cultivation at all, and there was certainly no way that he could've risen up to become the number one cultivator of the human race that was revered by the entire Spirit Realm.

If there were one thing that had accompanied him throughout his entire cultivation journey, then it was undoubtedly this Heaven Controlling Vial. [2]

During the 300 years in which he had been unconscious following his ascension to the Immortal Realm, he had lost Daoist Xie, the Gold Devouring Beetle Monarch, and many of his past allies and assets, but he had always been unconsciously protecting this vial, not allowing himself to part with it.

When it came to this vial, he felt a special type of attachment to it.

All of a sudden, Han Li raised an eyebrow, and he stopped stroking the vial as a peculiar look appeared on his face.

His brows furrowed slightly as he pulled out the stopper before looking into the vial, and a hint of surprise and elation surfaced in his eyes.

He then immediately replaced the stopper on the vial before rushing out of the secret chamber.

[1]. For more on the Seven Mysteries Sect and the God Hand Valley, please refer to RMJI Chapter 3: Seven Mysteries Sect and RMJI Chapter 5: Doctor Mo, respectively.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on the Heaven Controlling Vial, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2430: Heaven Controlling Vial.

[Back]

Chapter 42: Recovering Something That was Lost

In the pill refinement chamber of the cave abode, Han Li removed the stopper of the Heaven Controlling Vial once again, then set it down onto the ground next to the pill furnace. After that, he took a few steps backward, then raised a hand to release an incantation seal to activate the array beneath the furnace, embroiling the furnace in scorching flames.

Moments later, he took a deep breath, then extended a finger before beckoning toward the pill furnace.

A ball of crimson fire flew out from beneath the furnace, circling around in the air before forming a thin line of fire that resembled a small snake, which flew into the Heaven Controlling Vial at Han Li's behest.

Red light flashed within the vial, and immediately thereafter, it became illuminated with dazzling radiance. The leaf patterns on its surface began to glow with a dark red hue, and they were flashing as if they had sprung to life.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he stood still on the spot in a contemplative silence.

A short while later, the red light within the vial suddenly faded, and the vial returned to normal as if nothing had happened.

However, Han Li's gaze remained fixed on the vial, as if he were waiting for something.

Time slowly passed by, and around 15 minutes later, he raised a hand once again, drawing a slightly larger ball of fire out of the pill furnace before sending it flying into the small vial.

Once again, red light flashed momentarily within the vial before fading away.

However, this time, the red light seemed to have lingered for a slightly longer duration than last time.

A thoughtful look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

He continued to guide fire into the vial, and the intervals between each injection of fire were getting shorter and shorter.

Just as expected, the duration of the red light lingering in the vial was also growing longer and longer.

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li injected another burst of fire into the vial, and this time, the red light within the vial flashed for a full 15 minutes without displaying any signs of fading.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a clear cry rang out from within the vial, and traces of silver light appeared, devouring the red light at a rapid rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

In the next instant, a burst of piercing silver light erupted out of the opening of the vial, flying all the way up to the top of the pill refinement chamber, where it crashed into the ceiling with a dull thump.

The burst of silver light tumbled down slightly as a result of the impact, and the silver radiance that it was releasing illuminated the entire pill refinement chamber.

Blue light flashed through Han Li's eyes as he looked up at the burst of silver light, and an elated look appeared on his face, but his brows then immediately furrowed slightly.

The burst of white light circled through the air a few times, then transformed into a small silver bird with a body that was entirely comprised of flames, which spread its wings and flew down directly toward Han Li.

Han Li raised a hand, and the silver fire raven drew to an elegant halt around half a foot above his palm, then began to fly around his index finger while chirping joyfully, seemingly elated to be reunited with its master.

This fiery bird was none other than the Essence Fire Raven, which had been born after Han Li's Flame of Essence had developed a hint of spiritual nature. [1]

Back when he was in the Human Realm, he had attained the Purple Apex Flame using the Celestial Blue Flame with the glacial qi released by the Six-winged Frost Centipede, then fused the Purple Apex Flame into the Greatyin True Flame. After arriving in the Spirit Realm, he had then used the Greatyin True Flame to devour a large number of other flames, finally giving rise to this Flame of Essence. [2]

Not only was this flame naturally capable of devouring all types of spirit flames, it was extremely effective when it came to taming fire-attribute spirit beasts, and it was one of the most important assets that had allowed him to reign supreme in the Spirit Realm.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh as he cast aside that train of thought, then raised his hand slightly, and the fire raven instantly folded its wings, landing obediently on his palm.

For some reason, he was unable to sense this flame since his awakening, and he had thought that the reason for this was that it had been lost to him, but as it turned out, the flame had been in a state of slumber in his Heaven Controlling Vial this entire time.

Back in the secret chamber, his spiritual sense had suddenly developed a faint connection with this flame, and that was why he had immediately rushed to the pill refinement chamber to try and use the flame of the furnace to awaken the fire raven. To his surprise, he was able to succeed on the first try.

However, there was a rather grim look in his eyes as he inspected the silver fire raven dancing over his palm.

In its current form, the fire raven wasn't even three inches tall, and its aura was significantly diminished compared with when it was at its peak.

This only served to further exacerbate the frustration that Han Li had been feeling.

It was clear that the current state of the fire raven had something to do with the circumstances that had led to his memory loss and the debilitation of his powers.

Han Li vowed to himself there and then that no matter who it was that had reduced him to this state, he was going to repay the favor with interest.

Moments later, he cast aside that train of thought, then released a burst of azure light out of his sleeve to draw the silver fire raven into his body.

The fire raven was most likely going to have to be nurtured in his body for quite some time before it could recover to any semblance of its former glory.

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li departed from his cave abode again, arriving at the northwestern corner of his spirit farm.

He swept his spiritual sense through the area to ensure that nothing was amiss, then raised his hand and released a series of small triangular flags with a flick of his wrist, marking out a circular area.

He then began to chant an incantation while making a hand seal, and the small flags instantly flashed with purple light, forming an indistinct light barrier that encompassed the entire area.

After that, he stepped into the area, and the purple radiance glowing from the light barrier vanished as it completely faded into the darkness of the night.

If anyone were to pass by near Han Li's cave abode at this time, they wouldn't be able to sense anything unless they were at least at the Deity Transformation Stage, but a cultivator of that caliber would immediately be detected by Han Li and dealt with accordingly.

Inside the light barrier, Han Li swept a hand through the air, and around two dozen beautiful wooden boxes appeared, hovering in front of him.

He raised his hand, and the lids of all of the wooden boxes flew up at his behest, allowing a medicinal aroma to waft through the air.

The wooden boxes contained several dozen white spirit medicines with complete root systems, and they flew out of their boxes before descending onto the ground and taking root in the soil.

These spirit medicines were a little similar in appearance to regular ginseng, but in reality, they were all Cloud Crane Herbs that were roughly around 100 years old.

During the daytime in these past few days, Han Li had made several visits to the Trade Valley, purchasing all of the Cloud Crane Herbs that he could find.

In order to avoid attracting attention, he made sure to conceal his cultivation base and don a different disguise for each visit.

After taking a glance at the Cloud Crane Herbs that had been planted into the ground, Han Li pulled out the Heaven Controlling Vial again.

He took a deep breath before removing the stopper of the vial, then tipped the vial over, aiming its opening at the Cloud Crane Herb directly below him.

The green liquid slowly flowed out of the mouth of the vial before dripping down onto the Cloud Crane Herb.

The liquid then slowly seeped into the roots of the Cloud Crane Herb, and a faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, following which he departed from under the light barrier.

[1]. For more information on the Essence Fire Raven and the Flame of Essence, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2434: Heavenly Devil Contract.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on the Celestial Blue Flame, the Six-winged Frost Centipede, the Purple Apex Flame, and the Greatyin True Flame, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1113: Dark Water and Profound Jade, RMJI Chapter 667: Six-Winged Frost Centipede, RMJI Chapter 731: Purple Apex Flames, and RMJI Chapter 1109: Capturing the Nascent Soul, respectively.

[Back]

Chapter 43: Vengeance Exacted

The seasons quickly passed by, and two years flew by in the blink of an eye.

To the northwest of the Prosperous Nation was the Bloodlight Mountain Range, which stretched for thousands of kilometers. The spiritual qi here wasn't very abundant, and the mountain range was filled with barren mountains, as well as deep, misty valleys.

Inside a certain massive dark red valley in the mountain range was a dense cluster of buildings, and some red-robed cultivators were occasionally flying through the air at low altitudes, while others were making their way in and out of the buildings with urgent expressions.

Inside a large hall deep in the valley, a blue-robed middle-aged man was pacing back and forth in an agitated manner, raising his head from time to time to cast his gaze toward a massive stone gate deep in the hall.

The stone gate was tightly shut, and crimson light was surging incessantly over its surface.

"Has Boss still not come out of seclusion?" A male voice rang out from outside the hall, following which a burly man with a heavily scarred face strode in.

"He should be coming out soon. How are things going on your end?" the blue-robed man asked in an urgent voice.

"Reinforcements from nine branches have already arrived, and the reinforcements from the other four branches should be on their way as well. Most of the inner court disciples who were carrying out duties outside of the sect have also been summoned back. Aren't we making too much of a big deal out of this?" the burly man asked with a hesitant expression.

"In the span of just 10 days, six branches have been razed to the ground, and even the branch masters have disappeared without a trace as if they've evaporated off the face of this realm! Do you think either of us would be able to replicate such a feat?" the blue-robed man sighed.

"How is that possible? I didn't realize that the situation was so severe. The problem is that with everyone gathered in one place, we've had to cease trade in all of our branches, resulting in heavy losses of profit. I'm worried that Boss will blame you for making decisions on your own and..." The burly man's voice suddenly trailed off here, and he shuddered as if a terrifying thought had occurred to him.

A fearful look also appeared on the blue-robed man's face, but he then shook his head as he replied, "I'm well aware of all of that, but if I had delayed any further, there was a good chance that our sect would've suffered losses too severe to recover from.

“Everyone always treats us with fear and respect, but in reality, all of them are praying for our Blood Sword Sect to fall. If we display any signs of weakness, even those demons wouldn't hesitate to swoop in and land the killing blow on us."

A vicious light flashed through the burly man's eyes as he said in an enraged voice, "They wouldn't dare! Everyone knows what Boss is capable of. Don't you remember what happened to the Yu Family?

“They used to be the most powerful family in the state, yet the head of their family made the mistake of standing up against our sect, and the entire family of over 1,300 people was slain by Boss in a single night! Not even the mortals among them were spared! Now that Boss has made a breakthrough to the mid-Deity Transformation Stage, he'll be sure to crush the perpetrator with ease!"

"I'm afraid things may not be so simple. Over a month ago, that group of Shadow Cat women that was being transported by Branch Master Shi was intercepted, and over 20 people, including Branch Master Shi, vanished during the incident. To this day, they still haven't been found, and it seems that there's a very good chance that their disappearance has something to do with what's been happening recently.

“Branch Master Shi was a mid-Nascent Soul cultivator, yet even his nascent soul wasn't able to escape. That should be a clear indication of what we're dealing with here," the blue-robed man said with a grim expression.

"I hadn't heard about that at all! In that case, it sounds like the perpetrator is no less powerful than Boss. Perhaps we'll have to turn to the Heavenly Ghost Sect for help," the burly man said with an alarmed expression.

Right at this moment, the crimson light on the surface of the stone gate faded, and it swung open to reveal a white-robed man.

The man appeared to be in his early thirties and was clean-shaven with a handsome appearance, giving him an air of gentle elegance.

The blue-robed man and the burly man hurriedly fell to their knees upon seeing this.

The white-robed man made his way over to the two men with a faint smile, then said, "No need for such formalities. Get up and tell me what you have to say."

The two men hurriedly offered their gratitude before rising to their feet.

"Boss, I..." The blue-robed man stepped forward to say something, but he was cut off by the white-robed man.

"I already received the message you sent to me a few days ago. Otherwise, I wouldn't have come out of seclusion early. I don't have much time, Feng Song, just tell me if there's been any progress on the situation."

"Three days ago, the Sui State branch was attacked as well, and there were almost no survivors. In light of this incident and what happened with Branch Master Shi, we have strong reason to believe that the perpetrator is at least at the Deity Transformation Stage.

“On top of that, judging from the observations made at the sites of the incidents, it appears that they're particularly adept in using fire-attribute cultivation arts or treasures," Feng Song replied as he dabbed at the cold sweat that had appeared on his forehead.

"Almost no survivors? So that means that there were survivors, right? I told you I don't have much time, Feng Song. I suggest you don't test my patience with these word games," the white-robed man said with a hint of a smile on his face.

Feng Song's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly said, "Please forgive me, Sect Master! There was one survivor from the Sui Stage branch, and he's waiting outside. I'll get him to come in right away."

The white-robed man offered no objections to this, so Feng Song immediately turned around before calling out to someone outside the hall. At this point, the clothes on his back were already completely drenched in cold sweat.

A young man with a thin build quickly made his way into the hall at Feng Song's behest, then fell to his knees before extending a respectful salute.

"No need for formalities. Stand up and tell about what happened at the time of the attack," the white-robed man prompted with a gentle smile.

The young man didn't dare to stand up, and he replied in a nervous, stuttering voice, "Th...Three days ago, our branch was attacked late at night. I...I was unable to see the perpetrator clearly. All I know is that they unleashed some type of fire-attribute ability that incinerated the entire branch to the ground, and... and there were no survivors. Not even Branch Master Yu managed to survive the attack."

"If there were no survivors, then how are you still alive?" the white-robed man asked.

"I was away carrying out some duties for the branch, and at the time of the incident, I still hadn't returned to the branch yet, so I was only able to witness the attack from afar, and that's how I survived," the young man replied with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

"Is there anything you're not telling me?" the white-robed man asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

The young man became rather anxious upon seeing this. "N... No, Sect Master..."

A faint smile appeared on the white-robed man's face, and he suddenly reached out with one hand before making a grabbing motion. The young man's body instantly stiffened as several streaks of black light appeared above him before burrowing their way into his head like a nest of vicious snakes.

The young man let loose an agonized howl as blood gushed out of all of his orifices, but he then quickly fell silent before collapsing to the ground.

"Looks like he was telling the truth," the white-robed man remarked as he lowered his hand, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Ever since the young man entered the hall, Feng Song and the burly man had been standing with their heads lowered the entire time, not daring to utter a single word.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom suddenly rang out, followed by a flurry of alarmed cries as the entire hall trembled violently.

A displeased look appeared on the white-robed man's face as he flew toward the entrance of the hall at an incredible speed, and Feng Song and the burly man hurriedly followed along.

At this moment, the entire sky above the dark red valley was enshrouded under a red light barrier. Above the light barrier were three giant black mountains, each of which was over 1,000 feet tall with black light revolving incessantly around them.

The massive mountains and the red light barrier seemed to have been caught in an impasse, with neither side able to get the better of the other.

Countless figures flew out of the buildings in the valley before looking up at the sky with alarmed expressions.

All of a sudden, yet another giant black mountain came crashing down from the sky, causing the red light barrier to ripple violently, and finally, it was unable to withstand the pressure, shattering with a resounding boom.

The four enormous black mountains descended from the heavens, encompassing close to half of the entire valley beneath their massive shadows.

Everyone immediately erupted into a panicked frenzy, fleeing in all directions, but the mountains were crashing down far too quickly to be evaded, and looks of despair appeared on the face of everyone standing beneath the mountains.

Right at this moment, the white-robed man appeared in the sky above the hall, then raised a hand to summon a large crimson flag.

The flag swelled drastically in size, releasing a vast expanse of crimson light as it positioned itself beneath the bases of the four mountains.

The mountains and the flag clashed with devastating force, and the crimson flag shuddered violently, but it was able to keep the four mountains at bay.

"Long live our sect master!"

The disciples of the Blood Sword Sect were ecstatic to see that they had been saved.

However, before they had a chance to celebrate, a dark shadow appeared in the sky, following which another giant mountain came crashing down.

Under the combined might of the five massive mountains, the giant crimson flag was torn apart. With nothing else standing in their way, the five mountains came crashing down at an astonishing speed.

The five enormous mountains encompassed virtually the entire valley, plunging the area into darkness.

The white-robed man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he immediately flew out of the way without any hesitation, escaping right before the five mountains crashed down onto the ground.

Huge clouds of dust rose up from the impact of the five falling mountains, and the earth quaked violently while agonized howls rang out incessantly, only to be immediately drowned out by bursts of loud rumbling.

At this point, the white-robed man had already appeared above the valley, and he was looking directly up ahead with a furious expression.

There, a jade flying ark was hovering in mid-air, upon which stood an elderly daoist priest and a beautiful young woman.

They were none other than Daoist Master White Stone and Liu Le'er.

"Who are you?" the white-robed man asked as his eyes narrowed slightly.

"I'm the one who's going to put an end to your life!" Liu Le'er declared in a cold voice.

A thought seemed to have occurred to the white-robed man, and he mused, "Oh? You're a member of the Cloud Fox Race. Ah, I see, you must be that little demonic fox that managed to escape a few years ago.

“It's quite impressive that you've already reached the Core Formation Stage in just a few years. The pelts of the Cloud Fox Race are an extremely sought-after material for refining defensive treasures. I made an absolute killing selling the hides of your brethren."

"Jia Ren, I'm going to kill you!"

Tears began to well up in Liu Le'er's eyes as she made a rapid series of hand seals, and a burst of silver light flashed from her left arm, following which a silver fireball emerged. The fireball quickly transformed into a palm-sized silver fire raven, which flew directly toward the white-robed man.

While Jia Ren was speaking, he had already released his spiritual sense to sweep through the surrounding area in a radius of several hundred kilometers, but he didn't discover any cultivators at or above the Deity Transformation Stage.

He initially faltered slightly at the sight of the completely mundane-looking silver fire raven, following which a derisive sneer appeared on his face.

"To think that two measly Core Formation cultivators would dare to challenge me. What a joke!"

He opened his mouth to release a black ring, which instantly transformed into a fiery black monster that was close to 1,000 feet tall.

The creature's form resembled that of a lion, and it was giving off an extremely violent aura as it pounced toward the silver fire raven.

The disparity in the statures of the two creatures was so vast that it was almost comical.

However, as soon as the two clashed, the silver fire raven instantly vanished into the body of the fiery black monster before shooting out the other end.

The fiery black monster's body instantly stiffened, then exploded with a resounding boom.

Jia Ren's eyes widened with incredulity upon seeing this, but he immediately reacted, turning around to flee from the silver fire raven. At the same time, light flashed all over his body, and he was instantly encased in a suit of glowing crimson armor.

However, the silver fire raven was incredibly fast, catching up to him in an instant before piercing through his body, completely bypassing the suit of crimson armor.

Jia Ren didn't even get a chance to cry out before he erupted into flames, and even the treasures and magic tools that he was carrying were quickly incinerated into ashes along with his body.

The silver fire raven circled around in the sky, then opened its mouth to blast a wave of silver flames down onto the valley below.

As the wave of silver flames descended, it expanded rapidly, and by the time it descended upon the valley, it had already swelled to become a raging sea of silver fire.

With the five giant mountains in place, none of the people in the valley were able to escape in a short time.

Liu Le'er looked down at the sea of scorching flames, and her vision was already blurry with tears.

"Father, Mother, Big Brother, Big Sister... I've finally avenged you all and erased the Blood Sword Sect off the face of this realm," she murmured to herself.

"Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Liu," Daoist Master White Stone said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"It's all thanks to the help that you've given me these past years, Fellow Daoist White Stone. Brother Rock told me that he'll remember everything that you've done," Liu Le'er replied as she wiped her tears away before extending a curtsey toward Daoist Master White Stone.

"I wouldn't dare to expect anything from Senior Han. I'm merely doing what I've been told to do," Daoist Master White Stone hurriedly replied.

Chapter 44: Origin Separation Law Chains

Meanwhile, on the Cloudrise Peak of the Spirit Flame Mountain Range.

The interior of a certain secret chamber in a secluded cave abode was completely illuminated by dazzling white radiance.

A huge human-shaped white cocoon was situated at the center of the secret chamber, and its surface was riddled with thin threads of white light, forming countless layers that were stacked up on top of one another.

All of a sudden, the array on the ground began to glow brightly, particularly the nebula diagram beneath the white cocoon, filling the entire secret chamber with even brighter radiance.

The threads of light on the surface of the white cocoon instantly began to squirm incessantly as if they had sprung to life, and immediately thereafter, countless white runes appeared on the cocoon before expanding at an incredible speed.

Moments later, the cocoon exploded with an earth-shattering boom, revealing a young man who was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed.

The young man's upper body was completely bare, but there was a cloud of white qi all around him, and it was none other than Han Li.

All of a sudden, he opened his eyes, which were flashing with blue light, and an astonishingly powerful aura erupted out of his body to dispel the white qi around him.

Five dazzling specks of blue light could be seen on his chest and abdomen, each of which contained a starlight rune that was revolving and shimmering incessantly.

The flesh, tendons, and bones under his skin were also glowing faintly, making it appear as if his body were holding countless stars.

A short while later, as the starlight runes gradually faded, the radiance emanating from his body also slowly disappeared.

Han Li exhaled deeply, and a hint of irrepressible excitement welled up in his heart.

After two years of grueling cultivation, he had finally successfully manifested a fifth profound aperture, mastering the fifth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

The progress that he was making was hundreds of times faster than what the average cultivator could expect, but what excited him the most was that his physical injuries had finally been completely healed, and his spiritual sense had also been restored to around a third of what it had been at his peak.

As he assessed these changes in his body, he flipped a hand over to produce a light blue spirit herb that resembled a piece of ginseng, then placed it into his mouth and began chewing.

Even though his dantian was slowly being replenished with magic power, a wry smile appeared on his face.

With the help of the Heaven Controlling Vial, he had already accumulated quite a large collection of Cloud Crane Herbs that were 500 to 600 years old during the past two years.

In his current state, this was already enough, and anything beyond that would simply go to waste.

Not long ago, he had conducted an experiment, maturing a Cloud Crane Herb all the way to 10,000 years old before consuming it. However, as soon as the magic power yielded by the herb went beyond the Nascent Soul Stage threshold, the superfluous magic power simply dissipated without providing any benefit to the recovery of his cultivation base.

Han Li shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought, then closed his eyes to inspect his own internal condition. As a result, he discovered that the mist within his dantian had clearly become far thinner and more sparse.

This was a very encouraging sight, and he quickly tracked down his nascent soul using the golden light that it was giving off, then projected his spiritual sense toward it. The nascent soul was still in its original posture and remained in a state of slumber.

Han Li hesitated momentarily upon seeing this, then manifested a series of thin threads of spiritual sense in his dantian, which slowly approached the nascent soul at his behest.

As soon as the spiritual sense threads drew close to the nascent soul, they instantly accelerated, piercing directly toward it like a storm of steel needles.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out as an arc of black light swept out of the nascent soul's body, keeping all of the spiritual sense threads at bay.

Han Li's body shuddered, and he gave a muffled groan as his dantian churned violently.

After some more hesitation, he gritted his teeth before turning to his Spirit Refinement Technique.

His spiritual sense instantly filled the entirety of his dantian, and the number of spiritual sense threads increased dramatically, forming a formidable wave that struck the arc of black light with devastating force.

The arc of black light only managed to withstand the assault momentarily before dissipating into a plume of black smoke.

The wave of spiritual sense threads instantly inundated the miniature golden figure, and Han Li's spiritual sense was finally able to enter his nascent soul.

However, the sight that he was greeted by was far from a pleasant one.

There were eight inky-black chains that were glowing faintly spreading throughout the inside of his nascent soul's body.

These chains ran through the entirety of the nascent soul, with some of them connected to the nascent soul's limbs, while others were linked directly to its head. All of the black chains had faint black mist permeating around them, giving them an extremely peculiar appearance.

What was even more astonishing to Han Li was that these black chains seemed to be imbued with some type of unknown power of laws.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he manipulated his spiritual sense to form a small ax, which was swung down upon one of the black chains.

A loud clang rang out as the sharp edge of the ax struck the chain, and it shuddered violently before being repelled and sent flying back by some type of inexplicable force. As it was sent flying back through the air, it disintegrated into specks of light that quickly vanished.

Han Li was struck by a slight rush of dizziness as a result, but after a brief rest, he decided to try again.

Under the manipulation of his spiritual sense, a large amount of his spiritual power was transformed into a cloud of smoke that drifted toward the black chain before adhering to it in an attempt to melt away the chain.

However, in the instant that the smoke came into contact with the chain, the latter immediately began to rustle rapidly, releasing wisps of black mist that quickly enveloped the smoke before devouring it.

Han Li was still unwilling to give up and continued with his experimentation.

Meanwhile, somewhere in the Immortal Realm.

On a vast desert with a dark and overcast sky, fierce wind was howling incessantly like the wailing of countless ghosts, sweeping up clouds of sand and dust that filled the entire air.

In the distance, several dozen sand tornadoes were positioned next to one another to form a yellow wall that stretched all the way up into the heavens. The wall of tornadoes was moving forward, and as it did so, it was becoming wider and wider.

However, once the wall of tornadoes reached a point that was roughly five kilometers away from the center of the desert, it abruptly disintegrated, sending sand flying in all directions as if it had crashed into an immovable mountain, even though it clearly hadn't encountered any obstacles.

At the center of the palace stood a majestic hall that was over 100 feet tall. The entire hall was of an earthy yellow color, and there were no embellishments at all on the outside. It was as if it had risen up from the sand of the desert, and it was giving off a barren and archaic aura.

The interior of the hall was quite large, with several dozen thick square pillars distributed throughout. There were around a dozen braziers hanging on the walls, and they were giving off a faint green glow that gave the entire hall a dark and sinister appearance. With the dim light provided by these braziers, one could just barely make out a large black chair at the center of the hall.

What was rather strange was that despite the howling wind outside, no sound could be heard at all inside the hall.

On the large black chair sat a thin middle-aged man, who was in the process of raising one of his shriveled hands, causing the black chains around his arm to clank and rustle.

The man had a set of sunken cheeks and a dry and withered face. His mouth was slightly agape, revealing rows of white teeth. He was wearing a white cloak that left large sections of his purplish-green skin exposed, giving him the appearance of a discolored zombie.

Upon closer inspection, it could be seen that there was a series of thick black chains wrapped around his body beneath the cloak, and the chains extended in all directions, filling virtually the entire hall.

All of a sudden, the zombie-like man's tightly shut eyes abruptly sprang open, and a hint of surprise appeared on his wizened and discolored face.

"Come to me!" the zombie-like man commanded in an extremely hoarse voice, almost as if his throat were also filled with wind and sand.

The chains on the ground not far in front of him rustled momentarily, and an earthy yellow bulge slowly rose up from the ground, then transformed into an imposing man wearing a suit of archaic copper armor.

The man's face was dark green in color, almost as if there were a layer of copper rust growing over his skin, and he immediately fell to one knee. "How may I be of service, Patriarch?"

"In the past 1,000 years, have any of my disciples used the Origin Separation Law Chains that I've bestowed on them?" the zombie-like man asked.

"300 years ago, Master Fang Pan once used his chains to kill an enemy while serving on duty for the Immortal Palace. Aside from that, no one else has used their chains," the armored man immediately replied.

"I see," the zombie-like man mused, and after a brief pause, he instructed, "Send a message to Fang Pan. Tell him that the enemy that he killed with those chains 300 years ago is still alive, and they've reactivated the power of laws imbued within those chains."

"Yes, Patriarch," the armored man replied.

"Also, tell him to eradicate this enemy as soon as possible. Otherwise, I'm going to intervene in 100 years and recover the power of laws in those chains," the zombie-like man added in an expressionless manner as he slowly closed his eyes.

Chapter 45: That's Impossible

Inside his cave abode, Han Li slowly opened his eyes, withdrawing his spiritual sense from within his body, and there was a weary look on his face.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he flipped a hand over to produce a blue Cloud Crane Herb, which he placed into his mouth and began chewing as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Moments later, he exhaled before suddenly breaking the silence.

"Fellow Daoist Mo Guang, I have some questions for you."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the shadow that was cast onto the ground in front of him warped and elongated, following which a black-robed man with skin as dark as ink rose up from the shadow.

The man cast his gaze toward Han Li in silence, and Han Li wasted no time, cutting straight to the chase.

"Do you know of any secret technique that can seal one's nascent soul using chains that contain some type of power of laws?"

"Does this have something to do with the seal on your nascent soul?"

After the past two years of recuperation, Mo Guang had also made some strides in his recovery, but he was still rather mechanical in his way of speech.

Han Li nodded in response, then gave Mo Guang a brief rundown of the state that his nascent soul was in.

Mo Guang was silent for a moment before replying, "Judging from my past experience, in your current situation, you'll most likely have to recover your former magic power cultivation base, then rely on some secret technique to break the seal on your nascent soul. Unfortunately, due to the seal that's been placed on your nascent soul, it's impossible for you to cultivate and recover your cultivation base, so it seems to be a self-contradicting dilemma."

"I thought that would be the case. In fact, my situation is even worse than what you've just described. Even if I were to self-detonate my physical body and possess another body with my nascent soul, I still won't be able to free myself from this seal," Han Li said with tightly furrowed brows.

"I recall you recently paid a visit to this sect's scripture library. Did you discover anything useful there?" Mo Guang asked.

"I read through all of their scriptures, but there was nothing of use," Han Li sighed in a resigned manner.

Mo Guang fell silent again for a moment before replying, "In that case, I can only imagine that there are no secret techniques in this realm of a sufficiently high caliber to provide a solution to your problem. You'll most likely have to find a way to return to the Immortal Realm before you can pursue ways to remedy the issue."

……

In a lush forest somewhere in the Immortal Realm.

The forest was countless ancient trees that were over 1,000 feet tall, some of which were vibrant and thriving, while others were withered and decrepit. There were also some that were of a purplish-red color, presenting a peculiar sight to behold.

Deep in the forest was an open area that was tens of thousands of feet in size. There weren't any tall trees in this area, only patches of shrubs, creating a stark contrast with the environment around it.

However, at the very center of this area was a strange ancient tree that extended all the way up into the clouds.

The tree was entirely of a dark azure color with a diameter in excess of 1,000 feet. The trunk of the tree was extremely straight with very few branches, and there wasn't a single leaf growing on the tree, giving it a bare, pillar-like appearance.

What was even more interesting was that at some point above the tree, there were seven or eight branches growing diagonally out of the trunk, and these branches were supporting a massive gray bird's nest, looking much like an upside-down tattered straw hat from afar.

An incredibly massive bird was laying in the nest, whimpering quietly, seemingly in a great deal of pain.

The bird's entire body was riddled with arrow-like feathers, and it had a disproportionately massive head, but a rather thin neck, and there was a huge pouch hanging near its chest, which was expanding and shrinking with each breath that it took.

All of a sudden, the bird fully extended its neck as it raised its head up high, casting a wary gaze toward a certain direction, and the rate at which the pouch in front of its chest was expanding and shrinking sped up dramatically.

The forest on the edge of the open area rustled violently in three different directions, and a humanoid figure leaped out from each direction before flying rapidly toward the giant nest.

The three figures were all wearing tight-fitting black robes, and they leaped out into the open in perfect synchronicity, with even the degree of their movements completely identical. What was even more remarkable was that the three men were also identical in appearance, with all three bearing the same handsome and youthful male face.

The three were rapidly closing in on the giant nest at an indescribable speed, leaving trails of afterimages in the wake. All of a sudden, all three of them blurred before vanishing on the spot.

The enormous bird was quite alarmed by this, and the pouch in front of its chest bulged slightly, following which it abruptly opened its beak toward the southeast to let loose a deafening cry.

Incredibly powerful soundwaves interspersed with countless azure blades of wind were sent sweeping toward the tall trees up ahead.

The countless blades of wind formed an arc-shaped wall amid the sound of thunderous rumbling, and all of the shrubs in the wake of the wall of wind were uprooted before being torn to shreds, while all of the tall trees in the wall's path were also felled before being reduced to sawdust.

The remnants of all of these plants were swept up by the wall of wind, becoming part of the wall as it continued to sweep through the dense forest without displaying any signs of slowing down.

In the southeast, the two black-robed figures that had just disappeared suddenly re-emerged out of thin air before rapidly descending toward the ground.

At the same time, azure light flashed from their bodies in unison, and they instantly became blurry and indistinct as they flashed through the air, constantly adjusting their speed in a calm and methodical manner to evade all of the oncoming blades of wind.

The giant bird's thunderous roar continued to ring out, and countless more blades of wind were sent sweeping in all directions alongside devastating soundwaves.

However, the two figures were able to traverse casually through the blades of wind as if they were taking a stroll in the park, continuing to approach the giant bird as if there were nothing in their path.

As the two figures drew closer and closer, the giant bird looked down at the nest beneath itself, then let loose a despairing wail.

The fleshy pouch on its chest began to rapidly expand, becoming as large as the rest of its body in mere moments, and it was still continuing to expand.

One of the black-robed young men was furious to see this.

"You think you can self-detonate? Not on my watch!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the third black-robed young man, who had been concealed this entire time, suddenly appeared in the air above the giant bird without any warning.

He was wielding a long black blade, and with just a flick of his wrist, the blade instantly sliced through the bird's throat amid a flash of black light.

A powerful burst of wind erupted out of the wound, carrying a vast volume of blue blood that erupted over 100 feet upward like a gorey fountain.

By the time the fountain of blue blood ran dry, the pouch on the giant bird's chest had also shrunk back down to its original size. Its head was laying limply in the massive nest, and its feathers were covered in its blood.

Beneath it was a huge white egg that was tinged with traces of blue blood, and it was nestled against the giant bird's abdomen, looking very lonely and vulnerable.

The three black-robed figures jumped down from the giant bird's head in an expressionless manner, then made their way over to its two wings and its tail. After rummaging through the bird's thick plumage for a while, each of them plucked out a glowing feather.

Right at this moment, a flash of yellow light suddenly lit up from the waist of one of the black-robed figures, accompanied by a burst of urgent buzzing.

The other two immediately arrived by the black-robed young man's side, and the three figures blurred before quickly fusing as one.

Immediately thereafter, the black-robed young man pulled out a round communication plate from his waist, then injected his spiritual sense into it, upon which his brows suddenly furrowed tightly as he exclaimed, "That's impossible!"

A vicious look appeared in his eyes as he spoke, and he quickly stowed the giant egg away before speeding off into the distance as a gust of fierce wind.

Chapter 46: Two Solutions

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li watched as Mo Guang gradually vanished back into his shadow, and a wry smile appeared on his face. He no longer wanted to think about the seal that was imposed on his nascent soul.

He raised his head to look up at the starry night sky through the huge hole in the ceiling, and a short while later, he rose to his feet before making his way over to Mizar star, the sixth star of the Big Dipper Energy Gathering Array. Once there, he sat down with his legs crossed again, then made a hand seal to cast several incantation seals in succession to activate the entire array.

After taking a moment to prepare himself, Han Li closed his eyes and fell completely still.

Close to an hour later, right as he began to cultivate the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts, an unexpected turn of events unfolded.

For some reason, the starpower that he was able to draw from the night sky was several times more potent than before, and within the span of just a few seconds, six massive pillars of starlight had taken shape.

If one were to inspect the scene from afar, they would see six pillars of light descending straight from the night sky, giving off immense starpower fluctuations.

Han Li was quite surprised to see this.

He had triggered similar phenomena while cultivating the fifth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts, but they hadn't been anywhere near as spectacular. There were quite a few cultivation arts in the Spirit Domain Realm that relied on harnessing the power of starlight, so such a phenomenon wasn't all that remarkable. However, given how much of a spectacle he was putting on here, it was going to be very difficult to avoid drawing attention.

He shook his head, not paying the matter much heed as he continued to focus on cultivation.

……

In the air above a certain cave abode stood a burly man, who was looking at the six enormous pillars of light with a surprised and solemn expression.

In the next instant, black light appeared over his entire body, and he flew through the air as a blurry shadow before quickly landing near Han Li's cave abode in a stealthy manner.

The closer he drew to the cave abode, the more he was able to sense the unfathomably immense starpower contained within those pillars of light, which was spreading through the air in powerful waves.

After a brief hesitation, he decided to take a risk and draw even closer for a more thorough examination.

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out beside him without any warning. "Hold on, Luo Jun."

In the next instant, a scholarly-robed figure appeared in front of him in a flash, and it was none other than Nangong Changshan, the master of the Cloudrise Peak.

Luo Jun faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which the black light around him faded, and he immediately cupped his fist in a salute. "Peak Master, I..."

Nangong Changshan raised a hand to cut him off. "There's no need to say anything. Come with me."

Before Luo Jun had a chance to reply, Nangong Changshan sped away toward the pinnacle of the Cloudrise Peak as a streak of white light.

Luo Jun seemed to want to say something, but at this point, Nangong Changshan was already far away, so he could only follow along.

A short while later, Luo Jun descended in front of the hall at the pinnacle of the Cloudrise Peak.

Nangong Changshan was already making his way into the hall with his hands clasped behind his back, and Luo Jun hurriedly approached him.

"Peak Master, given the phenomenon that Han Li has triggered, he's definitely not practicing any ordinary cultivation art. On top of that, his origins have always been suspicious. If we don't investigate this matter properly, what are we going to do if the sect decides to hold us accountable?"

"The supreme elder personally sent me a message not to investigate this matter," Nangong Changshan replied as he continued to make his way into the hall.

A stunned look appeared on Luo Jun's face upon hearing this. "The supreme elder? Why..."

Nangong Changshan suddenly stopped in his tracks, then turned around as he said, "The supreme elder must have his reasons. All we need to do is follow his orders."

"Alright, in that case, it seems we have no choice," Luo Jun replied with a nod.

"Issue an order to all of the disciples of our peak. Tell them that no one is to approach Han Li's cave abode, and disrupting during his cultivation is strictly prohibited!" Nangong Changshan instructed.

"Yes, Peak Master!" Luo Jun immediately departed to carry out the orders assigned to him.

"Who exactly are you, Han Li? The supreme elder is always in seclusion and rarely ever makes an appearance for anything, yet..." Nangong Changshan murmured to himself as he fell into deep thought.

……

The phenomenon triggered above Han Li's cave abode didn't last very long. Close to three hours later, the six giant pillars of starlight disintegrated into nothingness.

Despite the spectacular nature of the phenomenon, not a single person from the sect approached Han Li's cave abode to investigate. It was as if no one had even noticed what was happening.

Inside his cave abode, Han Li was still seated with his legs crossed, and his eyes were already open, but he remained completely still, seemingly a little concerned about something.

The cultivation of the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts was far more difficult than he imagined. Not only was the process far more complex than it was for the fifth level, most importantly, the amount of starpower required also increased dramatically.

With his current spiritual sense, he was able to satisfy the starpower requirements, but the more spiritual sense he used, the more magic power he would have to expend.

Prior to this, the Cloud Crane Herbs that he had grown were sufficient to support his cultivation, but at this point, even if he were to constantly use the Heaven Controlling Vial to accelerate the maturation of the Cloud Crane Herbs, there was still no guarantee that he would have a sufficient supply to support his cultivation.

At this rate, if he wanted to master the sixth level of the cultivation art, it would take at least a decade.

With that in mind, Han Li's brows furrowed tightly with concern.

He had to return to the Immortal Realm as soon as possible, and he couldn't afford to wait 10 years.

Objectively speaking, mastering the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts in just 10 years was already completely unheard of. If Patriarch Cold Flame were to hear about this, his jaw would've most likely dropped straight to the ground.

Han Li stroked his chin in contemplation, and a short while later, a thought seemed to have suddenly occurred to him.

He closed his eyes as he sifted through the scriptures of the Cold Flame Sect stored in his mind.

Moments later, his eyes sprang open as a faint smile appeared on his face.

As expected of one of the three dominant powerhouses of the Spirit Domain Realm, the scriptures of the Cold Flame Sect really did contain two potential solutions, the first of which was directly tied to the Origin Realm Temple.

There were many cultivation arts in the Origin Realm Temple that relied on harnessing the power of starlight, and it was said that the founding patriarch excelled in such cultivation arts.

Inside the temple was a Star Gathering Platform, which had been constructed using countless precious materials, and the platform had an ancient star array engraved upon it.

The array had been personally set up by the immortal founder of the Origin Realm Temple, and it was far more potent than the Big Dipper Energy Gathering Array that Han Li had created.

The array was vastly renowned across the entire Spirit Domain Realm, and it was said that with the assistance of the array, one would be able to easily draw four to five times the power of starlight they would've normally been capable of.

However, this platform was an extremely cherished resource of the Origin Realm Temple, and only the brightest disciple and elders could access it. As for people outside of the sect, it was prohibited for them to even catch a glimpse of the platform.

The second potential solution was to use a treasure known as the Starmoon Mirror, the refinement method for which was recorded in one of the jade slips from the inner library.

The Starmoon Mirror wasn't a powerful offensive treasure. Instead, it was an auxiliary treasure that could attract a vast amount of starpower with an injection of only a tiny amount of magic power.

The refinement method for the mirror was found by chance in a secret area by a Body Integration Stage elder of the Cold Flame Sect.

However, there weren't many star-based cultivation arts in the Cold Flame Sect, and a huge amount of precious materials were required to refine the treasure, so even though this was an extremely precious jade slip, no one had actually used it to refine any Starmoon Mirrors.

Most importantly, the main material used for refining this treasure was the Yin Dawn Stone, which was not only an extremely rare material, but also something that the Heavenly Ghost Sect held in the utmost regard.

It was said that when cultivating the Great Heavenly Ghost Arts, the premium cultivation art of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, a large amount of Yin Dawn Stones had to be expended in the cultivation of the final few levels.

As a result, the few known Yin Dawn Stone mines in the Spirit Domain Realm were all under the Heavenly Ghost Sect's control.

Hence, access to the Star Gathering Platform and refining Starmoon Mirrors were both rather difficult options to pursue.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li rose to his feet before leaving his cave abode.

Chapter 47: Probing

It was already very late at night as Han Li emerged from his cave abode, and he took a moment to ascertain the correct direction before flying away as a streak of light.

However, he had only flown for a short while when an enormous white palm suddenly appeared above him without any warning, then came crashing down upon him.

At the same time, countless white fire lotus flowers appeared in the air around him before revolving on the spot, releasing countless flower petals that instantly encircled an area with a radius of over 1,000 feet, making it impossible for Han Li to avoid the descending giant palm.

A glacial aura swept through the area, causing the air temperature to plummet drastically, and a layer of frost had appeared on the nearby ground.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then threw a punch to release a burst of enormous power.

A string of dull thumps rang out, and almost all of the white fire lotus flowers disintegrated like apparitions, dissipating into countless specks of light.

The spiritual light on the surface of the giant white palm was also trembling violently in the face of the immense power unleashed by Han Li's punch, and the surrounding space began to warp as a burst of rumbling rang out.

The owner of the giant palm seemed to have been caught off guard by this, and the palm was withdrawn in a slightly panicked manner before vanishing into thin air.

Immediately thereafter, spatial fluctuations erupted not far away, and a humanoid figure appeared. The figure's entire body was enshrouded under a layer of white light, making it impossible to make out their physical appearance. They were holding a translucent blue jade ruler in their hand, and there were profound patterns etched all over the surface of the ruler.

As soon as the figure appeared, they immediately tossed the ruler in their hand high up into the sky.

The ruler circled around in the air before swelling to over 1,000 feet in length, and all of the patterns on its surface began to radiate dazzling blue light.

The white figure raised a hand, and the massive ruler immediately came crashing down toward Han Li with incredible might.

In response, Han Li reached out with one hand before making a grabbing motion.

Even though no direct contact was made, an enormous burst of force was still sent surging toward the massive ruler, stopping it cold in its tracks and causing the spiritual light on its surface to quiver violently.

Right at this moment, the light radiating from the patterns on the giant ruler brightened significantly, forming a monstrous projection of a creature with a cow's head and a dragon's body.

The projection opened its mouth to let loose a thunderous roar, and the blue ruler began to descend again.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he activated his Big Dipper Origin Arts. Five specks of blue light immediately appeared on his chest and abdomen, forming a clear Big Dipper constellation. However, the first five stars in the constellation were bright and dazzling, while the other two stars were dull and devoid of luster.

He then abruptly clenched the fingers of his outstretched hand together, causing the nearby space to warp and churn violently.

The monstrous projection released by the giant ruler let loose an anguished howl before disintegrating with a dull thump.

"Stop, Fellow Daoist Han! It's me, Sima Jingming!" the white figure hurriedly said upon seeing this.

The white light around him faded as he spoke, revealing a purple-robed man with a head of white hair.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he stopped right before he was about to clench his hand into a fist.

Sima Jingming quickly made a series of hand seals, and the blue ruler shrank down to its original size before returning to his grasp in a flash.

Only then did he heave a sigh of relief.

Through the spirit treasure in his hand, he was able to clearly sense just how fearsome that grab from Han Li was. If he had hesitated even a moment longer, the ruler would've at least been severely damaged, if not completely destroyed.

He hadn't gone all-out in his attack, but judging from how casual and nonchalant Han Li looked, it was clear that he had held back as well.

"What is the meaning of this, Fellow Daoist Sima?" Han Li asked in an expressionless manner as he clasped his hands behind his back.

"Please don't misunderstand, Fellow Daoist Han. I have no intention of disrespecting you, I simply wanted to test your power. After all, your agreement with our patriarch is extremely important to our sect, and I have to see exactly what our sect is getting in exchange for all of the resources that you've taken," Sima Jingming said with a smile as he stowed his jade ruler away.

"So what do you think now?" Han Li asked with a hint of a smile on his face.

"You are far more powerful than I expected, Brother Han. In addition to that, it's truly astounding that you were able to cultivate the Big Dipper Origin Arts to this extent in such a short time. There have been some in our sect who have attempted to pursue this cultivation art in the past, but none of them were able to make any substantial progress," Sima Jingming praised in a heartfelt manner.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Sima," Han Li replied with a smile. "Regarding the scriptures that I took from the inner library, I can make replacement copies of all of them once I return from my errand."

"Thank you for the kind offer, but there's no need for that, Fellow Daoist Han. Our sect has backup copies of all of the lost scriptures. All I ask is that you don't forget your promise to our patriarch," Sima Jingming said as he cupped his fist in a salute toward Han Li from afar.

"Rest assured, I won't go back on my word," Han Li replied in a calm manner.

"That's very reassuring to hear. It looks like you still have some matters to attend to, so I won't hold you up any longer, Brother Han," Sima Jingming said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Han Li didn't say anything further as azure spiritual light appeared over his body, and he flew away into the distance, vanishing out of sight in the blink of an eye.

……

In the Northern Glacial Immortal Region of the Immortal Realm.

There was a mountain that was over 10,000 feet tall, enshrouded in a dense mist that was filled with spiritual qi. On the pinnacle of the mountain stood a resplendent golden palace that was shimmering under the rising sun.

At this moment, there was an elderly man with a long beard, seated on a sandalwood chair in the palace. The man was wearing a purple and golden daoist robe, and a lotus flower crown on his head. He was holding a jade teacup, out of which he took a small sip, then raised his head to cast his gaze toward the person standing before him.

The person in question was a black-robed young man who appeared to be around 20 to 30 years of age, and he extended a respectful bow toward the elderly man as he said, "Immortal Master Tong Xu, my name is Fang Pan, and I've come here today with the hope that you can track down someone for me."

"I have no interest in who you are. Do you know the rules of this place?" the elderly man asked in an indifferent voice as he gently set his teacup down onto the table beside him.

The black-robed young man immediately took a half-step forward as he declared, "I present to you a 10,000-year-old Voidsea Purple Yang Flower, two top-grade Golden Dragon Eye Stones, and a vial of Yin Yang Reversal Elixir. Will that be sufficient, Immortal Master?"

Two intricate purple boxes and a white jade vial appeared in the air before him as he spoke. The lids of the boxes and the stopper of the vial had all been removed to reveal the contents inside.

The elderly man's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this, and he gave a slight nod of approval. "Looks like you've come to me with some sincerity. Who is it that you're looking for?"

"I'm looking for a formidable foe that I fought against 300 years ago. I thought that he had already perished during our battle, but recently, I learned that he's still alive. However, I don't know where he is right now, and I was hoping that you would help me find him," the black-robed young man replied as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Do you have anything related to his bloodline, or any clippings of his hair or nails or anything like that?" the elderly man asked.

The black-robed young man hesitated momentarily, then flipped a hand over to produce a white porcelain vial, which he offered to the elderly man as he said, "The person I'm searching for has a very special bloodline, and I was able to secure a drop of his blood essence during our battle. Would this be sufficient, Immortal Master?"

The elderly man accepted the vial before swirling its contents around, and to his surprise, the vial was unexpectedly heavy. He then removed the stopper of the vial before taking a slight whiff, upon which a hint of surprise appeared on his face.

"How strange! Who exactly is this person? His bloodline contains the powers of many types of true spirits," Immortal Master Tong Xu exclaimed.

"Truth be told, he was originally from a lower realm and ascended to the Immortal Realm. He possessed many strange abilities and was an extremely troublesome opponent. I was only able to defeat him by some strokes of fortune," the black-robed young man replied after a brief hesitation.

"I see. Come with me."

Immortal Master Tong Xu was silent for a moment before rising to his feet, then made his way toward the rear hall of the palace with his hands clasped behind his back.

The black-robed young man followed him as they passed by a beautiful golden screen, then passed through the rear hall to arrive in a secret chamber.

The secret chamber was extremely spacious with three circles of patterns engraved on the ground, clearly forming some type of extremely complex array. There were no tables and chairs in the room, and the only thing in the chamber was a large copper urn at the very center.

The urn was roughly three feet tall, and its surface was also riddled with strange patterns that connected seamlessly with the patterns on the ground.

The black-robed young man followed Immortal Master Tong Xu to the urn, then looked down to find that it was filled with black liquid, with a reflection of the two visible on the surface of the liquid.

Immortal Master Tong Xu removed the stopper of the vial in his hand, then tipped all of the blood essence inside into the urn.

A drop of golden blood flowed out of the vial, then fell into the urn with a small splash, sending ripples cascading across the surface of the liquid in the urn.

Immediately thereafter, the inky black color of the liquid in the urn began to recede in all directions, and in the blink of an eye, it had become extremely clear and transparent.

Through the liquid, it could be seen that there were circles of patterns engraved onto the bottom of the urn as well.

Immortal Master Tong Xu began to chant a complex incantation, then suddenly uttered the word "open".

At the same time, he poked his index finger against his own glabella, then pointed at the large copper urn.

A faint buzzing sound rang out, and the urn shuddered as soon Immortal Master Tong Xu's finger came into contact with its rim, following which a burst of bright azure light began to radiate from the patterns on the urn.

After that, the light quickly spread along the patterns, and soon, the entire array on the ground had lit up.

Before Fang Pan had a chance to react, he found himself enshrouded within a vast expanse of azure light.

He discovered that he was standing above a large body of water, and he inspected his surroundings to discover a lush mountain range.

"I'm... inside the urn!" Fang Pan murmured to himself as an enlightened look appeared on his face.

Chapter 48: Abduction

"Don't get distracted! You only have five seconds!"

Immortal Master Tong Xu's voice suddenly rang out from above like rumbling thunder, and Fang Pan hurriedly did as he was told, focusing his attention on his surroundings, but there was nothing to be seen aside from the scenery around him.

All of a sudden, he seemed to have sensed something, and he abruptly lowered his head, upon which he discovered a golden line of blood extending down into the body of water beneath his feet.

Upon closer inspection, Fang Pan discovered that there was an indistinct azure figure beneath the surface of the water. At times, the figure appeared close, while at other times, it appeared to be quite distant, and Fang Pan was doing everything in his power to see the figure clearly, but it was a futile task.

Right as he was about to crouch down and plunge his head into the water for a closer look, the trail of blood beneath his feet suddenly blurred before vanishing.

Fang Pan faltered slightly upon seeing this, but before he had a chance to think about anything, his surroundings suddenly became warped and abstract again.

By the time he returned to his senses, he discovered that he was still standing by the large copper urn, and he was hunched over slightly with his hands resting on the rim of the urn.

He looked down to find that the liquid within the urn was still as dark as ever, and it was as if everything that he had just seen had been nothing more than a dream.

"What did you see?" Immortal Master Tong Xu asked.

"Apologies for my incompetence, but I wasn't able to see anything clearly. The figure that I saw was quite indistinct, and I wasn't able to make out any concrete features," Fang Pan replied in a truthful manner.

Immortal Master Tong Xu pondered these findings momentarily, then explained, "In that case, it's very likely that the person you're searching for isn't currently in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. Instead, they must be in a certain secret area in the immortal region or perhaps a lower realm directly under this immortal region."

"Immortal Master, would it be possible for you to ascertain which secret area or which lower realm he's in?" Fang Pan asked with a hopeful expression.

"That's preposterous! Do you realize how vast the Immortal Realm is? You've provided me with no coordinates, and you expect me to track down someone with just a drop of blood essence?" Immortal Master Tong Xu harrumphed coldly in a displeased manner.

Fang Pan hurriedly cupped his fist in an apologetic salute upon seeing this. "Please forgive me for my insolence, Immortal Master."

A short while later, Fang Pan departed from the mountain, and he stood in mid-air with his hand clasped behind his back and a cold and sinister look on his face.

"You can run away to any corner of any realm, but I'm still going to find you to tear you to shreds!"

He pulled out a communication plate from his waist as he spoke, then whispered a message into it. After that, he pointed a finger at his own glabella before drawing his finger away from his forehead, and a light screen surfaced over his palm.

The light screen depicted a tall and broad azure-robed young man with a set of ordinary facial features.

With a wave of his hand, the light screen also vanished into the communication plate.

……

Several days later.

Inside a misty valley in the northwestern region of the Prosperous Nation, the sounds of explosions and clashing treasures were ringing out incessantly.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out as the mist exploded violently, immediately following which a streak of green light flew out from within.

The streak of green light contained a young woman with three glowing azure jade badges revolving around her body, and beneath her feet was a green jade spear.

The young woman was none other than Liu Le'er, and she didn't make it very far out of the valley before five more streaks of light shot out of the dense mist, flying after her in hot pursuit.

All of her pursuers were giving off Nascent Soul Stage auras, and even though Liu Le'er was spurring on the flying spear beneath her feet with all her might, she was still slower than her pursuers.

After about 15 minutes, the distance between her and her pursuers had been closed down to no more than 300 feet.

All of a sudden, Liu Le'er made a hand seal and stopped cold in her tracks, then turned to her pursuers with a cold expression. "Who are you and why do you insist on pursuing me?"

The streak of black light that was leading the way among her pursuers faded to reveal a burly man with a thick beard, and he glanced at the flying spear beneath her feet with undisguised greed in his eyes as he chuckled, "Don't ask unnecessary questions. Surrender now and we'll spare you from any physical torment."

The other four streaks of light split up into two groups of two, flying to either side of Liu Le'er to trap her in a tight encirclement.

The streaks of light then faded to reveal a red-faced elderly man, a purple-robed young woman, and two black-robed young men who were completely identical in appearance, appearing to be identical twins.

"What makes you think you can get away with this? Do you think the disciples of our Cold Flame Sect are easy to pick on?" Liu Le'er asked as she swept a cold gaze over her assailants.

"You sure talk big for a mere Core Formation cultivator. Let's see if you're still going to be so cocky after this!" the red-faced elderly man chuckled as he abruptly swept a sleeve through the air, and a crimson ring shot out of his hand before sweeping toward Liu Le'er as countless crimson projections.

Aside from the burly man, the other three pursuers also each pulled out a treasure, then unleashed a series of magic power attacks of different colors that hurtled directly toward Liu Le'er from three different directions.

A grim look appeared on Liu Le'er's face, but she was prepared for this, and she swept her hand through the air as she chanted an incantation, and the three azure jade badges around her instantly swelled to several times their original size, manifesting layers upon layers of badge projections that shielded her from all directions.

Four bursts of dazzling light erupted, and the azure badge projections flashed erratically as a string of shattering sounds rang out.

The light radiating from the badge projections had dimmed significantly, but they were able to keep the attacks from the four Nascent Soul cultivators at bay, much to the surprise of all five of Liu Le'er's pursuers.

"This is not a place we should linger in, so we have to end this battle as quickly as possible. Take care not to kill her," the burly man instructed, then raised a hand to release the object in his hand, which transformed into a giant black brick that was over 100 feet in size before also entering the fray.

With all five Nascent Soul cultivators joining forces, assault became even more ferocious, and the spiritual light radiating from the azure badge projections quickly dimmed.

However, right in the instant before the badge projections were about to be shattered, Liu Le'er raised a hand in an unhurried manner to summon a white silken handkerchief that was glowing with spiritual light, and it seemed to be a treasure that wasn't inferior to the azure jade badges.

The handkerchief circled around above Liu Le'er's head, releasing layers of white radiance that rippled through the air around her, encompassing her entire body and giving her an indistinct appearance.

The five Nascent Soul cultivators were quite alarmed to see this, clearly not expecting a Core Formation cultivator to be carrying so many high-grade treasures.

However, it was clear that this wasn't their first time working together, and even though there was no verbal communication between them, all of them immediately injected more magic power into their respective treasures.

A burst of rumbling rang out as the white light around Liu Le'er began to tremble violently, but it was still able to hold itself intact.

Inside the white light, Liu Le'er hurriedly swallowed a pill, then made a rapid series of hand seals with a tense look on her face.

This was the first time that she had faced several enemies of a far more advanced cultivation base than herself on her own. She was only able to kill Jia Ren of the Blood Sword Sect with the Essence Fire Raven that Han Li had sealed into her body through special means, and if she hadn't taken a pill in advance to temporarily elevate her magic power so that she could tap into more of the fire raven's power, there was no way that she would've been able to kill Jia Ren with just a single attack.

She was able to last to this point against her pursuers by relying on the treasures and pills that Han Li had bestowed upon her prior to her departure, but her situation was growing grimmer and grimmer by the second.

I can't allow anything to happen to me! I promised Brother Rock that I was going to keep myself safe!

With that in mind, Liu Le'er bit down onto her own lower lip, and a decisive look appeared on her face as she quickly made a hand seal.

A profound silver array on her left arm instantly lit up, and a silver fire raven that was slightly smaller than the one that had taken Jia Ren's life shot out of her arm, spreading its wings as it flew out of the white light in a flash.

"Argh, what the hell is this thing?"

"No..."

In the blink of an eye, both of the black-robed young men were completely engulfed in silver flames amid cries of panic and horror.

The sequence of events had taken place so abruptly that the other three Nascent Soul cultivators didn't even have a chance to react before the two black-robed young men were incinerated into nothingness. Not even their nascent souls had managed to escape.

In the next instant, the red-faced elderly man was also completely devoured by the silver flames. The protective spiritual light around him was completely ineffective, and he didn't even get a chance to cry out before he was also erased from existence.

The burly man and the purple-robed young woman were horrified to see this, and they immediately turned to flee in different directions.

The burly man's cultivation base was slightly superior to that of the purple-robed young woman, so he was naturally also a little faster.

However, the silver fire raven didn't give them any chance to escape, flying after them like a bolt of silver lightning and covering a distance of several thousand feet in the blink of an eye. It pierced directly through the purple-robed young woman's chest from behind, then plummeted straight down as a scorching ball of fire.

"Master, save..."

Moments later, a blood - curdling howl rang out before abruptly cutting off, and the burly man was also incinerated into nothingness by the silver flames.

The silver fireball then reverted back into its fire raven form before flying back to Liu Le'er, vanishing into her left arm in a flash.

Liu Le'er was quite relieved to see this, but her face had turned as pale as a sheet, and she was barely able to remain on her feet.

She hurriedly took another pill, and only then did some color return to her cheeks.

Right at this moment, spatial fluctuations suddenly erupted above her, immediately following which a black devilish claw appeared out of thin air before swooping down at an alarming speed.

Before the claw had even fallen upon Liu Le'er, the space around her began to ripple violently, and she was struck by a crushing burst of spiritual pressure.

The protective white light around her was already rather unstable, and it instantly collapsed under the immense spiritual pressure.

Liu Le'er was greatly alarmed by this, and she hurriedly drew upon her magic power to flee the scene, but in the next instant, the space constricted around her, and she couldn't even lift a single finger, let alone make any hand seals.

She could only look on helplessly as rays of black light were released from the palm of the devilish claw, forming a huge black net that quickly bound her entire body.

The black devilish claw then vanished into thin air in a flash, immediately following which a black-robed elderly man appeared in mid-air not far away.

Chapter 49: Extortion

"How did a little demon fox like you acquire such an incredible flame? Oh, I see, that Han brat gave the flame to you, right? No wonder he's so troublesome to deal with. This is quite the unexpected blessing. Looks like the heavens are smiling down upon me!" the black-robed elderly man cackled as he stared intently at the silver seal on Liu Le'er's left arm.

At this moment, Liu Le'er was completely bound and immobilized by the black net, and after hearing what the elderly man had just said, a thought suddenly occurred to her as she exclaimed, "You're Qi Xuan of the Heavenly Ghost Sect!"

Qi Xuan's smile faded upon hearing this, and a sinister look appeared on his face. "That's right. If you know who I am, then I'm sure you also know why I've captured you."

"You're trying to use me to lure in Brother Rock!"

A furious expression appeared on Liu Le'er's face, and a resolute look flashed through her eyes.

Immediately thereafter, her pupils lit up with green radiance, and specks of green light also appeared on her glabella before flashing erratically.

The elderly man extended a finger upon seeing this, releasing a burst of black light that entered Liu Le'er's glabella in a flash.

The specks of green light on her glabella were instantly snuffed out, and she fell unconscious before she could do anything else.

"It's still not time for you to die yet. Once I capture that Han brat, I'll take both of you to Hao'er's grave and burn you into ashes with my ghostly fire!" Qi Xuan harrumphed coldly in a resentful manner.

His gaze then returned to Liu Le'er's left arm, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce a red vial, which was riddled with various types of complex runes.

He tossed the vial up into the air so that it was hovering directly in front of him, then chanted an incantation before flicking his fingers through the air, seemingly preparing some type of secret technique.

A short while later, he abruptly pointed a finger at the vial, and all of the runes on its surface instantly lit up, while a burst of fiery red light flew out from within the vial.

Dozens of translucent threads flew out of the red light, then vanished into the silver seal in Liu Le'er's left arm in a flash before pulling outward.

The silver seal immediately began to glow brightly, and specks of silver flames appeared on its surface as the seal was dragged out by the threads of light.

Qi Xuan was ecstatic to see this, and he quickly made a series of hand seals.

The light pouring out of the vial instantly became much denser, and more and more translucent threads of light appeared before vanishing into the silver seal.

Liu Le'er shuddered slightly as her left arm began to spasm, and she gave a muffled groan.

More and more silver flames were dragged out of the seal to form a silver fire raven, but its aura was extremely feeble, and it appeared to be on the verge of falling asleep.

Right at this moment, a burst of azure light flashed from deep within the seal, and it was attempting to drag the fire raven back into the seal.

A derisive sneer appeared on Qi Xuan's face upon seeing this, and he opened his mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which fused into the red vial.

The vial instantly began to glow with dazzling red light, and all of the translucent threads of red light intertwined to form a pair of translucent chains that locked themselves around the silver fire raven's neck.

Silver light flashed from the fire raven, and it suddenly snapped wide awake.

It seemed to have been enraged by the chains around its neck, and it let loose a furious cry as it spread its wings while releasing a pillar of silver flames out of its beak.

The translucent chains instantly evaporated into nothingness upon contact with the silver flames, and the pillar of fire pierced directly through the red vial before hurtling directly toward Qi Xuan.

The pillar of fire was traveling at an incredible speed, reaching Qi Xuan in the blink of an eye.

Qi Xuan was greatly alarmed by this turn of events, and he hurriedly summoned a small green shield while rushing back in retreat, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake. In the blink of an eye, he was already several hundred feet away, but his left arm had been reduced to ashes as it had come into contact with trace amounts of the silver flame.

If the speck of silver fire that had come into contact with his body had been even slightly larger, he would've at least been severely injured, if not killed.

He took a deep breath, then flipped a hand over to produce a crimson pill that he promptly swallowed. The muscles on the shoulder of his missing arm began to squirm violently, and new flesh began to grow at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

After just a few seconds, his left arm had been regrown.

Only then did Qi Xuan cast his gaze toward Liu Le'er with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes.

At this point, the red vial and the green shield had already been completely devoured by the silver flames, while the silver fire raven had vanished back into the seal on Liu Le'er's arm amid a flash of azure light.

Even though he had just suffered a close call, the incredible display of power put on by the silver fire raven only made him even more determined to tame it for himself.

……

In a lush, low-lying mountain range, a series of intricately constructed pavilions and palaces were littered over the landscape amid clouds of mist that were filled with spiritual qi.

High up in the sky above a certain valley, seven or eight figures were flying through the air before landing at the entrance of the valley.

The group was led by a white-robed young man who appeared to be 16 to 17 years of age, and there was a look of arrogant confidence on his handsome face.

As soon as he landed on the ground, he immediately turned to the rest of the group. "We enter the valley right away, and this time, we can't let it escape no matter what."

"Yes!" everyone replied in unison before immediately rushing into the valley.

However, there was a gray-robed elderly woman in the group who didn't spring into action like everyone else. Instead, she made her way over to the young man's side, supporting herself with a strange-looking silver cane.

"You should go as well, Granny Sun. This Purple Cloud Sable is extremely cunning. I doubt they'll be able to capture it without your help," the young man said as he turned to the elderly woman.

"I'm afraid I can't do that, Young Master. I was instructed by the temple master to protect you at all times, and I can't stray from my post," the elderly woman replied with a shake of her head.

"You'll only be going into the valley ahead of me to capture the Purple Cloud Sable. How is that straying from your post?" the young man argued as his brows furrowed slightly.

"The Temple Master instructed me to remain by your side at all times. If anything were to happen to you, I could die 1,000 times without even coming close to atoning for my crime." The elderly woman was still unwilling to oblige.

A displeased look appeared on the young man's face. "This Gourd Valley falls under the jurisdiction of our Origin Realm Temple, and it's also virtually right next to our temple! Who would dare to stir up trouble here? Do they have a death wish?"

"That may be true, but..."

Before the elderly woman had a chance to finish, the young man cut her off in an exasperated manner. "Cut the chit-chat! If the Purple Cloud Sable escapes because of this delay, I'm going to report you to the temple master!"

A hesitant look appeared on the elderly woman's face upon hearing this, but she still held her ground.

"Hurry up!"

The young man immediately flew into a rage upon seeing this.

The elderly woman could only grit her teeth and oblige, flying into the valley as a streak of light.

The young man looked on at the elderly woman's departing figure, and he was still feeling rather angry that his authority had been challenged.

He began to make his way into the valley, but after taking only two steps, he sensed something behind him, and he reflexively turned around.

As a result, he was greeted by the sight of two mesmerizing specks of blue light, and his consciousness immediately began to fade.

Han Li slowly emerged out of thin air behind him with a purple talisman in his hand, and there was blue light flashing within his pupils.

He calmly stowed the High Zenith Invisibility Talisman away, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he made his way over to the young man.

The young man was standing completely still on the spot with a dazed expression and vacant eyes.

"Where is the Star Gathering Platform of the Origin Realm Temple?" Han Li asked.

"On the pinnacle of the Nine Palace Peak," the young man replied in a mechanical voice.

"Oh? Why is it not on the main peak, the Heaven Worship Peak?" Han Li asked with a perplexed expression.

"The Nine Palace Peak is the tallest peak, and the field of view on its pinnacle is broader than on all other peaks. This makes it the most effective location for drawing upon the power of starlight, and that's why our temple's founder established the array there," the young man replied without any hesitation.

"What are the cultivation bases of the people stationed at the Star Gathering Platform?" Han Li asked.

The young man continued to answer Han Li's questions in an expressionless manner, revealing all of the details about the Star Gathering Platform on the Nine Palace Peak.

The Nine Palace Peak was second in status only to the Heaven Worship Peak in the Origin Realm Temple, and there were always many temple elders and disciples cultivating on the mountain.

However, the pinnacle of the mountain where the Star Gathering Platform was situated was a restricted area of the temple, and access to the area was granted only to some inner court elders and a very select group of disciples.

According to the young man, the Star Gathering Platform was encompassed under a powerful restriction, and there was an indeterminate number of elders stationed there, but one thing that was for sure was that there was at least one Body Integration Stage elder there.

Han Li took a moment to process this information, then gently tapped a finger against the young man's glabella before vanishing on the spot in a wraith-like manner.

Only then did a hint of life return to the young man's eyes, and he still recalled that he had sensed something behind him. He hurriedly turned around, to investigate, only to find that there was nothing there.

He shook his head with a confused expression, then turned and continued into the valley.

Meanwhile, Han Li emerged from behind an ancient tree, and he was just about to depart when a burst of light appeared on his waist, following which a yellow talisman flew out on its own without being summoned.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this talisman.

All of a sudden, the talisman burst into flames on its own, and a blurry image appeared within the fire before gradually becoming clearer.

The image depicted a young woman slumped over a stone table. Her face was completely devoid of color, and her eyes were tightly shut in a state of unconsciousness.

Her slender wrist was currently locked within the grasp of a thin and wizened hand.

The owner of the hand was a thin black-robed elderly man who was looking directly at Han Li with a dark expression.

Han Li took a glance at the elderly man, then at the robe that he was wearing, and his eyes narrowed slightly as he concluded, "You must be Qi Xuan."

"That's right! Two years ago, you killed my grandnephew, Hao'er, then assassinated my close friend, Lu Ya. After that, you've been hiding in the Cold Flame Sect this entire time like a cowardly turtle! I must say, it's been quite the hassle tracking you down. Now that this little demon fox has fallen into my hands, are you going to save her or not?" the elderly man cackled with a sinister expression.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he asked, "What do you want?"

"Come to the Wraith Peak in the Yin Necropolis Valley of our Heavenly Ghost Sect in a month. You must come on your own, and if I don't see you there by the time a month is up, don't blame me for putting an end to her life," Qi Xuan said in a cold voice.

He tightened his grip around Liu Le'er's wrist as he spoke, and even in her unconscious state, she couldn't help but furrow her brows in pain as her face grew even paler.

A dark look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

With one final burst of sinister cackling, the flames in front of Han Li vanished, leaving behind only a ball of ash that was quickly carried away by the wind.

Chapter 50: Breaking Out of the Pagoda

Half a month later, in the Yin Necropolis Mountain Range.

There was a layer of dark clouds in the sky above a tall and steep mountain, and even though it was currently noon, not much sunlight was able to filter down from the sky. It seemed that a storm was afoot.

The mountain was riddled with trees, but these trees weren't of the normal bright green variety. Instead, these trees were of a much darker green color, making the entire mountain appear as if it had come straight out of an ink painting.

Right at this moment, a rift was suddenly opened up in the dark clouds in the sky, and a streak of light shot out, revealing a tall and broad azure-robed young man.

It was none other than Han Li, and he hovered in mid-air as he briefly inspected his surroundings, then closed his eyes to release his spiritual sense over the entire mountain.

Moments later, his eyes sprang open, and a peculiar look appeared on his face. He then continued to fly through the air before descending toward a misty forest.

After landing on the ground, he made his way forward and skirted around an ancient tree, upon which he caught sight of a petite figure in the mist, laying diagonally against a dead tree in a completely still manner.

"Le'er," he called out as his brows furrowed slightly.

The petite figure stirred slightly upon hearing his voice, and her eyelashes fluttered, following which her eyes slowly opened.

In the instant that she caught sight of Han Li, an elated look appeared on her pale face, and despite her condition, she still put on a feeble smile. She then opened her mouth to say something, but a restriction seemed to have been placed upon her mouth, making her unable to utter any intelligible words.

"It's alright, I'm here now," Han Li consoled as he slowly made his way toward her.

A thought seemed to have suddenly occurred to Liu Le'er upon seeing this, and a horrified look appeared in her eyes as she frantically shook her head at Han Li.

However, Han Li paid no heed to this and continued to advance toward her. In her desperation, she tried to struggle into an upright position, but a burst of loud crackling suddenly rang out around her.

A series of chains that were flashing with arcs of black electricity appeared over her body, binding her from head to toe. As soon as she made even the slightest move, the chains would release bursts of black electricity to torment her.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged at the sight of the agonized look on Liu Le'er's face, but a hint of cold killing intent flashed through his eyes as he continued to advance.

Right as he took another step forward, an unexpected turn of events abruptly unfolded.

The white mist in the forest suddenly turned as dark as ink, and it began to churn violently. Immediately thereafter, a gust of fierce wind swept into the forest, and all of the black mist instantly transformed into a giant vortex.

The surrounding temperatures plummeted drastically, and ghastly howling rang out in all directions.

Han Li was situated at the center of the vortex, and everything suddenly turned dark around him, while a burst of suction force erupted from the vortex, trying to drag him downward.

He gave a cold harrumph as he continued to approach Liu Le'er, seemingly completely unaffected by the vortex.

Right at this moment, a burst of loud rumbling rang out from underground, and the ground on either side of him quaked violently before shattering with explosive force.

A pair of giant ghostly hands that were riddled with sharp spikes erupted out of the ground before grabbing tightly onto Han Li's legs.

Almost at the exact same moment, the black mist above his head scattered in all directions, and a burst of immense pressure came crashing down upon him from above.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as a dark purple octagonal pagoda descended from the heavens like an immovable mountain, trapping Han Li within.

The pagoda was around 500 to 600 feet tall with purple spirit patterns all over its surface, and it was giving off an indescribably sinister aura.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and it seemed that Han Li had fallen into the trap before he even had a chance to react.

A string of panicked, muffled sounds instantly rang out from Liu Le'er's mouth upon seeing this, and she began to struggle violently.

However, the more she struggled, the tighter the chains on her body constricted around her, and the arcs of black electricity surging along the lengths of those chains were inflicting such severe agony upon her that cold sweat was pouring down her forehead.

The ghostly mist around the pagoda surged, and four figures emerged around the pagoda in a flash.

One of the four figures was none other than Qi Xuan, and directly across from him was a well-built yellow-robed man, while the remaining two figures consisted of a thin middle-aged man in a silver robe and a red-robed middle-aged woman.

All four of them were Deity Transformation cultivators, and they were all making the same hand seal, which they only withdrew once they had reached the pagoda.

"It's all thanks to this Purple Nether Pagoda of yours that we were able to capture that Han brat in one fell swoop, Elder Tian," Qi Xuan said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute toward the yellow-robed man.

A pleased look appeared on the yellow-robed man's face, and he glanced at the pagoda as he replied, "You're far too kind, Elder Qi. Speaking of which, you had to pay quite a heavy price for me to borrow this powerful treasure from my master, yet you're using it to target a mere Nascent Soul cultivator? Don't you think this is overkill?"

"I did this as a safety precaution. After all, Elder Lu Ya perished by his hands, and for that, I received quite a severe punishment from the Enforcement Hall," Qi Xuan sighed with a shake of his head.

"In any case, now that we've helped you capture him, don't forget about the things that you promised us, Brother Qi," the red-robed woman said with a faint smile.

"Of course. Rest assured..."

Before Qi Xuan had a chance to finish his sentence, the giant pagoda suddenly shuddered violently along with the earth around it. As a result, he was distracted from what he was saying, and his voice trailed off mid-sentence.

"What's going on here?" the red-robed woman asked with a surprised look in her eyes.

The silver-robed man standing across from her chuckled in a nonchalant manner as he replied, "There's no need to be alarmed. My Rot Brute Ghost is in there with that Han brat. It seems like he's trying to resist and break out, but I'm afraid things won't end so well for him."

"I didn't think that your Rot Brute Ghost would already be powerful enough to shake the Purple Nether Tower," the red-robed woman said in a relieved voice as she patted her own voluptuous chest.

As soon as her voice trailed off, another rumbling boom rang out from within the purple pagoda, and this one was even louder than the last one.

The earth quaked violently beneath the feet of the four Deity Transformation cultivators, and they were struggling to keep their balance.

At the same time, a series of deep rifts had appeared on the ground, and the rifts were only continuing to expand like a system of cobwebs.

The red-robed woman's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she turned to the silver-robed man as she asked, "Is this your Rot Brute Ghost's doing as well, Brother Luo?"

The silver-robed man was just about to open his mouth to say something when he involuntarily threw up a mouthful of blood.

"Impossible! My Rot Brute Ghost has been killed..." the silver-robed man exclaimed with a stunned expression as he wiped the blood from the corners of his lips.

Qi Xuan and the red-robed women were shocked to hear this.

"It seems that Elder Qi was correct. This Han brat really does possess an incredibly formidable physical body. Having said that, there's no need to be alarmed. This Purple Nether Pagoda is a Divine Spirit Treasure. Even a Spatial Tempering cultivator would struggle to break free from it, how could a mere Nascent Soul cultivator possibly do anything?" the yellow-robed man said in a confident manner.

"That may be true, but this treasure is something that can only be used by Body Integration cultivators. With our combined powers, we're just barely able to use it, but it's still significantly less effective than it otherwise would be. If you ask me, we should go all-out right now and use the pagoda to kill him as soon as possible," Qi Xuan suggested with tightly furrowed brows, clearly still rather concerned.

"I concur with Brother Qi's proposal. We should kill that Han brat as soon as possible to avoid any unforeseen circumstances. Once his physical body is destroyed, his nascent soul will be completely at our mercy," the silver-robed man chimed in with a vicious expression.

With the decision made, the four Deity Transformation cultivators adopted the same hand seal once again as they began to chant an incantation.

All of the purple patterns on the giant pagoda immediately lit up, and countless profound runes emerged in a flash. Wisps of dense purple qi began to emanate from the pagoda, causing the surrounding air temperature to plummet even further, so much so that large patches of frost were beginning to appear in the nearby area.

At the same time, the entire pagoda seemed to have become heavier, and it embedded itself deep into the ground.

However, before the four Deity Transformation cultivators had a chance to do anything else, the giant pagoda shuddered violently once again, and the spirit patterns on its surface began to flash erratically.

The yellow-robed man's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and in the next instant, a series of massive cracks appeared on the surface of the pagoda, running down its entire length from top to bottom.

Immediately thereafter, the giant pagoda exploded violently right before the astonished eyes of the four Deity Transformation cultivators, and a huge cloud of purple mist rose up into the air.

A burst of incredibly powerful shockwaves spread through the surrounding area, and even though the four Deity Transformation cultivators were doing their best to hold their ground, they still couldn't help but be forced back. Meanwhile, Liu Le'er was also picked up by the shockwaves and sent flying back through the air.

The shattered remains of the pagoda clattered down onto the ground, and as the dust slowly settled, a fearsome giant ghost was revealed. The ghostly creature was around 50 to 60 feet in size, and it was laying flat on its back with a huge hole punched through its chest, out of which putrid black blood was flowing incessantly.

Han Li stood atop the head of the giant ghost, and he took a glance at Liu Le'er to ensure that she was unharmed, then directed a cold gaze toward the four Deity Transformation cultivators around him.

The four Deity Transformation cultivators were astonished, and the prospect of a Nascent Soul cultivator destroying the Purple Nether Pagoda from the inside was downright preposterous to them, but it seemed that there was no other possible explanation for this situation.

In the next instant, Han Li threw a pair of punches through the air, the first of which was directed toward the silver-robed man, while the second one was aimed at the red-robed woman.

Both of them felt a burst of enormous force surging toward them, and by the time they reacted to the attack, it was already too late to take evasive measures.

The silver-robed man hurriedly raised his hands, and his sleeves flared up as wide as they would go as two plumes of dense black qi came surging out.

Within the black qi were five bloodstained ghostly heads, and they opened their gruesome mouths up wide as they sped toward the oncoming shockwave.

Immediately after the five ghostly heads came a crimson ghostly seal that was riddled with Yin runes, and the seal rapidly swelled to the size of a house before positioning itself in front of the silver-robed man.

Meanwhile, the red-robed woman wore a horrified expression as she flicked her wrists in a blind panic, releasing 13 bone flying bone swords that hurtled directly forward amid a burst of ghastly howling.

She then curled the fingers of one hand into a claw before digging her nails viciously into her other forearm, tearing several horrific gashes onto her own body. Countless red blood insects that were each around the size of a grain of rice came crawling out of those gashes, instantly forming a crimson shield in front of her.

Chapter 51: Minor Spatial Teleportation Technique

A string of dull thumps rang out incessantly from both directions at once.

Almost as soon as the five ghostly heads appeared, they exploded like a cluster of smashed watermelons, and the crimson ghostly seal was also completely pulverized.

On the other side, the 13 bone swords also shattered into pieces before being reduced to dust, immediately following which the crimson shield was torn apart as if it were made from paper.

Two blood-curdling cries rang out almost in unison as the silver-robed man and the red-robed woman's bodies exploded violently.

A purple nascent soul that was around two inches tall flew out of the silver-robed man's remains, and there was a horrified look on its face as it immediately tried to flee the scene.

However, before it was able to fly away, Han Li had already appeared right beside it, then reached out a hand to catch it firmly in his grasp.

The purple nascent soul struggled and writhed with all its might in an attempt to break free, but all it took was a nonchalant squeeze of Han Li's hand to erase it from existence.

The red-robed woman's nascent soul didn't dare to flee right away. Instead, it took advantage of the distraction provided by the silver-robed man's nascent soul to flee the scene, flying rapidly toward the forest in the distance.

Han Li suddenly turned around before opening his mouth to release a burst of white qi, which took on the form of a flying sword as it hurtled through the air.

A burst of rumbling rang out within the forest up ahead, and one huge tree was felled after another.

Deep in the forest, a streak of white light flashed past, and the red-robed woman's nascent soul was instantly sliced into two before disintegrating into specks of light.

This seemed to have been a complex process, but in reality, it had all taken place in the blink of an eye.

Meanwhile, Qi Xuan and the yellow-robed man were already fleeing in opposite directions, frantically unleashing secret techniques to enhance their speed.

The yellow-robed man was standing atop a giant bone bird, and the bird was flying at an incredible speed, able to cover a distance of 2,000 to 3,000 feet with each flap of its wings.

As for Qi Xuan, he had grown a pair of crimson wings that were around 10 feet in length on his back and he was flying even faster than the yellow-robed man. At this point, he was already over 10,000 feet away.

Both of them were greatly alarmed and horrified to sense the auras of their two companions being instantly snuffed out.

The yellow-robed man immediately flipped a hand over to produce a black and red octagonal copper mirror, and black and red light flashed from its surface as it appeared directly behind him.

Even with that, he still didn't feel safe, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release nine small black flags, which connected with one another in mid-air to form a dense black light barrier in the blink of an eye, forming a watertight protective layer all around him.

At the same time, a string of cracks and pops rang out from within his body, and his clothes were torn to shreds as a series of thorn-like bone spikes protruded out of his skin, then fused together to form a suit of bone armor that covered all of his vital regions.

In the other direction, a decisive look appeared on Qi Xuan's face as he raised his right hand, then chopped his own arm off in one swift motion.

A large plume of blood erupted through the air, transforming into a cloud of blood mist that enveloped his entire body, turning him into a streak of crimson light that sped through the air at an incredible speed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly, and he didn't immediately give chase. Instead, he pointed a finger at Liu Le'er from afar.

A streak of azure light shot forth before vanishing into her body in a flash.

A series of black lightning chains instantly appeared around her, then shattered with a dull thump.

"Brother Rock!" Liu Le'er called out in an ecstatic voice.

Han Li gave her a faint smile, then beckoned to her with one hand, and a dull black talisman flew out of her body, exploding mid-flight to release five miniature black mountains that fell into Han Li's grasp.

Han Li then cast his gaze toward the two fleeing figures, and his arms flashed through the air in a blur.

Two of the miniature mountains flew out of his grasp, transforming into a pair of black shadows that hurtled through the air toward Qi Xuan and the yellow-robed man, closing down the gap at a phenomenal rate.

Black light flashed on the surfaces of the two mountains, and they each swelled to over 100 feet in size mid-flight, leaving a trail of ripples in the space in their wake.

Soon, both the yellow-robed man and Qi Xuan felt a burst of terrifying power sweep toward them from behind, much to their alarm and horror.

The yellow-robed man hurriedly tried to make a hand seal, but it was already too late.

The black mountain crashed through with devastating force, instantly destroying the octagonal copper mirror, the black flags, and all of his other protective treasures upon contact.

The bone bird beneath his feet also exploded into countless bone fragments with a despairing cry.

The yellow-robed man was then struck by the mountain, and the suit of bone armor that he was wearing was instantly shattered, while his body was also reduced to a mangled mass of flesh and blood.

His nascent soul didn't even get a chance to escape before it was destroyed in the blink of an eye by the tremendous force imbued within the mountain.

At this point, Qi Xuan was already close to four kilometers away, and he was horrified to see what had become of his final remaining companion in the distance.

Right at this moment, the other black mountain came hurtling toward him with unstoppable might.

In this dire situation, he let loose a guttural roar as his eyes turned bright red, and his body also took on a crimson hue. Countless veins bulged beneath his skin, and his entire body began to swell up like a balloon.

A resounding boom rang out, and flames scattered in all directions as the cone of fire exploded, falling down from above as balls of fire.

His body then exploded into a massive ball of crimson light, while crimson ripples spread through the air in all directions.

The black mountain arrived on the scene like lightning, but it was stalled slightly by the crimson light.

Qi Xuan's nascent soul took advantage of the opportunity to fly out of the crimson light, then abruptly vanished on the spot. In the next instant, it appeared over 1,000 feet away, then opened its mouth to release a ball of blood essence, which formed a ball of crimson light around itself.

The nascent soul then continued to flee into the distance at an incredible speed.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he beckoned to Liu Le'er again.

Silver light flashed from her left arm, and a clear cry rang out, following which countless specks of silver flames emerged to form a palm-sized silver fire raven.

The bird spread its wings before landing on the center of Han Li's palm.

Han Li made a hand seal before pointing a finger at the silver fire raven, and it instantly swelled several times in size before rapidly elongating to form a fiery silver bow with countless silver runes dancing around it.

Even though no arrow was nocked on the bow, he still grabbed onto the bowstring with his other hand before gently pulling back.

The fiery silver bow began to glow with dazzling light, then blasted several bursts of silver flames through the surrounding air. The silver flames instantly converged to form a silver fire arrow, which was aimed at Qi Xuan's nascent soul from afar.

Even though Qi Xuan's nascent soul was already close to 10 kilometers away at this point, it still felt a chill run down its spine, and a sense of foreboding welled up in its heart, causing its expression to change drastically.

"Stop!"

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out in the distance.

A speck of black light had appeared on the horizon, and it swelled to become a dark cloud in the blink of an eye, approaching the scene at an alarming speed.

Qi Xuan's nascent soul was ecstatic to see this, and it immediately changed directions, flying toward the dark cloud.

However, Han Li paid no heed to the voice as he released the bowstring, and the silver arrow was immediately fired before vanishing into thin air.

In the next instant, the silver arrow reappeared directly behind Qi Xuan's nascent soul, then pierced through it in the blink of an eye.

The nascent soul erupted into silver flames amid a horrified wail, and it was reduced to a ball of black light in the blink of an eye.

Right at this moment, the dark cloud also reached the nascent soul, and a burst of black qi swept toward it, but it was already too late.

"How dare you!"

Rumbling thunderclaps rang out within the dark cloud, and it was clear that whoever was inside the cloud was furious.

A black ghostly claw that was the size of a small mountain extended out of the cloud, reaching for Han Li with gusts of fierce Yin wind blowing all around it.

As the ghostly claw descended from above, bursts of black ghostly flames appeared on the tips of its fingers, releasing countless black fireballs that rained down in a torrential storm.

Han Li remained completely unfazed by this, and a cold look flashed through his eyes as he clenched his fist before throwing a punch toward the sky.

A burst of tremendous force erupted into the heavens, threatening to tear through the very air in its path.

All of the black fireballs raining down from above were quickly snuffed out, and the giant black claw was also stopped cold in its tracks.

Black light flashed over the claw momentarily before it exploded violently into countless bursts of black qi that dissipated into nothingness.

Gusts of ferocious wind were swept up, tearing the black cloud in the sky apart with ease.

As a result, a black-robed elderly man was revealed, and his body swayed slightly before he quickly steadied himself with a bewildered look on his face.

Han Li raised his head to look up at the black-robed elderly man, and a hint of derision appeared in his eyes.

A dark look appeared on the black-robed elderly man's face upon seeing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce a shimmering silver object, which he hurled through the air.

This was a silver array plate that flew directly toward Han Li amid a sharp screeching sound, and it abruptly exploded on its own mid-flight.

Boundless silver radiance erupted from the array plate, spreading over an area over 1,000 feet in size, encompassing both Han Li and Liu Le'er within.

Countless silver runes appeared within the light amid what appeared to be the sound of Buddhist prayers.

A thought abruptly occurred to Han Li upon seeing this, and he was just about to do something when a streak of black light flew out of the silver radiance, screeching toward Liu Le'er at an incredible speed.

Han Li vanished on the spot in a flash, then instantly appeared in front of Liu Le'er before sweeping an arm through the air.

The streak of black light was sent flying by his casual swat, revealing itself to be a black flying dagger.

Right at this moment, the silver light in the surrounding area suddenly brightened significantly, filling the entirety of his field of view.

His body was enshrouded under a certain force, and the scene around him rapidly transitioned.

Soon, his vision was restored, and he found himself in an empty and spacious area.

"That was the Minor Spatial Teleportation Technique!" Han Li mused to himself as he swept his gaze over his surroundings.

He found himself situated in a massive valley under a dense layer of dark clouds. There were tall black mountains on either side of him, with some buildings visible on those mountains.

At this moment, he and Liu Le'er were on a huge plaza in the valley, and the black-robed elderly man was hovering in mid-air above them.

The plaza was several hundred acres in area and was riddled with black jade. Plumes of black qi were surging out of the black jade, forming a faint yet resilient layer of black mist over the plaza, making the entire plaza appear as if it were situated on a black cloud.

In front of the plaza was an enormous and majestic hall, above which was a black plaque that carried the words "Heavenly Ghost Hall" in large characters.

Chapter 52: It's My Turn Now

Almost as soon as Han Li and Liu Le'er appeared on the plaza, the earth around the giant plaza began to tremble, and nine black stone pillars rose up out of the soil, encircling a large circular area.

Each pillar was so thick that the average adult human would only just barely be able to wrap their arms around it, and they stood at over 100 feet tall. Countless runes and array patterns were engraved all over the surfaces of the pillars, and there were also many glowing black gemstones embedded into them. These gemstones seemed to be some type of special spirit stone, and they were all shimmering with bright black light.

Aside from that, there was a statue of a different ghostly creature situated at the top of each pillar. All of them were extremely life-like, and even though they were nothing more than statues, just the mere sight of them was enough to send chills running down one's spine.

Dazzling black light rose up from all the ghostly creatures on top of the stone pillars before connecting together in a flash to form a hemispherical black light barrier in the blink of an eye.

The surface of the light barrier was riddled with black runes that were flashing incessantly, and countless indistinct ghostly projections were manifested amid bursts of eerie ghostly wailing, presenting a terrifying sight to behold.

Liu Le'er couldn't help but shudder upon seeing this, and she unconsciously sidled up closer to Han Li.

She was no longer the inexperienced little fox girl that she once was, but this fearsome sight was still enough to strike horror deep into her heart.

Han Li didn't even bother to take a single glance at the black-robed elderly man as he swept a hand through the air, releasing the silver fire raven out of his palm. The fire raven transformed into a silver net of fire at his behest before settling over Liu Le'er as a protective barrier.

"Stay in there, and don't be afraid."

Liu Le'er was greatly reassured by Han Li's calm demeanor.

Right at this moment, countless streaks of light rose up from the surrounding buildings before converging toward the plaza, and they were all black-robed Heavenly Ghost Sect disciples.

It didn't take long before the sky above the plaza was filled with several hundred people, and there were still more people constantly approaching from all directions.

However, Han Li paid no heed to the commotion around him. Instead, he was calmly examining the nine stone pillars and the black light barrier around him with blue light flashing in his eyes.

The Heavenly Ghost Sect disciples converging from all directions were under the impression that the sect had been invaded by powerful enemies, and they were all rather bewildered to see only an ordinary-looking young man who appeared to be in his twenties and a little girl at the center of the plaza.

However, no one dared to ask any questions after catching a glimpse of the dark expression on the black-robed elderly man's face.

The black-robed elderly man made no effort to address the disciples around him as he descended onto one of the black stone pillars, then began to chant an incantation as he released nine array plates out of his sleeves before making a rapid series of hand seals.

The nine array plates flew through the air before each of them descended onto one of the nine giant stone pillars, then vanished into the black light radiating from the giant pillars in a flash.

Even more runes surged out of the black light barrier, and it instantly became significantly thicker, while the rather indistinct ghostly projections also became clearer and more substantial.

Only then did the black-robed elderly man allow himself to heave a faint sigh of relief, but he still continued to make hand seals without pause.

Right at this moment, two particularly bright streaks of light shot forth from the distance before arriving above the plaza in the blink of an eye, revealing a pair of figures, one of which was a white-haired elderly man, while the other was an imposing man with a dark complexion.

Just like the black-robed elderly man, both of them were also Spatial Tempering cultivators.

Once the Heavenly Ghost Sect disciples present on the scene realized that there were three sect elders present at once, all of the commotion and chatter instantly died down.

As soon as the white-haired elderly man and the dark-skinned man arrived, they immediately released their spiritual sense in unison to sweep over Han Li and Liu Le'er while also quickly inspecting the surrounding area.

"What is the meaning of this, Elder Jiang? Why did you use the Minor Spatial Teleportation Plate to bring these two juniors into the sect? On top of that, you've even activated the nine Heavenly Ghost Monarch Pillars! I'm sure you know just as well as I do how much resources have to be expended just to activate this array even once," the white-haired elderly man said with a displeased expression.

The dark-skinned man also turned to the black-robed elderly man with a perplexed expression.

"You've come at just the right time! Help me power the array to refine these two at once!" the black-robed elderly man said in an urgent voice as he continued to make hand seals.

"You activated the array just to refine these two low-grade cultivators? The Heavenly Ghost Monarch Pillars can trap even Body Integration Stage beings! Is this supposed to be a joke, Brother Jiang?" the dark-skinned man chuckled, displaying no intention to cooperate.

The white-haired elderly man also refrained from joining the black-robed elderly man.

A stir ran through the nearby disciples as well, but they didn't dare to say anything for fear of irking the black-robed elderly man.

Many of them had already managed to identify that the two people trapped in the array were only at the Nascent Soul Stage and the Core Formation Stage, and even among the disciples present, there were many who were capable of killing them with ease.

However, the black-robed elderly man was a Spatial Tempering cultivator, and he was proclaiming that it was necessary to activate the nine Heavenly Ghost Monarch Pillars just to take care of such a lowly pair of cultivators. If word of this were to spread to the outside world, he would be made the butt of countless jokes.

"Don't underestimate them! That Nascent Soul Stage brat is an extremely formidable body cultivator with powers far beyond what his cultivation base suggests!" the black-robed elderly man said in an urgent voice.

The dark-skinned man was still unconvinced and shook his head with an amused smile.

The white-haired elderly man lowered his head to look down at Han Li, who was still casually looking around, seemingly completely oblivious to the perilous situation that he was in.

Right at this moment, Han Li's gaze suddenly settled on something, and he murmured to himself, "Seeing as I'm already here, why don't I kill two birds with one stone?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he sped over to one side of the light barrier, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake, then casually tapped a certain spot on the light barrier with a single finger.

An incredible scene immediately unfolded.

The entire black light barrier began to tremble violently, while the light radiating from its surface flashed erratically, and the ghostly projections within it suddenly erupted into a chaotic frenzy as if they had gone insane.

The dark-skinned man's smile immediately stiffened upon seeing this, and his eyes widened with shock.

The black-robed elderly man shuddered as he threw up a mouthful of blood, and he made a rapid series of hand seals, doing everything in his power to stabilize the array.

"We need to stabilize the array! We can't let him break free!" the white-haired elderly man yelled in an alarmed voice as he flew through the air before landing on top of one of the stone pillars.

The dark-skinned man also returned to his senses and flew toward another one of the stone pillars with a stunned expression, but it was already too late.

With one final flash of light from the surface of the light barrier, all of the ghostly projections instantly vanished. Immediately thereafter, nine giant ghostly faces appeared in unison on the surface of the light barrier corresponding with the locations of the nine stone pillars, and all of the ghostly faces wore agonized expressions as they let loose ear-piercing shrieks.

Their voices were extremely sharp and abrasive, and all of the disciples on the plaza immediately screamed as they threw their hands over their heads, while some of the weaker ones among them began to bleed out of their ears and nostrils.

After letting loose those horrific screams, countless black runes surged out of the nine giant ghostly faces in a frenzy before abruptly crumbling away.

The entire light barrier also shattered like glass, disintegrating into countless specks of black light.

Not only that but countless cracks also appeared on the statues of the ghostly creatures on top of the nine stone pillars before they exploded in rapid succession.

At this point, Han Li had already withdrawn his finger, and his hands were clasped behind his back as he made his way toward Liu Le'er amid the countless specks of black light drifting through the air.

Liu Le'er was ecstatic as she stood under the silver net of fire, and if it weren't for the fact that they were still completely surrounded by enemies, she would've already erupted into jubilant cheers.

The three Spatial Tempering Stage elders of the Heavenly Ghost Sect were astonished to see that the array had been destroyed so easily, and all three of them felt as if they had been dealt a heavy blow.

The hundreds of Heavenly Ghost Sect disciples present were also completely rooted to the spot, looking on with dazed expressions.

"How dare you destroy our sect's precious array!" the black-robed elderly man roared with fury as he opened his mouth to release a burst of white light, which transformed into a white bone blade with nine large silver rings on its back.

At the same time, he made a rapid series of hand seals, releasing five or six incantation seals in quick succession.

The nine silver rings on the bone blade clattered together to produce a disorienting sound, while countless crimson runes abruptly appeared on the surface of the blade, releasing a dazzling blade projection that was close to 1,000 feet in length, which came crashing down directly upon Han Li.

At the same time, the white-haired elderly man reached out to summon an antiquated black cane, at the tip of which was an ornate black dragon's head.

The cane circled around in mid-air before swelling drastically in size, transforming into a black wyrm with a pair of wings on its back.

The wyrm opened its cavernous mouth to release a vast expanse of black flames, while the dark-skinned man also flipped a hand over to produce a gray feather fan without any hesitation.

The fan seemed to have been made from the feathers of some type of spirit bird, and he injected his magic power into the fan in a frenzy before sweeping it vigorously through the air.

The sky instantly darkened as gusts of fierce gray wind swept through the air, transforming into seven or eight gray wind dragons that pounced toward Han Li.

With the three Spatial Tempering Stage elders springing into action, the surrounding Heavenly Ghost Sect disciples also quickly joined the fray, summoning all types of treasures while chanting different incantations.

All of a sudden, spiritual light of all types of different colors appeared all around the plaza.

Han Li immediately swept an enormous burst of spiritual sense over the entire plaza upon seeing this, sending an indescribably powerful burst of spiritual pressure crashing down upon the entire area.

All of the people in the plaza felt as if they had received a blow to the head.

Stars instantly began to dance in front of the eyes of the nearby Heavenly Ghost Sect disciples, and they immediately fell unconscious before plummeting out of the sky, falling onto the plaza in a limp and immobile state.

All of the treasures summoned by the disciples also clattered down onto the ground as a result.

In contrast, the three Spatial Tempering Stage elders possessed considerably more powerful souls than the disciples at the scene, so they were able to quickly shrug off the effects of the spiritual sense attack.

The three of them continued to unleash attacks at Han Li without skipping a beat, and in the blink of an eye, a blade projection, a wave of black flames, and the thunder of wind dragons descended upon Han Li.

Han Li remained completely still on the spot, displaying no intention to take evasive measures.

A string of resounding booms rang out, and the crimson blade projections were the first to strike Han Li's body, only to be completely shattered and revert back to a white bone blade that was repelled back through the air.

The black flames and the wind dragons also disintegrated upon making contact with Han Li's body, unable to inflict any harm upon him. In fact, even his azure robes remained completely unscathed.

As for Liu Le'er, she was also safe and sound under the silver net of fire as all of the attacks had been withstood by Han Li.

The three Spatial Tempering Stage elders drew a sharp breath in unison, unable to believe what they were seeing.

"It's my turn now!" Han Li declared in an indifferent voice as he raised his head.

Chapter 53: Scorched By Devilish Flames

As soon as his voice trailed off, Han Li's body blurred before vanishing on the spot.

"Look out!" the black-robed elderly man hurriedly yelled in an urgent voice.

However, before he had a chance to do anything else, he felt a blur flash past his eyes, following which he was sent flying back like a ragdoll as if a giant mountain had just crashed into him. He flew all the way to a mountain outside of the plaza before crashing into the mountain with such force that his body was completely embedded into the mountain face, and it was unclear whether he had survived the attack.

The white-haired elderly man and the dark-skinned man looked on as the black-robed elderly was sent flying, and before they even had a chance to make sense of the situation, two more dull thumps rang out as the two of them were also sent flying away in different directions before crashing heavily into the mountain face.

The entire plaza had fallen completely silent.

Liu Le'er was staring at all of the unconscious bodies and treasures littered all over the plaza, and her jaw had completely fallen onto the ground.

She had always known that Han Li was extremely powerful, but this still went far beyond her imagination, and she felt as if she were in a dream.

While she was still looking on with a dazed expression, Han Li arrived by her side as he asked with a concerned expression, "Are you alright, Le'er?"

"I'm fine, Brother Rock. It's all thanks to those treasures and pills that you gave me. That Qi Xuan was a really insidious bastard! Not only did he want to take your spirit flame for himself, he used me as bait to lure you here. Thankfully, he didn't do anything to me aside from keeping me prisoner," Liu Le'er replied with a hint of lingering fear in her eyes.

Han Li nodded in response, then sat down with his legs crossed before producing a white pill that he placed into his own mouth.

Even though he had intentionally held back on the spiritual sense attack he had unleashed earlier, his current meager reserves of magic power had still almost completely run dry.

Liu Le'er faltered slightly upon seeing this, then looked around with a concerned expression as she asked, "Shouldn't we be leaving this place before other people get here, Brother Rock?"

The massive commotion that Han Li had caused here had naturally attracted the attention of the entire Heavenly Ghost Sect, and many streaks of light were converging toward the plaza.

"There's no hurry to leave," Han Li replied with a nonchalant smile.

Mere moments later, several particularly large streaks of light arrived on the scene, revealing six figures that were giving off auras that weren't inferior to those of the three Spatial Tempering Stage elders from earlier.

The six of them were greatly alarmed to see the situation down below, and they all focused their eyes on Han Li.

The six of them were rather hesitant about how to proceed, and they quickly released their spiritual sense to inspect Han Li's cultivation base, then exchanged a glance with one another before retreating to open up some distance, and only then did they release their treasures.

Six treasures of different colors descended from the heavens, screeching through the air as they hurtled directly toward Han Li with devastating might.

Han Li didn't even bother to stand up, remaining in a seated position as he lashed out with his fists, throwing punches in six different directions to oppose the oncoming treasures.

Powerful shockwaves rippled through the air, proliferating in all directions.

A string of deafening booms rang out, and it was as if all of the treasures had crashed into invisible walls. Six enormous bursts of spiritual light erupted forth, and the entire space seemed to be trembling violently.

By the time the light faded, Han Li was already nowhere to be seen.

The six figures in the air faltered slightly upon seeing this, immediately following which Han Li appeared in front of a middle-aged man with a pair of narrow eyes before throwing a punch without any hesitation.

The middle-aged man didn't get a chance to react at all before he was sent flying back by a burst of tremendous force.

Five resounding booms rang out in quick succession, followed by the sound of a heavy impact, and the middle-aged man slumped down onto the ground, having fallen completely unconscious.

Han Li then sent the five remaining Spatial Tempering cultivators flying with a punch each, then returned to Liu Le'er's side, where he stood with his hands clasped behind his back.

The Heavenly Ghost Sect cultivators that were approaching from all directions were just in time to witness this astonishing scene, and they hurriedly stopped cold in their tracks with alarmed expressions, exchanging bewildered glances as they pondered how to proceed.

All of these high and mighty Spatial Tempering Stage elders were getting swatted away like flies by a completely unremarkable-looking Nascent Soul cultivator. Some had smashed deep craters into the plaza, some had been entombed in the nearby mountain face, and some had crashed through and toppled nearby buildings.

In particular, the hundreds of unconscious disciples and the treasures littered all over the ground around the plaza presented a harrowing sight to behold.

Right at this moment, a streak of white light shot forth from the distance, arriving in the sky above the Heavenly Ghost Hall, most of which had already collapsed at this point.

The light then faded to reveal a burly man in a silken robe who appeared to be no more than 30 to 40 years of age. He had a square face with a short purple beard, and he was giving off a formidable aura.

"Grand Elder Lu!"

"It's Grand Elder Lu! Thank heavens..."

All of the disciples around the plaza were ecstatic to see the arrival of the purple-bearded man, and they all called out in elation as if they had found a life raft to cling onto.

The man's gaze fell upon Han Li, and he wore a cautious expression as he quickly made a series of hand seals.

"So a Body Integration cultivator has finally shown up," Han Li mused to himself with a faint smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a miniature mountain amid a flash of black light.

The mountain flew out of his grasp with a swipe of his arm, rapidly swelling to several hundred feet tall mid-flight as it hurtled directly toward the purple-bearded man.

Even before the mountain arrived, a burst of astonishing force surged through the air.

The purple-bearded man remained calm and collected, and he was making hand seals at such an incredible speed that his hands had turned into an untraceable blur.

At this point, the black mountain had already swelled to over 1,000 feet in height, yet right when it was about to crash into the purple-bearded man, he suddenly stopped what he was doing.

A burst of dark purple light appeared beneath his feet, following which a hidden array that was riddled with runes abruptly emerged, swallowing him up in an instant.

The mountain missed its target as a result, continuing to crash toward the wreckage of the Heavenly Ghost Hall down below.

At the same time, identical purple arrays appeared beneath Han Li and Liu Le'er's feet as well, releasing a burst of purple light that enveloped the two of them in an instant.

……

Inside a secluded valley in the Yin Necropolis Mountain Range.

The space here was very confined, and there was barely any natural light. The entire valley was filled with dense black mist, and on either side of the valley were rock faces that stood at over 1,000 feet tall, upon which were engraved some strange patterns and complex ghostly runes.

Situated at each of the four corners of the valley was a large bluestone pillar, all four of which were riddled with runes and quite archaic in appearance.

Right at this moment, purple light suddenly flashed from the ground, and both Han Li and Liu Le'er appeared in the valley at the same time.

Liu Le'er was still under the protection of the fiery net formed by the silver fire raven, and she was swaying slightly from the rush of dizziness brought on by the sudden teleportation, but aside from that, she was completely fine.

As soon as Han Li arrived in the valley, he immediately raised his head to inspect his surroundings.

The purple-bearded man from before had already appeared on one of the bluestone pillars, and two male cultivators and one female cultivator were seated atop the other three pillars, seemingly meditating with their eyes closed.

The woman had a voluptuous figure and a set of beautiful features that were complemented by a red dress. She didn't appear to be very old, but she was giving off a mature charm.

The other two cultivators consisted of a giant of a man with only a single eye, and a hunch-backed elderly man.

Judging from their auras, all three of them were also Body Integration cultivators.

The three of them opened their eyes in unison upon sensing the disturbance in the valley, and they took a bewildered glance at Han Li's duo before turning to the purple-bearded man.

"Didn't you go to the Heavenly Ghost Plaza to take care of some intruders, Elder Lu? Why are you back so soon, and why did you bring these two outsiders into this forbidden zone?" the woman asked with a displeased look on her face.

"There's no time to explain! Hurry up and activate the Earthly Ghost Soul Suppression Array! That man is a Body Integration Stage body cultivator!" the purple-bearded man said in an urgent voice with a grim look on his face.

The other three cultivators were all quite surprised to hear this, but each of them instantly summoned a black badge without any hesitation.

The four of them then tossed their badges through the air in unison with a flick of their wrists.

Four metallic clangs rang out as the badges flew directly downward, instantly burrowing into the ground around Han Li.

Immediately thereafter, the ground beneath Han Li's feet began to tremble violently, and a string of thunderous rumbling rang out from beneath the ground.

The soil around him churned violently while the rocks crumbled away, and four peculiar archways erupted out of the ground, surrounding Han Li and Liu Le'er.

Each of the archways was around 500 to 600 feet tall with four pillars that were riddled with human and beast bones. A crimson skull was hanging from each corner of the archways' eaves, and they were swaying incessantly in the wind like red windchimes.

A giant ghostly head was engraved into the very center of each archway, and each of them was different in appearance from the others.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything, the four ghostly heads on the archways seemed to have suddenly sprung to life, and their eyes swiveled toward him in unison.

A vast expanse of crimson light erupted out all of their eyes, then intertwined to form a projection of a sea of churning blood that encompassed the entire area around Han Li and Liu Le'er in a radius of several thousand feet.

Situated within the sea of blood, Han Li could feel an immense weight forcing down upon his shoulders. His robes were pressed tightly against his body, and all of his movements had become slightly slow and sluggish.

Blue light flashed through his eyes, and a string of loud cracks and pops rang out from within his body in quick succession. However, he only swayed slightly under the tremendous force weighing down on him before steadying himself again, seemingly completely unfazed.

The silver net above Liu Le'er was beginning to warp under the enormous pressure, and the uppermost section of the net had caved in significantly, but it was able to hold its shape once Han Li cast a string of incantation seals into it, much to Liu Le'er's relief.

The woman in red was staring at Han Li and Liu Le'er with an incredulous expression. "How is this possible?"

"Looks like we've still underestimated him. At the very most, this array will only be able to temporarily trap him. However, now that I've brought them into the Devilish Flame Valley, I can use the Ninth Heaven Devilish Flames left behind in the valley by Patriarch Bone Flame to refine them," the purple-bearded man said as a fierce look appeared in his eyes.

The one-eyed man and the hunch-backed elderly man exchanged a quick glance, and both of them nodded in agreement with this course of action.

Thus, the four of them immediately began to make a rapid series of hand seals, and the sound of their collective chanting rang out within the valley.

At the same time, a faint buzzing sound appeared in the valley before quickly becoming louder and louder, causing the entire valley to tremble and buzz.

Small rocks began to roll down from the cliff faces on either side of the valley, and the ghostly runes engraved upon them were radiating dazzling light.

The previously rather indistinct patterns suddenly became extremely vibrant and life-like, and they quickly joined together to form a series of black fire lotus flowers.

The lotus flowers swayed as bursts of black flames were released from their petals, surging incessantly into the valley. Before long, the entire valley had been filled with a sea of black flames that completely inundated Han Li and Liu Le'er.

Chapter 54: Devouring the Devilish Flame

This black flame was rather peculiar. With the scorching heat that it released, it was as if the entire valley had been plunged into a furnace, but at the same time, inky-black devilish qi was gradually permeating throughout the area, giving off a terrifying aura.

Situated within the sea of black fire, Han Li and Liu Le'er were subjected to incredibly high temperatures, so much so that the air around them was becoming warped and indistinct.

Liu Le'er had already turned as pale as a sheet as she watched the oncoming sea of devilish flames with a horrified expression.

However, she then immediately discovered that the silver net of fire around her seemed to be releasing some type of immense suction force that was drawing in all of the surrounding devilish fire and the unbearable heat, creating a cool and refreshing area with a radius of several dozen feet. As a result, Liu Le'er was instantly feeling a lot more reassured.

Even though Han Li didn't have the silver flame to protect himself, he appeared to be extremely calm and collected as he stood within the churning sea of devilish fire.

Right as the devilish flames around him were about to sweep over his body, he suddenly opened his mouth before inhaling sharply.

All of the black devilish flames around him instantly surged into his mouth in a frenzy, and in the span of no more than two or three seconds, most of the fire in the valley had been devoured by Han Li.

The four Body Integration cultivators around the valley were so astonished to see this that their eyes almost bulged out of their sockets, and they hurriedly stopped what they were doing.

As a result, the black fire lotus flower diagrams on the cliff faces quickly reverted back to their original form, but compared with before, the patterns had clearly dimmed slightly.

Meanwhile, Han Li was displaying no signs of stopping, and only after he had devoured all of the black fire in the valley did he close his mouth before letting loose a loud burp, seemingly still not quite satisfied with the meal.

"How can any possibly be able to devour the Ninth Heaven Devilish Flame?"

"What kind of monster is this man?"

"We can't afford to hold back any longer, Fellow Daoists. We have to kill him now while he's still trapped in this Earthly Ghost Soul Suppression Array. Otherwise, once he comes out, the consequences will be catastrophic!" the purple-bearded man yelled in an urgent voice.

He raised a hand as he spoke to summon an antiquated purple copper lantern that was no more than half a foot tall, then chanted a complex incantation as he gently rubbed his hands together.

A faint purple flame was ignited within the lantern, and at the same time, countless tiny purple runes emerged on the surface of the lantern before quickly revolving around it.

A burst of dense purple smoke rose up from the lantern, then quickly swelled to form an extremely life-like giant purple tiger in the blink of an eye. The tiger was the size of a pavilion, and it raised its head before letting loose a silent roar, then pounced directly toward Han Li at an incredible speed.

On another stone pillar, the woman in the red dress was chanting an incantation, while a layer of red light had appeared over her eyes.

The red dress that she was wearing began to billow around her despite the lack of wind, and all of the skin and flesh all over her entire body was rapidly withering away at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye. The nails on her slim fingers elongated and turned black, transforming into a set of sinister claws, while the flesh on her seductive face melted away, and she transformed into a living pink skeleton.

She swooped down in a graceful manner, traveling at an astonishing speed. In the blink of an eye, she appeared directly above Han Li, leaving a trail of afterimages in her wake before swiping down viciously with one set of claws.

Spatial fluctuations erupted above Han Li, and a white bone claw the size of a small mountain emerged. The fingers of the giant claw were as sharp as blades, and they were screeching through the air as they grabbed viciously down upon Han Li's head with gray baleful qi surging out of the palm of the claw.

Even though the bone claw was also embroiled in the projection of the sea of blood, it seemed to be completely unaffected.

Han Li remained still on the spot as he casually raised a hand upward, releasing a miniature black mountain, which transformed into a full-sized mountain in the blink of an eye before crashing into the white bone claw with vicious might.

The black mountain exploded beneath the bone claw, plummeting out of the sky as a shower of giant rocks, but the bone claw also shattered upon impact.

The boundless expanse of baleful qi quickly faded, leaving behind only the countless bone fragments that remained of the giant claw.

Before the pink skeleton had a chance to do anything else, it was swept up by a devastating shockwave from below like a frail leaf in the wind, sent flying without being able to offer any resistance. The pink skeleton tumbled through the air like a ragdoll before crashing into a mountain face, where it was also shattered into a pile of bone fragments.

Right at this moment, the giant purple tiger entered the fray, opening its mouth to release a pillar of purple light that came crashing down with remarkable speed and power.

However, all it took was a casual wave of Han Li's hand to dispel the pillar of purple light with a resounding boom, following which he leaped up into the air, completely disregarding the heightened gravitational force as he appeared right under the giant tiger's belly.

He then reached out with both hands like lightning, closing his grip around the giant tiger's head with one hand while grabbing onto one of its hind legs with the other. The muscles on his arms bulged, and despite the giant tiger's frantic struggles, it was completely unable to escape his vice-like grip.

Right as he was about to wrench his hands apart and tear the tiger into two, a dull thump suddenly rang out from the ground down below, and four huge black spears that were giving off a faint black sheen erupted out of the soil, piercing through the sea of blood as they plunged viciously toward Han Li's vital organs.

A loud clang rang out, and it was as if the four spears had struck a steel wall. The impact of the strike caused the spears to be repelled back as they quivered violently.

All of a sudden, the ground split apart, and a giant black spider sprang out.

There were two rows of white compound eyes on its head, and its eight spear-like legs were as thick as human arms. There was also a gray fleshy pouch hanging beneath its abdomen, and upon closer inspection, Han Li discovered that the pouch contained none other than that hunch-backed elderly man.

The spider seemed to have grown out of the bulge on his back, presenting a very strange sight to behold.

As soon as the black spider appeared, it crossed its two sharp forelegs once again before raising them upward. The crimson light radiating from its forelegs gave them the appearance of a pair of red-hot giant scissors, which were closing in viciously on Han Li's neck.

However, this time, Han Li chose to retaliate rather than remain passive. While still holding onto the giant purple tiger, he sprang down with ferocious might, sweeping his right foot horizontally through the air during his descent.

A resounding boom rang out as the spider's two forelegs were shattered, and it was sent flying through the air by a burst of tremendous force, crashing into a mountain face before being buried under the falling rocks.

As soon as Han Li landed on the ground, he spread his arms apart viciously to tear the giant purple tiger into two.

However, things suddenly took an unexpected turn.

Instead of disintegrating into nothingness, the giant purple tiger transformed into a huge cloud of purple mist that completely encompassed Han Li.

A strong, indescribable scent was released by the purple mist, and it possessed the ability to cloud the mind and disorient the senses.

"Brother Rock!" Liu Le'er called out in an alarmed voice upon seeing this.

Not far away, the pink skeleton had reformed itself from its remains, and it stood up in a slightly unsteady manner as it cackled, "Hehe, so what if you possess a formidable physical body? Under the effects of Elder Lu's Soul Corroding Ghostly Mist..."

Before it had a chance to finish its sentence, an agonized howl suddenly rang out from the top of one of the stone pillars.

The purple-bearded man came tumbling down from the stone pillar before rolling around in agony, while the purple copper lantern fell onto the ground beside him.

The purple mist formed by the giant purple tiger faded to reveal Han Li, who drew the purple copper lantern into his grasp with a casual beckoning gesture. After a brief inspection, he stowed the lantern away into his storage bag.

At the same time, a translucent thread of spiritual sense shot out of the purple-bearded man's head before flying back into Han Li's glabella.

Only then did he turn and cast his gaze toward the archway to the left before asking in an indifferent voice, "Have you still not found an opening to attack me?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, a figure emerged from behind the archway in a flash before rapidly retreating. It was none other than the one-eyed man, who had refrained from attacking this entire time.

At this moment, his entire body was encased in a suit of spiky bone armor, and he was holding a translucent crimson ax in one hand, which was clearly also an extremely powerful treasure.

After retreating to some distance away, the one-eyed man cast a wary gaze toward Han Li, displaying no intention to attack.

He had just witnessed Han Li dominate three Body Integration cultivators at once with ridiculous ease, and throughout the entire process, he hadn't found any opportunity to attack.

He couldn't even remember the last time he had felt this helpless in a battle.

Han Li took a glance at the one-eyed man before withdrawing his gaze, then made his way toward one of the archways in an unhurried manner.

Judging from how tightly his clothes were pressed against his body, it was clear that the enormous force being exerted by the sea of blood was still acting upon him, but even though he wasn't walking very quickly, he clearly wasn't struggling, either.

Upon making his way over to one of the archways, he inspected it momentarily before suddenly bending down at the knees and wrapping his arms around one of the pillars. He then suddenly began to exert force through his entire body, hoisting the pillar upward.

The ground rumbled and quaked violently as a humanized look of shock and horror appeared in the eyes of the giant ghostly head on the archway.

The entire archway began to sway from side to side while growing taller and taller before finally being completely uprooted.

The giant ghostly head let loose an anguished wail, immediately following which the entire archway shrank down amid a flash of black light, reverting back into a black badge that fell into Han Li's grasp. At the same time, the vast sea of blood also churned violently before shrinking significantly in size.

Han Li stowed the badge away before making his way toward another archway.

At this point, the hunch-backed elderly man and the purple-bearded man had already clambered back to their feet, and the red skeleton had already returned to its original human form.

The four Heavenly Ghost Sect Body Integration cultivators were standing at the four corners of the valley, watching with complex looks on their faces as Han Li uprooted the archways one by one, but none of them stepped in to try and stop him.

All four of them were standing in silence, seemingly waiting for something.

A few minutes later, as Han Li stowed the final black badge away, he suddenly raised an eyebrow before turning toward a certain direction.

He then abruptly opened his mouth before exhaling forcefully, releasing all of the devilish flames that he had devoured earlier.

The devilish fire erupted into the heavens, then converged in mid-air to form four clouds of fire the size of wagon wheels. Immediately thereafter, the fiery clouds transformed into four fiery black pythons, each of which was several dozen feet in length, and they pounced toward the four Body Integration cultivators in unison.

The four of them were greatly alarmed to see this, and they hurriedly summoned different defensive treasures, conjuring up protective barriers to shield themselves from the flames.

Chapter 55: Explanation

Even though the four Body Integration cultivators had taken extensive defensive measures, they were still sweating profusely from fear.

The four fiery black pythons were only around 30 to 40 feet in length each, but they were manifested by the Ninth Heaven Devilish Flames that had previously filled this entire valley. As high-grade cultivators of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, they were more aware than anyone else of just how fearsome these flames were.

Even as Body Integration cultivators, the slightest lapse in concentration could've resulted in catastrophic circumstances.

Never did they think that they would be on the receiving end of these devilish flames someday.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light appeared in the air above the valley, then split up into four before descending rapidly from above, moving at such an astonishing speed that it was as if they had arrived in front of the four Body Integration cultivators through instantaneous teleportation.

These were four streaks of translucent swordlight, and they began to revolve in mid-air to form four wheels of light, each of which was around 10 feet in diameter.

In the next instant, the four fiery black pythons crashed into the wheels of light before exploding violently into bursts of black fire.

In the end, the fiery black pythons were snuffed out as powerful shockwaves swept through the air.

Immediately thereafter, spatial fluctuations erupted in the air above the valley, and a black-robed man who appeared to be in his forties appeared. He had a graceful and refined appearance, but his brows were as sharp as a pair of menacing swords.

The four swords then reverted back into streaks of white light that returned to the black-robed figure before vanishing into his body in a flash.

"Martial Uncle Duan!"

The four Body Integration cultivators were ecstatic to see the arrival of the black-robed man.

Han Li remained on the spot as he cast his gaze directly toward the black-robed man.

The man was none other than one of the two Grand Ascension Stage patriarchs of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, Duan Renli.

Duan Renli swept his gaze over the area to find that the revered Devilish Flame Valley of the sect had been reduced to a chaotic mess, while the four Body Integration cultivators were looking completely downtrodden and defeated. His expression remained unchanged, but his eyelids were twitching ever so slightly.

He then lowered his head to direct his gaze toward Han Li before extending a hand forward and spreading his fingers apart.

The five fingers on his hand instantly took on a translucent appearance, and spiritual light was flashing incessantly from his fingertips.

Countless streaks of white light shot out of his fingertips, then transformed into hundreds of white bone flying swords that were each around a foot in length, screeching through the air as they rained down upon Han Li.

Han Li made a hand seal upon seeing this, and a burst of cracks and pops rang out as his body swelled drastically in size. Countless golden scales then appeared over his skin amid a flash of golden radiance, instantly covering his entire body.

The storm of white bone swords arrived in the blink of an eye, striking him in rapid succession, creating explosions of white and golden light that completely devoured him.

Powerful shockwaves swept through the surrounding area like a ferocious hurricane, causing countless thin white rifts to appear in the surrounding space in a radius of several hundred feet.

At the same time, spatial fluctuations erupted in the air directly above the explosions, and a small black seal appeared out of thin air, then instantly swelled to the size of a pavilion before descending from above while radiating boundless black radiance.

Even before the seal had come fully crashing down, it was releasing a burst of asphyxiating spiritual pressure that was causing the nearby to twist and warp significantly.

All of a sudden, an earth-shattering boom rang out, and the giant seal was suddenly stopped cold in its tracks around 10 feet above the ground, unable to descend any further.

Duan Renli's expression finally changed slightly upon seeing this.

Even though he had just unleashed two powerful attacks one after another, all of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and at this moment, the explosions of white and golden light faded to reveal the situation down below.

Han Li was standing still on the spot like an immovable mountain with his right arm raised above his head. The arm was completely covered in golden scales, and it was holding the giant black seal aloft in the air. His feet had already sunken into the ground, and a series of rifts had opened up around him.

He looked up at Duan Renli with a calm expression, then abruptly bent his right arm before straightening it again.

A deafening boom instantly rang out, and the mountainous black seal was hurled away as if it were nothing more than a piece of wood, flying out of the valley at an astonishing speed before vanishing into the distance.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li sprang up into the air, arriving not far in front of Duan Renli in a flash before throwing a vicious punch his way.

Duan Renli's expression remained completely unchanged upon seeing this, and right at this moment, a silver ring suddenly appeared behind Han Li without any warning before flying directly toward him.

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this, and he quickly turned around while swinging his hand through the air in a chopping motion to slice the ring into two.

However, to Han Li's surprise, the two halves of the silver ring suddenly vanished, leaving only a trail of afterimages in their wake.

In the next instant, they appeared on either side of him without any warning.

Immediately thereafter, the two halves of the silver ring converged toward the center to form a whole ring once again, constricting Han Li's body tightly within it.

Dazzling spiritual light radiated from the ring as it continued to constrict, and sparks were flying erratically between the inner wall of the ring and golden scales on Han Li's skin, which were crackling incessantly, looking as if they were about to be crushed into pieces under the immense pressure.

At this point, Liu Le'er had already retreated to the corner of the valley, and she was greatly alarmed to see this. "Brother Rock!"

In contrast, the four Body Integration cultivators were ecstatic to witness this development.

Han Li didn't appear to be panicked in the slightest as let loose a low roar, and a burst of thunderous rumbling instantly rang out within his body as five specks of blue light appeared on his chest and abdomen.

At the same time, all of the muscles all over his entire body bulged, increasing his stature even further.

He then raised his arms with tremendous might, forcibly expanding the silver ring as it flashed erratically. Countless silver runes appeared on its surface, but that still wasn't enough for it to contain Han Li's unfathomable strength, and it exploded with a dull crack.

A serious look finally appeared on Duan Renli's face, and he shot back in retreat while raising his hands, seemingly about to unleash some other treasures or abilities.

Han Li certainly wasn't just going to allow Duan Renli to do as he pleased, and he abruptly vanished on the spot.

In the next instant, Han Li reappeared right behind Duan Renli in a wraith-like manner, then clenched his hand into a fist before throwing a punch.

His fist was glowing with dazzling golden radiance, and a large white rift was left in the space in its wake.

Duan Renli immediately turned around, then opened his mouth to release a crimson cloud, which transformed into a crimson light shield that positioned itself directly in front of him.

Han Li's fist struck the crimson shield, and the surface of the shield caved in significantly before it exploded into a cloud of blood mist. Han Li's fist wasn't slowed down in the slightest as it punched straight through Duan Renli's chest.

However, he knew that this wasn't the end of the battle.

In the next instant, Duan Renli's body disintegrated into a cloud of blood mist, leaving behind only a white skeleton that was dangling off Han Li's arm.

Spatial fluctuations erupted over 1,000 feet away, and Duan Renli emerged out of thin air. He appeared to be completely unscathed, but his face was slightly pale.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and the four Body Integration cultivators couldn't help but exchange a glance with one another, only to find their own astonishment mirrored in one another's eyes.

Duan Renli scrutinized Han Li in silence for a moment, then mused, "To think that a body cultivator comparable in power to Grand Ascension Stage beings has appeared in this realm in just the past few centuries that I've been in seclusion. May I ask your name?"

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Duan. My name is Han Li," Han Li replied with a faint smile, then casually cast the white skeleton aside.

The golden scales all over his body quickly faded, and he appeared to be content to end the battle there.

"I see. May I ask for what purpose you've come here, Fellow Daoist Han? As a cultivator of your caliber, you should be acting in a way that's befitting of your powers. Why have you come to wreak havoc at our Heavenly Ghost Sect and harmed so many of our disciples? I believe you owe me an explanation," Duan Renli said as his voice suddenly took a cold turn.

"It's rather amusing that you're turning this on me. First, your Heavenly Ghost Sect abducted someone close to me, then forcibly teleported me here using a secret technique. I was hoping that you would be able to give me an explanation," Han Li said with a cold smile.

Duan Renli faltered slightly upon hearing this, then turned to the four Body Integration cultivators before asking, "What's going on here?"

The other three Body Integration cultivators all turned to the purple-bearded man for an explanation.

"I received news earlier that someone had invaded our sect, so I went to investigate. I could see that this... Fellow Daoist Han was quite a formidable opponent, so I teleported him here to contain him in the array. As for why he came to our Heavenly Ghost Sect, I'm afraid I don't actually know," the purple-bearded man explained after a moment of hesitation.

"Investigate this matter right away!" Duan Renli instructed in an implacable voice.

"Yes!" the purple-bearded man hurriedly replied before flying out of the valley.

Duan Renli's gaze returned to Han Li in silence.

Han Li turned to Liu Le'er to give her a reassuring look, then turned back to face Duan Renli with a faint smile on his face.

Around 15 minutes later, the purple-bearded man returned to the valley, then communicated a message to Duan Renli through voice transmission.

Duan Renli's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing what was said, but his expression then immediately returned to normal as waved a dismissive hand.

The purple-bearded man hurriedly backed away to the side.

"So you're from the Cold Flame Sect, is that right, Fellow Daoist Han?" Duan Renli asked in a slow and deliberate voice, seemingly pondering what he was going to say next.

"That's right," Han Li replied in a truthful manner.

"It's incredible to think that the Cold Flame Sect managed to produce a body cultivator as powerful as yourself completely in secret. I must offer the Cold Flame Sect and yourself my sincerest congratulations," Duan Renli said with a fake smile on his face.

"I suggest you don't try to change the subject, Fellow Daoist Duan," Han Li replied with a faint smile.

"I've already made sense of the situation. What I've heard is that you had some differences with a now-deceased outer court elder of our sect, and everything that happened after that was all a huge misunderstanding. Seeing as that elder is already dead and the situation has already been clarified, there's no point for our battle to continue. How about we stop here, and I'll send some people to accompany you and your companion out of our sect?" Duan Renli suggested.

In his eyes, Han Li's cultivation base wasn't very high, but he had clearly employed some type of method to conceal his true cultivation base. The other Grand Ascension Stage being of the Heavenly Ghost Sect just so happened to be away at the moment, so it was unwise to continue this battle.

"So I was teleported into your sect for no reason, then had to endure attacks from countless cultivators of your sect, and now, you're telling me that this is all just a big misunderstanding and to pretend as if nothing ever happened. Would you agree to this if you were in my place, Fellow Daoist Duan?" Han Li countered with a cold smile.

Chapter 56: Rise of the Heavenly Ghost

"What do you want?" Duan Renli asked in an indifferent voice.

"I want 50 kilograms of refined Yin Dawn Stone," Han Li replied without any hesitation.

A peculiar silence instantly descended upon the entire valley with this declaration.

"You want 50 kilograms of Yin Dawn Stone?"

"You destroyed several major restrictions of our sect and completely ruined the Devilish Flame Valley! How dare you state such a brazen demand?"

"You must be delusional!"

After a brief stunned silence, the four Body Integration cultivators all erupted into furious tirades before Duan Renli had a chance to say anything.

Duan Renli's expression remained unchanged, but a hint of anger had crept into his voice as he said, "You're asking for far too much, Fellow Daoist! An entire Yin Dawn Stone mine is only able to produce around half a kilogram of Yin Dawn Stone per year, and you're asking for 50 kilograms at once! Don't you think you're going too far?"

"I don't think that at all. Surely you can't tell me the Heavenly Ghost Sect is unable to offer up at least that much Yin Dawn Stone," Han Li replied with a nonchalant smile.

"It looks like you came here with the intention of starting trouble. If you're unwilling to leave, then you can remain here forever!" A furious look appeared on Duan Renli's face as he spoke, and it was clear that he had been completely enraged by Han Li's attitude.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a vast expanse of crimson light erupted out of his body, illuminating the entire surrounding area. At the same time, he released a burst of terrifying spiritual pressure that almost made the nearby space congeal, and he opened his mouth to release a miniature crimson flag that was several inches tall.

The flag circled around in the air before swelling to around 10 feet in height with baleful qi surging all over its surface. An image of a sinister ghostly head with a pair of horns could be clearly seen on the flag, and at the moment, the ghostly head's eyes were tightly shut.

Crimson light began to surge over the giant flag as Duan Renli chanted an incantation, sweeping up gusts of wind that reeked of blood and gore. The ghostly head then opened its cavernous mouth, releasing a thick pillar of crimson light that hurtled directly toward Han Li with unstoppable might.

Even before the pillar of light reached Han Li, a nauseating stench permeated throughout the entire valley, and the nearby air temperature plummeted drastically.

Han Li abruptly vanished on the spot upon seeing this, and as a result, the pillar of crimson light struck nothing but empty air.

In the next instant, spatial fluctuations erupted behind Duan Renli, following which Han Li appeared out of thin air before throwing a punch. His fist was covered in golden scales, and a ferocious barrage of hundreds of fist projections was unleashed in an instant.

A burst of astonishing force passed through the barrage of fist projections, threatening to shatter the space in its wake.

In the face of such an astonishing attack, all Duan Renli did was extend a finger before pointing it at the giant crimson flag before him in an unhurried manner.

A vast expanse of crimson mist instantly swept out of the flag like lightning before quickly spreading through the air, transforming into a crimson cloud with a radius of several hundred feet. The cloud completely encompassed Duan Renli within it, giving him a rather murky and indistinct appearance.

The golden fist projections fell upon the crimson cloud like rain, but it was as if they had struck an enormous wall of cotton. In a strange turn of events, the incredible power imbued within the first projections instantly vanished upon making contact with the crimson cloud, and with each fist projection that landed, the crimson cloud would expand slightly.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately withdrew his fists before flying back in retreat without any hesitation.

The crimson cloud instantly swept down like a turbulent wave, then rapidly spread apart to either side, while a series of crimson vortexes appeared, releasing bursts of powerful force that swept through the surrounding air, causing the nearby space to warp and twist violently.

A string of loud rumbling rang out, and Han Li felt the air constrict around him, following which bursts of tremendous force surged toward him from all directions, causing him to slow down in his retreat.

Right at this moment, the eyes of the sinister ghostly head on the surface of the crimson flag sprang open, and two balls of red light that were as radiant as the sun was revealed, forcing all beholders to shield their eyes and avert their gaze.

Han Li felt his surroundings blur for a moment, and in the next instant, he suddenly found himself situated within a crimson space.

Above his head was a murky crimson sky, while down below was a boundless sea of blood. A faint layer of blood mist was hovering above the surface of the sea of blood, and there was a slightly sweet aroma permeating through the air.

"This is a domain treasure!" Han Li exclaimed as a hint of surprise appeared in his eyes.

Duan Renli was standing in mid-air not far away with his hands clasped behind his back, and his black robe was flapping audibly while crimson mist surged around him. "You sure are knowledgeable. Indeed, this Heavenly Ghost Blood Flag is a domain treasure, and it's the most revered treasure of our Heavenly Ghost Sect. You're extremely fortunate to be able to make this domain your final resting place."

"Is that right?" Han Li harrumphed coldly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a flurry of ghostly howls suddenly rang out in all directions.

The ghostly howls were undulating incessantly, and it was as if there were countless ghostly creatures screaming and screeching incessantly with all their might.

All of a sudden, Han Li's consciousness began to waver, and his eyelids became as heavy as lead. At the same time, a sense of bloodlust and frustration welled up in his heart, and it seemed that the bloodlust could be satisfied by engaging those ghostly creatures in a battle to the death.

In response to these intrusive sensations, Han Li made a hand seal without any hesitation, and a burst of cool and refreshing energy surged out of his glabella, instantly flowing through all of his meridians.

The deranged thoughts in his mind instantly ceased to exist, and the ghostly howling also faded into silence.

Duan Renli was astonished that Han Li was able to remain completely unaffected by the mind-altering properties of the domain.

The layer of mist hovering over the sea of blood was manifested from the resentment of countless ghosts, and it could completely cloud one's mind and tap into the innermost desires and bloodlust in one's heart. Even if Duan Renli himself were to be beset by its effects in a completely defenseless state, he certainly wouldn't have been able to regain full sanity and rationality so easily.

The fact that Han Li was completely unaffected by this indicated that his spiritual sense was far more powerful than even Duan Renli's!

Thus, one of the trump cards that Duan Renli had prepared was rendered useless from the get-go.

Right at this moment, Han Li's body suddenly blurred as he shot forth through the air, flying directly toward Duan Renli.

Duan Renli gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and he quickly made a hand seal.

The sea of blood down below suddenly began to churn violently, and an enormous wave of blood abruptly raised to devour Duan Renli,

Han Li instantly stopped cold in his tracks upon seeing this, and he closed his eyes to release his immense spiritual sense, but his brows then immediately furrowed slightly.

This space seemed to be infinitely vast, and the sea of blood down below was also extremely strange. Even Han Li's spiritual sense was only able to reach a depth of less than 200 feet in the sea of blood, making it impossible for him to find out where Duan Renli was hiding.

After a moment of contemplation, blue light flashed through his eyes as he unleashed his Brightsight Spirit Eyes ability. [1]

Everything within several hundred feet beneath the surface of the sea of blood instantly became as clear as day, but beyond that was still just a vast expanse of murkiness that was impossible to see through.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce Cloud Crane Herb that he quickly devoured, then injected most of his spiritual power into his eyes, yet right as he was about to activate his spirit eyes ability to its fullest extent, an unexpected turn of events abruptly unfolded.

The surface of the sea of blood several thousand feet ahead of Han Li suddenly began to churn violently, and the viscous blood surged toward a certain direction, forming an enormous vortex that was rumbling incessantly.

Han Li immediately flew up to an altitude of over 1,000 feet upon seeing this, and only then did he lower his head to inspect the scene that was unfolding down below.

The center of the vortex was splashing loudly, and waves were churning and rolling as an enormous skeleton rose up from the depths.

The skeleton was over 1,000 feet tall, and all of its bones were of a translucent red color, as if it were entirely constructed from blood jade. Every single bone was riddled with countless profound runes, and at the top of the skeleton's enormous head, nestled right between a pair of curved horns, sat Duan Renli's nascent soul with its eyes closed and its legs crossed.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly upon seeing this.

All of a sudden, the nascent soul's eyes sprang open, and it opened its mouth to release seven balls of blood essence in rapid succession. At the same time, it was making a series of hand seals while chanting an incantation.

The balls of blood essence exploded into seven clouds of blood mist, which wrapped themselves around the nascent soul's body, neck, and limbs like a nest of spirit snakes. Immediately thereafter, the blood mist began to radiate crimson radiance, encompassing the nascent soul within a ball of crimson light.

All of a sudden, the crimson ball of light vanished into the skull of the skeleton.

Two balls of crimson light instantly appeared within the giant skeleton's empty eye sockets, and all of the runes all over its body also lit up in unison.

Enormous waves were churning within the blood vortex down below, releasing bursts of viscous crimson light that rose up while revolving and intertwining, forming a corkscrew-shaped pillar of blood that engulfed the entire skeleton.

Through the pillar of blood, Han Li could see that the giant skeleton was gradually expanding even further in stature.

Shortly thereafter, the pillar of blood receded like the tide, and the giant skeleton had completely vanished, replaced by a terrifying ghostly creature that was over 1,000 feet tall. The creature had a pair of eyes that were as red as blood, and a pair of curved horns on its head, as well as a pair of dark purple bat wings on its back. Its entire body was covered in crimson fur, and even compared with its enormous body, its limbs were disproportionately long.

As soon as it appeared, it immediately began to release an astonishing aura that was causing even the space around it to tremble and quiver violently.

"So this is the legendary Blood Heavenly Ghost that's rumored to be from the Nether Realm? Interesting..." Han Li murmured to himself as he looked directly at the giant ghostly creature before him.

Right at this moment, the Blood Heavenly Ghost raised one of its arms, and a vast expanse of crimson flames erupted on its palm as it grabbed at Han Li from afar.

The sky above Han Li instantly dimmed as an enormous crimson ghostly claw that was around an acre in size appeared overhead, then came swooping down with scorching crimson flames burning all over its surface.

Even before the giant claw reached Han Li, a gust of ferocious wind had already come sweeping down, causing the sea of blood down below to ripple and churn violently.

In response, Han Li threw a punch directly upward, releasing a burst of tremendous force.

A resounding boom rang out, and the crimson ghostly claw was instantly destroyed, exploding into specks of crimson light and scattered flames that scattered in all directions.

However, Han Li was also forced to stumble back a few steps before steadying himself, and a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

The power imbued within the giant crimson claw had exceeded his expectations.

The specks of crimson light that scattered through the air didn't fade away. Instead, after scattering in all directions for a short distance, they suddenly stopped cold in their tracks, then converged and intertwined to form a ring of blood with a radius of several dozen feet. The ring then abruptly contracted, constricting tightly around Han Li.

Before Han Li had a chance to do anything, the Blood Heavenly Ghost beckoned to him, and the crimson ring around Han Li instantly flew toward it at an incredible speed. As a result, he was quickly drawn into the Blood Heavenly Ghost's grasp, leaving only his head exposed.

"Let's see how you're going to get away now!" the Blood Heavenly Ghost cackled as it closed its other claw around the one that was gripping Han Li, then tightened its grip with both claws.

Han Li immediately felt tremendous force constricting around him from all directions, and his bones were creaking incessantly. Even with his incredibly resolute physical body, he was struggling to withstand the pressure.

[1]. Can't find where the Brightsight Spirit Eyes ability was first mentioned in RMJI, but essentially, it's an ocular ability that significantly enhances one's eyesight and allows the user to see hidden cultivators and restrictions.

[Back]

Chapter 57: 12 Awakening Transformations

A hint of surprise flashed through the Blood Heavenly Ghost's eyes, clearly taken aback by the fact that it was unable to completely pulverize Han Li's body with its crushing grip.

However, it then harrumphed coldly as a series of thick crimson patterns appeared all over its body, and its arms bulged as it tightened its grip with all its might, determined to crush Han Li with brute force.

A pained look appeared on Han Li's face, but his body remained as resolute as a piece of indestructible iron essence, refusing to be crushed no matter how much force the Blood Heavenly Ghost exerted.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light suddenly erupted from Han Li's body, and countless golden scales appeared over his skin, while five specks of blue light emerged on his chest and abdomen.

He then let loose a low roar as he spread his arms outward with all his might, resisting against the vice-like grip around him.

A stunned look appeared on the Blood Heavenly Ghost's face as its fingers were slowly forced apart by Han Li.

With the space that was opened up around him, Han Li was able to fly out of the Blood Heavenly Ghost's grasp as a streak of golden light. His body rapidly swelled in size mid-flight, and thick tufts of hard golden fur quickly grew over his entire body, while a pair of white tusks protruded out of his mouth.

In the blink of an eye, he had transformed into a giant golden ape that was over 100 feet tall.

A violent aura erupted out of his body, and bursts of black baleful qi were dancing around him.

"This is... a Giant Mountain Ape!" the Blood Heavenly Ghost exclaimed in a surprised voice.

The giant ape that Han Li had transformed into rushed back to over 1,000 feet away, then thumped its fists against its chest and let loose a long roar as it felt the tremendous strength coursing through its body.

Even though Han Li's nascent soul had been sealed, the power of the true spirit bloodlines he had refined was still in his body, and upon recovering from all of his physical injuries, he was finally able to use his 12 Awakening Transformations again. [1]

Unleashing this ability instantly brought a flurry of memories flooding into his mind.

"It's no wonder that you possess such incredible strength if you're related to this true spirit. I've been searching everywhere for someone like you, never did I think one would show up on my doorstep! If I can refine this Blood Heavenly Ghost Flag again with your blood, its powers will be sure to be greatly enhanced!" the Blood Heavenly Ghost cackled as it launched itself through the air.

It clenched its right claw into a giant fist before throwing a punch at the golden ape, and a vast expanse of crimson light erupted from its fist.

The giant golden ape harrumphed coldly as it also retaliated with a punch of its own, releasing an enormous burst of golden radiance from its fist.

The two fists of completely incomparable sizes clashed, and an earth-shattering boom rang out across the entire sky, causing the sea of blood down below to tumble and churn violently.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost's body shuddered, and it was sent flying back by the impact. Its right arm shattered with blood and flesh flying in all directions before disintegrating into a huge cloud of blood mist, revealing the translucent blood-jade-like arm bones inside.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost plummeted into the sea of blood down below, raising a gargantuan wave of blood.

In contrast, the giant golden ape only swayed slightly before steadying itself, then lowered its head to cast its gaze downward.

The surface of the sea of blood churned for a while before falling still again.

However, in the next instant, a resounding boom rang out, and the sea of blood behind the golden ape split apart violently.

Waves of blood surged in all directions as the Blood Heavenly Ghost emerged from the depths. At this point, its shattered arm had already fully healed, and its eyes were glowing brightly with crimson radiance, seemingly having been completely enraged by the resistance being displayed by the giant ape.

It reached down with one hand, and a vast wave of blood rose up from down below, transforming into a crimson spear that was 300 to 400 feet in length before falling into its grasp. The Blood Heavenly Ghost then quickly took aim at the giant golden ape before hurling the spear viciously through the air.

A sharp screeching sound instantly rang out, and the giant ape immediately turned around.

However, instead of retreating, it advanced toward the spear while swinging a huge furry hand down with tremendous force.

A deafening thump rang out, and the crimson spear had virtually only just left the Blood Heavenly Ghost's grasp before it was swatted away, then shattered into countless pieces before disintegrating back into a wave of blood.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost was stunned to see this, and before it had a chance to take evasive measures, the giant golden ape had already reached within 1,000 feet of it before lashing out with both of its golden fists.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost fought fire with fire, raising its left arm to withstand the attack.

A resounding boom rang out, and the Blood Heavenly Ghost was sent flying once again. The blood and flesh on the left half of its body had been completely destroyed, revealing the translucent bones within.

Right as the giant golden ape was about to give chase and press its advantage, an enormous wave suddenly rose up from the sea of blood down below, then transformed into a fearsome dragon's head in the blink of an eye.

The dragon's head opened its cavernous mouth before closing it in a flash, devouring the giant golden ape right as it was about to catch up to the Blood Heavenly Ghost.

Immediately thereafter, a blood dragon that was over 1,000 feet in length rose up from the sea of blood, coiling its massive body in the air as it released a vast cloud of blood mist.

Not far away, the Blood Heavenly Ghost had already steadied itself, and the runes on its bones were flashing as bursts of viscous blood rose up from the sea of blood before intertwining themselves around the missing half of its body. New flesh instantly began to grow at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, squirming incessantly as it did so.

Taking advantage of the fact that the giant ape had been devoured by the blood dragon, the Blood Heavenly Ghost hurriedly made a hand seal while chanting a profound incantation.

Bright crimson light glowed within the giant dragon's eyes as it instantly coiled its own body into a massive ball of blood. Crimson light was flashing erratically from the surface of the ball of blood, and it was also rapidly expanding like a balloon.

A fierce look appeared on the Blood Heavenly Ghost's face as it made one final hand seal, but right at this moment, countless golden threads of light suddenly pierced through a certain part of the enormous ball of blood, creating a massive bulge.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding thump rang out, and a burst of golden light flew out before hurtling directly toward the Blood Heavenly Ghost.

Enveloped within the golden light was none other than the giant golden ape.

It had only flown no more than 200 to 300 feet before an earth-shattering boom rang out, and the gigantic ball of blood exploded violently, forming an even more gargantuan ball of crimson light, which was still rapidly expanding in all directions at an alarming rate.

Devastating shockwaves proliferated through the air, sending fierce gusts of wind sweeping through the surrounding area close to 10 kilometers in radius. Spatial ripples that were visible even to the naked eye appeared at the very epicenter of the explosion before fading in the blink of an eye.

The giant golden ape managed to break out of the ball of blood in time, but it was still partially caught in the explosion, and several tufts of its vibrant golden fur had been singed. Thankfully, the injuries that it had sustained didn't appear to be very severe. If it weren't for his fast reactions, even with his formidable physical body, he would've still suffered significant damage from the explosion.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost looked on at the rapidly approaching giant golden ape, and it flapped its dark purple bat wings, instantly conjuring up two gusts of fierce wind beneath itself. Its enormous body then transformed into a blurry crimson shadow that retreated into the distance at an incredible speed that was far superior to that of the giant golden ape.

At this point, it was already clear to the Blood Heavenly Ghost that continuing to challenge the giant ape to a contest of strength was not a wise option.

A cold look appeared on the giant golden ape's face upon seeing this.

The Giant Mountain Ape was renowned for its incredible strength, but its speed was rather lackluster, and there was no way that Han Li could catch the Blood Heavenly Ghost in this current form.

All of a sudden, the Blood Heavenly Ghost in the distance let loose a ghastly screech, and a series of bulges appeared in the sea of blood around the giant golden ape, each of which was several dozen feet in size.

Immediately thereafter, hundreds of crimson shadows shot out of the bulges before converging toward the golden ape from all directions.

It was a horde of crimson ghostly creatures, each with a single horn on its head. The creatures had green eyes and sharp claws, and clouds of blood mist were surging all around them.

The giant golden ape stopped in its tracks, and golden light began to radiate from its body. At the same time, it was rapidly shrinking in size and was quickly concealed within the clouds of blood mist around it.

In the next instant, a clear cry rang out, and countless bursts of azure light erupted out of the blood mist. Fierce gusts of azure wind then swept through the surrounding area to sweep the blood mist away, revealing a giant azure bird.

The bird was 70 to 80 feet in size with bright azure feathers and an azure feather crest on its head. Its wings were extremely wide, and when fully spread open, its wingspan exceeded the length of its body. There were also three long tail feathers trailing along behind it, giving it a majestic and mystical appearance.

With a vigorous flap of its wings, the giant azure bird released countless gusts of fierce wind, leaving hundreds of azure streaks in its wake before slashing into the oncoming horde of ghostly creatures.

Several dozen ghostly creatures were instantly sliced into shreds by the azure streaks, then exploded into clouds of blood mist.

The giant azure bird spread its wings once again, transforming into a blurry azure shadow that flew out of the encirclement of ghostly creatures in an extremely agile manner before racing toward the Blood Heavenly Ghost.

"This is... the Azure Luan Bird! Who are you?" the Blood Heavenly Ghost exclaimed, then hurriedly flapped its wings as it fled the scene.

However, the azure shadow was astonishingly fast, and it reached the Blood Heavenly Ghost in the blink of an eye before flying past amid a flash of azure light.

Three huge wounds that were deep enough to expose bone instantly appeared on the Blood Heavenly Ghost's chest, and blood erupted in all directions.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost reflexively turned around and raised its arms to retaliate, but by then, the azure shadow had already appeared behind it before flashing past its back.

Three huge wounds were instantly inflicted onto the Blood Heavenly Ghost's back, and blood splattered everywhere once again, while one of its bat wings was completely severed.

A furious crimson glow appeared in the Blood Heavenly Ghost's eyes, and it let loose an enraged roar as it lashed out at the azure shadow with its powerful claws.

Countless crimson claw projections were conjured up, then intertwined with one another to form a dense net.

However, the azure shadow suddenly vanished on the spot, then appeared to the right of the Blood Heavenly Ghost in the next instant as if by instantaneous teleportation, then pounced like lightning once again.

Three more deep wounds appeared on the Blood Heavenly Ghost's right arm, exposing its arm bones as blood erupted out of the wounds like a crimson fountain.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost let loose another furious roar as it attempted to retaliate, but unfortunately for it, it was completely unable to keep up with the azure shadow's speed.

A series of blurry azure shadows danced around the Blood Heavenly Ghost in a wraith-like manner, moving so rapidly that it was impossible to track with the naked eye.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost's body was instantly riddled with wounds, and its movements had also become quite sluggish.

If it weren't for the fact that the translucent bones in its body were extremely hard and resolute, it would've already been sliced into countless shreds.

A hint of fear finally flashed through the Blood Heavenly Ghost's eyes, and it threw its arms over its own head as it raced toward the sea of blood down below. At the same time, an enormous wave of viscous blood rose up to meet it.

Right at this moment, a clear cry rang out, and the azure shadow accelerated even further, dancing around the Blood Heavenly Ghost at an unfathomable speed, leaving trails of afterimages in its wake.

Ferocious gusts of wind were swept up, and countless long azure streaks appeared within the wind, filling the surrounding area in a radius of several kilometers as they tore viciously at everything.

The wave of blood had only just begun to rise up before it was instantly struck by dozens of azure streaks, causing it to disintegrate and tumble back into the sea of blood.

[1]. For more information on the 12 Awakening Transformations, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1425: 12 Awakening Transformations.

[Back]

Chapter 58: You Have My Thanks

A series of azure streaks appeared around the Blood Heavenly Ghost before rapidly forming an enormous azure cocoon that was slicing into its body from all directions, drawing blood with every single strike.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost was waving its arms frantically, but in complete futility. More and more chunks of flesh were torn out of its body, and whenever it tried to draw upon the sea of blood down below to recover from its injuries, it was always interrupted.

Only two or three seconds had passed since the emergence of the Azure Luan Bird, but the Blood Heavenly Ghost had already been reduced to nothing more than a giant crimson skeleton, just like when it had first appeared. Its entire body had been completely stripped of flesh with the exception of its head.

The ghostly creatures that were rushing in from the distance also disintegrated before they could reach the Azure Luan Bird due to insufficient magic power support.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost let loose a roar of fury and frustration as it began to spin around in mid-air, planning to find an opportunity to swoop down regardless of the consequences.

However, the Azure Luan Bird was only continuing to pick up in speed, and more and more azure streaks appeared in the air. Not only was the Blood Heavenly Ghost unable to descend toward the sea of blood, it was carried higher and higher up into the air by the gusts of fierce wind swept up by the countless azure streaks.

One azure streak after another struck the crimson skeleton in a relentless assault, and the crimson light radiating from the skeleton was slowly beginning to dim.

All of a sudden, yet another azure streak flashed past, and a faint crack rang out as a tiny crack finally appeared on the forearm of the giant skeleton.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost's pupils contracted drastically upon seeing this, and it hurriedly yelled, "Stop! I surrender!"

The azure shadow that was rapidly revolving around its body finally drew to a halt upon hearing this, reverting back into a giant azure bird over 100 feet away. It folded its wings against its sides, then stared intently at the Blood Heavenly Ghost with bright blue light flashing in its eyes.

The countless azure streaks in the air instantly faded, as did the ferocious storm of wind.

The Blood Heavenly Ghost heaved a faint sigh of relief upon seeing this, then immediately flew toward the sea of blood before plunging into its depths.

Moments later, a black-robed figure emerged from the sea of blood, and it was none other than Duan Renli.

His face was looking rather pale and weary, and it was clear that he had expended a great deal of energy during the battle.

The Azure Luan Bird rapidly shrank down upon seeing this, quickly reverting back into Han Li's human form.

The two of them exchanged a glance, and Han Li wore a faint smile, while Duan Renli was looking less than thrilled.

……

Inside the Devilish Flame Valley.

The four Body Integration cultivators were gathered in one corner of the valley, while Liu Le'er was standing at the other end of the valley with the silver net of flames around her.

All of them were looking up at the sky, where an enormous crimson cloud was overlooking virtually the entire valley.

A giant crimson flag was just barely visible within the cloud, occasionally releasing bursts of harrowing crimson light.

Liu Le'er was looking on with an anxious expression, while the four Body Integration cultivators were quite relaxed, and they were occasionally casting sinister glances her way, further exacerbating her unease.

As high-grade cultivators of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, they were well aware of just how powerful this Blood Heavenly Ghost Flag was.

The flag had been inherited from one of the ascended patriarchs of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, Patriarch Bone Flame, and there was a heavenly ghost sealed within it. It was said that this heavenly ghost was a ghostly monarch formed by a deceased immortal, and that it had been captured from the Nether Realm.

The flag was passed down between generations of supreme elders, and it was nurtured by the blood essence of those supreme elders. Throughout its history, it had also been refined using special blood essence on countless occasions, thereby further elevating its powers.

Out of all of the Grand Ascension cultivators of the Spirit Domain Realm, Duan Renli could only be considered to be in the middle of the pack. However, everything was different in the space within the flag.

It was true that Han Li was incredibly powerful, particularly when it came to his physical body, but his fate was already sealed from the moment he was drawn into the space within the flag.

"It's already been close to an hour. I'm sure that Han Li must've already been reduced to food for the heavenly ghost at this point. That little demon fox is really annoying to look at, how about we kill her now?" the purple-bearded man suggested as he cast his gaze toward Liu Le'er.

Not only had Han Li taken one of his most powerful treasures, he had also embarrassed him in front of Duan Renli. He was unable to exact his revenge on Han Li, so he was naturally eager to take out his anger on Liu Le'er.

The woman in red hesitated momentarily, then said, "There's no hurry, Elder Lu. In my opinion, we should still wait for Martial Uncle Duan to come out before making a decision."

"I agree. The silver flame around that little demon fox is no ordinary flame. It's capable of even devouring the Ninth Heaven Devilish Flame, and it seems to be some type of mutated true flame. I also think we should wait, just to be safe," the hunch-backed elderly man said with a contemplative expression.

The one-eyed man was staring intently up at the giant crimson cloud in the sky with his arms crossed, seemingly unable to even hear the conversation taking place around him.

The purple-bearded man's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but he still nodded reluctantly in agreement.

The four Body Integration cultivators made no effort to conceal their conversation, so Liu Le'er was naturally able to hear everything. She couldn't help but shudder in fear as she pressed her back tightly against the rock face behind her, and her face instantly became completely devoid of color.

All of a sudden, the one-eyed man broke his silence. "Looks like it's finally over."

Everyone immediately turned to look up at the sky in unison upon hearing this.

The massive crimson cloud churned violently before splitting apart down the center to completely reveal the huge crimson flag.

The four Body Integration cultivators were all a little perplexed by what they saw.

The giant crimson flag was still radiating dazzling crimson light, but the massive ghostly head on the surface of the flag seemed to have dimmed slightly compared with before.

Before they had a chance to ponder this any further, two streaks of light flew out of the flag before landing on the ground down below.

The streaks of light then faded to reveal Han Li and Duan Renli, who were standing across from one another.

Duan Renli stood with his hands clasped behind his back, watching Han Li with a cold gaze.

Han Li was looking right back at him with a calm smile on his face.

"Brother Rock!"

Tears instantly welled up in Liu Le'er's eyes as she rushed toward Han Li as quickly as she could.

However, she was already injured and suffering from magic power overexertion, so she was a little unsteady on her feet. Before she could reach Han Li, she tripped over her own feet and flew through the air.

Right at this moment, she felt herself being carried up by a burst of gentle, invisible force, following which her surroundings blurred, and before she knew it, she was already by Han Li's side.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the silver net of fire around Liu Le'er reverted back into a silver fire raven before vanishing into his body.

Liu Le'er opened her mouth to say something, but she suddenly sensed that the atmosphere was a little strange, so she immediately decided against saying anything as she stood off to the side in an obedient manner.

The four Body Integration cultivators had thought that there would be nothing left of Han Li at this point, yet not only was he alive and well, he appeared to be as calm and collected as ever, and all four of them were completely rooted to the spot, unsure of what to make of the situation.

Only after a long while did the four of them return to their senses, and they exchanged a few uncertain glances, wanting to ask about the outcome of the battle, but not daring to do so.

Right at this moment, Duan Renli suddenly broke the silence. "Fetch me 50 kilograms of Yin Dawn Stone."

His voice was quite calm, and it wasn't very loud, but it was no different from a rumbling thunderclap in the ears of the four Body Integration cultivators.

Even though they had already guessed the outcome, they were still left in complete disbelief.

It was clear from what Duan Renli was saying that he had lost.

He was one of the two supreme elders of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, a Grand Ascension cultivator who stood at the pinnacle of the Spirit Domain Realm, yet he had been defeated by this completely unremarkable-looking young man.

Furthermore, the defeat had been suffered in the space within the Blood Heavenly Ghost Flag.

"Do I need to repeat myself?" Duan Renli, and his voice was still as calm as ever, but there was clearly something brewing beneath the calm facade.

The four Body Integration cultivators shuddered upon hearing this, and the purple-bearded man and the woman in red hurriedly turned before flying out of the valley.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Duan," Han Li said with a faint smile.

Duan Renli took a cold glance at Han Li, then stowed the giant crimson flag away with a wave of his hand before flying away as a streak of black light, quickly vanishing out of sight.

……

A short while later, in the main hall on the Cloudrise Peak of the Cold Flame Sect.

"I had a feeling that he was no ordinary person, but never did I think that he would be so powerful that even Duan Renli of the Heavenly Ghost Sect is no match for him," Nangong Changshan said with a wry smile as he sat on the main seat in the hall.

"Thankfully, he's not an enemy of our Cold Flame Sect," Luo Jun sighed with a complex expression.

"Both the Heavenly Talisman Hall and scripture library incidents took place after Elder Han came to our Cloudrise Peak. If you ask me, he was most likely responsible for both, but there's no way we could've possibly suspected him before this," Nangong Changshan mused.

Luo Jun nodded in response. He had clearly already arrived at the same conclusion, but he didn't dwell on this matter any further. Instead, he quickly changed the subject.

"The Heavenly Ghost Sect has been extremely tight-lipped about what happened, but there's no way they could've kept it a secret given the magnitude of the incident. Apparently, many of the sects that were originally more inclined toward the Heavenly Ghost Sect and the Origin Realm Temple have displayed intentions of defecting to us."

"Indeed. Valley Master Yu of the Serene Prosperity Valley and Mountain Master Zhao of the Idle Mountain have both sent letters to our sect master requesting a private audience. In reality, these people just want to see Elder Han and verify his powers for themselves. Only then can they make a decision whether to join our Cold Flame Sect or not.

“Unfortunately for them, Elder Han went into seclusion not long after his return, and the supreme elder released an order, prohibiting anyone from disturbing Elder Han for any reason," Nangong Changshan said.

Luo Jun nodded in response with a contemplative expression and didn't say anything further.

The hall was silent for a moment before Nangong Changshan suddenly asked, "Elder Luo, what do you think of Elder Han?"

Luo Jun's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. In the past, he would've felt comfortable freely sharing his opinion, but now, he was rather hesitant.

Only after some extensive contemplation did he reply with a cautious expression, "I haven't had much interaction with Elder Han. Back when Martial Niece Gu first brought him into the sect, I didn't notice anything particularly remarkable about him aside from the fact that he's a powerful body cultivator. The more I think back now, the more I realize just how careful and calculated he is. Having said that, he doesn't seem to be a cold and uncaring person."

"Oh? What makes you think that?" Nangong Changshan asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"The sect master once asked Elder Han to move into the cave abode on the Holy Fire Peak neighboring the supreme elder's cave abode, but he refused, saying that he was satisfied with his current cave abode and didn't want to go through the hassle of moving.

“I feel like it goes deeper than that, almost as if he's trying to do our Cloudrise Peak a favor. After all, with someone so powerful staying at our Cloudrise Peak, the status of our peak will be greatly elevated in the sect," Luo Jun explained.

Nangong Changshan nodded in agreement upon hearing this. "That is indeed true. Come to think of it, Martial Niece Gu made a significant contribution in introducing Elder Han into our sect. From now on, double the amount of cultivation resources annually allocated to her."

"Yes, Peak Master," Luo Jun hurriedly replied.

Chapter 59: Borrowing the Star Gathering Platform

Several days later, in a cave abode garden halfway up the Cloudrise Peak.

A beautiful young woman in a palace dress with skin as fair as snow was slowly walking along half a step behind a tall white-robed woman.

These two were none other than Yu Menghan and Gu Yunyue.

"Thinking back to what you said back then, Elder Han's origins really are a mystery. On the way back to the sect, it had already become apparent to me that he was far more powerful than he let on, but it appears I still severely underestimated him," Gu Yunyue said with a wry smile.

"I wonder when or if I'll ever reach his level," Yu Menghan sighed as a hint of longing appeared in her eyes.

"Striving for the path of immortality in a limited lifespan is already a pursuit that goes against the natural order. Aptitude is important, but luck and fate are even more vital. That's why countless people have cultivated their entire lives without even reaching the Foundation Establishment Stage, let alone the Core Formation Stage and beyond.

“I've already been cultivating for over 500 years, and at this point, I've spent over a century stuck at the mid-Nascent Soul Stage. Perhaps there's a slim ray of hope for me to reach the Deity Transformation Stage someday, but the Spatial Tempering Stage is almost certainly out of reach.

“As for the Body Integration Stage and the Grand Ascension Stage, I wouldn't even dare to think about such lofty aspirations," Gu Yunyue said as she raised her head to look up at the sky with a slightly dejected expression.

A hint of melancholy also appeared in Yu Menghan's eyes upon hearing this.

Gu Yunyue withdrew her gaze before turning to Yu Menghan, then continued, "Given my limited aptitude, this is most likely as far as I'll go in my cultivation journey. However, you possess a spirit body constitution and exceptional learning ability. In just two short years since you've joined our sect, you've already reached the Foundation Establishment Stage.

“Barring any mishaps, you'll be sure to achieve greater things than I will in your cultivation, and there may even be a chance for you to reach the Spatial Tempering Stage and beyond."

"It's all thanks to your unreserved teachings and all of the precious pills you've bestowed upon me, Master. I am eternally grateful to you," Yu Menghan said in an earnest voice.

"Thanks to Elder Han, you won't have to worry about pills or resources for a very long time to come," Gu Yunyue replied.

Yu Menghan's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this.

"Come to think of it, I visited Elder Han once in the past two years, but at this point, his cave abode has already been marked down as a forbidden zone of the sect, so I most likely won't be able to visit him again," Gu Yunyue sighed with a hint of disappointment in her eyes.

……

Not long after that, the Cloudrise Peak of the Cold Flame Sect suddenly accepted a vagrant cultivator as an outer court disciple. The cultivator in question possessed mediocre aptitude, and even though he was already at an advanced age, he was only at the Core Formation Stage, so he didn't fulfill the recruitment criteria at all. As a result, there were a lot of dissenting voices that arose among the disciples of the sect in response to this decision.

That was until it became known that this cultivator by the name of Daoist White Stone was an acquaintance of Elder Han. In the wake of this revelation, all of the dissenting voices instantly subsided, and many people in the sect, including even elders from other peaks with far superior cultivation bases, began to approach Daoist White Stone in an attempt to befriend him, but that was another story.

Over a month quickly passed by.

On the main peak of the Origin Realm Temple, the Heaven Worship Peak, there was an ovular pond that was as green and translucent as jade. The pond contained an abundance of spiritual qi, which formed a layer of dense white mist over the surface of the water.

A shimmering golden carp would occasionally leap out of the water, and around a dozen elegant red-crested cranes were playing joyfully beside the pond while pecking at the spirit grass growing around the pond.

All of a sudden, a streak of purple light flew through the air before landing beside the pond in a flash.

The purple light faded to reveal a tall and broad man, wearing a purple daoist robe that was embroidered with a purple pattern. The man appeared to be around 40 to 50 years of age with a long black beard trailing down from his chin, giving him a rather mystical and ethereal appearance.

As soon as he landed on the ground, he took a quick glance at the cranes beside the pond, then cast his gaze toward the moss-covered stone wall on the other side of the pond.

With a flick of his wrist, a voice transmission talisman flew out of his sleeve, then flew into the rock face before vanishing in a flash.

Moments later, a layer of golden light flashed over the stone face, following which an opening that was as tall as a grown man appeared down the center of the stone wall.

The purple-robed man didn't hesitate in the slightest before flying into the opening.

Within the stone face was an extremely spacious stone chamber.

Inside the chamber was a three-level tall platform, with profound patterns engraved all over each layer. There were also a series of strange-looking yellow lanterns placed all over the platform, forming a peculiar array that was releasing astonishing spiritual power fluctuations.

At the very center of the top level of the platform sat a portly man who was seated on a cushion . He was wearing a loose-fitting golden robe that left a large section of his chest exposed, and he resembled a small mountain of flesh from afar.

The purple-robed man extended a respectful bow toward the "meat mountain", then reported, "Supreme Elder, we've just received a message from the Cold Flame Sect, stating that Elder Han of their sect wishes to use our Star Gathering Platform for cultivation, and they've promised us handsome compensation in return. Should we..."

The golden-robed man didn't immediately reply. Instead, he pondered the notion for a moment before replying in a slow and deliberate voice, "I asked you to investigate his identity and history. How is that coming along?"

His voice was extremely loud and resonant, and it was reverberating throughout the stone chamber.

"All we managed to find out is that he suddenly appeared in the Prosperous Nation two years ago, and he became a guest elder not long after he entered the Cold Flame Sect. However, during this time, he's always kept a low profile and remained unnoticed, so we only became aware of his existence after what happened in the Heavenly Ghost Sect," the purple-robed man replied.

"It's fine. If I were Sima Jingming, I would definitely have kept the existence of that man a secret. What has the Heavenly Ghost Sect been up to recently?" the golden-robed man asked.

"After the incident, everyone in the Heavenly Ghost Sect has been keeping a very low profile. They haven't expressed any displeasure or any intention to seek revenge," the purple-robed man replied.

"There's no way the two supreme elders of the Heavenly Ghost Sect would simply let something like this slide. We just need to wait and see," the golden-robed man scoffed, clearly unconvinced by this answer.

"Then about that request to borrow the Star Gathering Platform..." the purple-robed man said in a hesitant voice.

"The request is being made by someone with Grand Ascension Stage power, so it's best not to get on his bad side. Agree to his request for now," the golden-robed man decided after some deliberation.

The purple-robed man's brows furrowed slightly, and he hesitated momentarily, then said, "Truth be told, the grand elders of our temple are a little concerned about this. They're afraid that Elder Han would become even more powerful after cultivating in the Star Gathering Platform, and once that happens, our Origin Realm Temple will fall below the Cold Flame Sect in the pecking order.

“On top of that, activating the Star Gathering Platform requires a great deal of Starwash Stone expenditure. We're already having to be very conservative in using the Starwash Stones on the top disciples of our sect, it's truly a shame if we have to use those precious stones on an outsider."

"Tell them that their concerns are unnecessary. It's not so easy for a Grand Ascension Stage being to further their powers. On top of that, he's the one requesting to borrow our Star Gathering Platform, so the Cold Flame Sect will naturally be responsible for covering all of the expenses involved," the golden-robed man replied with a nonchalant smile.

"Yes, Supreme Elder!" the purple-robed man replied in a respectful manner.

……

Two months later, at the Origin Realm Temple.

There was a lush, winding mountain range with cotton-like clouds drifting through the sky, and the occasional crane and spirit bird could also be spotted, presenting a serene and prosperous sight to behold.

At the very center of the mountain range was a mountain that was far taller than all those around it, stretching all the way up into the clouds.

The peak of the mountain was laden with giant rocks, and spiritual qi was permeating through the air, but there wasn't much plant life present. At the very center was a nine-level platform that was shaped like a round pagoda. It was entirely of a translucent white color, as if it had been constructed from jade.

A group of brown-robed elderly men was seated around the platform with their legs crossed and their eyes closed.

As nighttime approached, the light of the setting sun shone down from the heavens, basking the rocks on the mountain peak in a warm orange glow and reflecting a dreamy and ethereal radiance off the white jade platform.

Right at this moment, two streaks of light suddenly sped through the distant sky, then landed at the foot of the platform to reveal a pair of figures.

The brown-robed elderly men who were seated around the platform all rose to their feet before making their way over to the two men, one of whom was the golden-robed meat mountain of a man, and they all extended respectful bows as they greeted in unison, "We pay our respects to the supreme elder."

The group of elderly men then turned their attention toward the unfamiliar young man next to the golden-robed man.

That young man was naturally none other than Han Li, who had come to borrow the Star Gathering Platform.

The golden-robed man remained silent as he waved a dismissive hand, and the four elderly men immediately returned to their original positions.

"Fellow Daoist Han, these four are the guardians of the Star Gathering Platform. There's only one Body Integration cultivator, while the other three are only at the Spatial Tempering Stage, but they've been working together for many years and are extremely competent. With these four overseeing proceedings, you can rest assured that you'll be safe here," the golden-robed man said with a smile.

Han Li naturally didn't want there to be any bystanders from the Origin Realm Temple present during his cultivation, but he knew that this was not something that he could refuse. Hence, he smiled as he replied, "You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain."

"Night is about to fall soon, so I won't delay your cultivation, Fellow Daoist Han. If you have any requests, feel free to raise them to those four," the golden-robed man said, then cupped his fist toward Han Li in a parting salute before flying away as a streak of light, vanishing into the distance in the blink of an eye.

Han Li watched as the golden-robed man departed, then quickly inspected his surroundings before arriving at the staircase of the Star Gathering Platform, but he wasn't in a hurry to scale it.

The four elderly men around the platform were already beginning to make hand seals while chanting incantations.

Circles of hidden runes lit up around the four men, and a golden light barrier that encompassed the entire Star Gathering Platform appeared.

At the same time, a small opening that was only large enough to fit one person emerged in front of Han Li.

Blue light flashed through his eyes, and he determined that even though the light barrier was giving off powerful spiritual power fluctuations, it was only a protective array, so he strode in through the opening without any qualms.

As soon as Han Li stepped through the opening, it immediately sealed shut, following which the light barrier fused into the air and vanished.

As Han Li set foot on the staircase, a burst of peculiar spiritual power fluctuations immediately swept through the surrounding area.

Han Li was rather intrigued by this, and he looked down to find that the stone staircase beneath his feet and the ground around him were riddled with tiny pits that would've been impossible to see without paying close attention.

He activated his spirit eyes ability momentarily to find that there was faint silver light flashing at the bottom of all of the tiny pits, and they were left behind from all of the starpower exposure that had accumulated over the course of countless years.

There were also many diagrams engraved onto the Star Gathering Platform that were connected by lines and circles. Some of them were extremely simple, consisting of only three to five diagrams, while others were more complex, consisting of clusters that comprised around a dozen diagrams each.

As Han Li scaled the staircase and inspected all of the diagrams, he gradually came to understand that these diagrams were all corresponding with the constellations in the sky.

Chapter 60: Wanted

Han Li continued to scale the staircase all the way until he reached the top of the Star Gathering Platform, and only at the very center of the platform's top level was he able to find a diagram of the Big Dipper.

He briefly inspected the diagram before sitting down with his legs crossed, then raised his head to look up at the sky, upon which he discovered that the heavens had already taken on a dark blue hue, and several stars had already appeared.

He closed his eyes and began to meditate in silence.

Around two hours later, Han Li's eyes sprang open, and he gently uttered the word, "begin".

The four brown-robed elderly men around the platform each flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized Starwash Stone upon hearing this, then pressed the stones into the indentations on the ground before them.

The four stones cracked in unison as bursts of white light rose up from the indentations, flowing along the runes and patterns engraved into the ground to quickly reach the Star Gathering Platform.

All nine levels of the platform instantly began to glow brightly while taking on a translucent appearance, and the constellation diagrams engraved onto the platform also began to radiate dazzling silver light. From afar, the platform resembled a miniature version of the night sky, and it was a breathtaking sight to behold.

At the same time, the stars in the sky were also becoming brighter and brighter, as if they were resonating with the platform, and boundless silver starlight rained down from the heavens like a faint silver mist that encompassed the entire Star Gathering Platform.

Han Li was situated within the silver mist, and it was as if he were seated among the stars.

He could feel a burst of vast yet gentle starpower surging all around him, and he took a moment to concentrate before making a hand seal and chanting the incantation for the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

A dull thump rang out within his body, and six extremely thick pillars of white light cascaded down from the night sky.

All six pillars of light shone down around Han Li, and the starpower that the pillars of light contained was downright astonishing.

Countless threads of translucent light emerged from the pillars of light, then abruptly straightened before piercing directly toward Han Li like countless steel needles.

At the same time, the faint silver mist that encompassed the entire Star Gathering Platform also began to rapidly surge as if it had been stirred up somehow.

Countless silver fragments of light began to swirl around under the influence of a burst of immense force, forming a silver vortex of light that was over 100 feet tall above the Star Gathering Platform.

The starpower that had been extremely gentle just a moment ago had suddenly become extremely violent.

After being encompassed within the vortex, the six pillars of light brightened and expanded considerably, and the starpower surging into them also increased by severalfold.

However, at the same time, the pain that Han Li was having to bear was also significantly more excruciating.

His robes were instantly soaked with blood, and countless threads of starlight were constantly piercing into his skin. The blood that flowed out of his body was swept up by the power of the silver vortex of light, forming a murky blood mist that enveloped his entire body.

The four brown-robed elderly men around the Star Gathering Platform were astonished to see this. Out of all of the many years that they had been stationed here, never had they seen such violent starpower, nor had they ever witnessed such a brutal and direct way of funneling starpower into one's body.

In the face of such an enormous amount of starpower, even a Body Integration cultivator would be struggling just to keep themselves alive.

However, right at this moment, a burst of light suddenly appeared at Han Li's waist, following which six palm-sized black mirrors suddenly emerged before flying toward the six pillars of light.

The round mirrors were enshrouded in clouds of black qi, and there were runes flashing faintly on their surfaces. These were none other than the Starmoon Mirrors that he had refined using the Yin Dawn Stones that he had secured from the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

As soon as the six mirrors fell into position, black light immediately surged over them, following which countless tiny runes erupted forth in a frenzy, forming an incredibly thick and dazzling pillar of light that shot straight up into the night sky.

"He's going to enhance the starpower even further? That's incredible!" the Body Integration Stage brown-robed elderly man murmured to himself in an astonished voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, six of the stars in the Big Dipper Origin Arts abruptly brightened significantly, and a vast expanse of dazzling silver radiance appeared in the air, then flowed into the silver vortex in a frenzy.

……

Half a year later, in a stone chamber on the Heaven Worship Peak.

The golden-robed Daoist Closed Mountain was seated with his eyes closed and his legs crossed on the third level of the platform, making hand seals and chanting incessantly.

All of a sudden, his chanting ceased, and he hurriedly rose to his feet.

A gust of wind swept into the stone chamber without warning, and in its wake, flames were ignited in several dozen yellow lanterns on the platform. Wisps of white smoke slowly rose up into the air, converging to form a cloud of white mist.

The surface of the mist blurred momentarily before an elderly figure with a lotus crown on his head emerged. The figure wasn't very tall or imposing, and he was wearing a golden daoist robe.

"Welcome, Patriarch Clear Bright!" Daoist Closed Mountain greeted in a respectful voice as he fell to his knees and kowtowed to the ground.

"No need for formalities. I descended today because I have a few things that I need you to do," the elderly daoist priest said.

Daoist Closed Mountain returned to his feet, standing with his hands by his sides as he asked, "What are your instructions, Patriarch?"

"The Clear Origin Stones that you offered last time were of a very good quality. I'll be requiring another batch within the next 10 years," the elderly daoist priest said.

"Yes, Patriarch."

"I've recently developed some new insights and made some adjustments to the Profound Star Observation Arts that I created. Take this improved version and put it in the scripture library..."

The elderly daoist priest delegated several instructions in succession, all of which Daoist Closed Mountain agreed to without any hesitation.

After that, the elderly daoist priest continued, "On top of all of that, there's an important matter that you need to attend to carefully."

A serious look appeared on Daoist Closed Mountain's face upon hearing this, and he waited in silence for further elaboration.

The elderly daoist priest swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a sheet of paper that was around a foot in size, which drifted over to Daoist Closed Mountain.

"If you find out any information on this man, report it to me immediately," the elderly daoist priest instructed in an implacable voice.

Daoist Closed Mountain accepted the sheet of paper before taking a look, and a hint of surprise immediately flashed through his eyes.

The sheet of paper bore the portrait of a young man, and it was none other than Han Li.

"Is there something wrong?" the elderly daoist priest asked.

"Patriarch, this man is in our temple right now!" Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly replied.

The elderly daoist priest's expression remained unchanged, but a hint of urgency crept into his voice as he asked, "Are you sure it's him?"

Daoist Closed Mountain hesitated momentarily, then replied in a certain voice, "The man in this portrait is completely identical to the man I'm referring to. There's no mistaking it, it's definitely him!"

The elderly daoist priest nodded in response, then asked, "Why is he in our Origin Realm Temple right now?"

"Please forgive me, Patriarch. This man is a guest elder of the Cold Flame Sect, and..." Daoist Closed Mountain quickly provided a detailed account of everything that he knew about Han Li.

A contemplative look appeared on the elderly daoist priest's face, and he remained silent for a long while.

Sweat was beginning to bead up on Daoist Closed Mountain's forehead, but he didn't dare to make a sound and could only wait in silence.

"This man is most likely a descended immortal, and there's currently a huge reward on his head in the Immortal Realm. Don't alert anyone prematurely, wait for me to make some arrangements. Before the arrangements are complete, make sure that he remained in our Origin Realm Temple no matter what," the elderly daoist priest instructed with a serious expression.

"Yes, Patriarch," Daoist Closed Mountain immediately answered.

……

In a certain region of the sea in the Immortal Realm.

The seawater here was as black as ink, and these turbulent black waves stretched on for as far as the eyes could see in all directions.

Close to 100 black mountains were hovering in the air above the black sea, atop which stood a series of giant black octagonal pagodas.

These pagodas varied drastically in height, with the tallest ones stretching to over 100,000 feet in height, while the shortest ones were only around 1,000 feet tall. However, all of them were identical in their inky-black color and their octagonal shape.

In a hall at the top of one of the smaller black pagodas sat Daoist Clear Bright in front of a square altar.

There was a white array that was giving off bright white radiance hovering above the altar.

Daoist Clear Bright cast an incantation seal toward the array, and the white glow that it was emitting immediately faded.

He then cast his gaze directly forward, and even though he was completely still, it was clear that he was pondering something.

After a long while, he finally gritted his teeth and made a decision, then flipped a hand over to produce a translucent crystal bead, which he tossed into the air in front of him.

An incantation seal was cast into the bead, and countless tiny runes instantly appeared over its surface, forming a slowly revolving array that was around a foot in size.

With each second that past, the array would ripple once.

Time slowly passed by, and nothing had changed even after 15 minutes.

However, Daoist Clear Bright remained patient and continued to wait.

Only after a half hour had passed did the array suddenly light up, and a projection of a tiny black figure within it. It was a black-robed man with a wide face and forehead, but he was as thin as a stick and his complexion was of a sickly yellow color.

"It's been over 1,000 years since we last met, but you're still looking not a day older, Layman Bone Flame," Daoist Clear Bright greeted as he cupped his fist in a salute with a warm smile on his face.

However, Layman Bone Flame clearly wasn't that thrilled to see Daoist Clear Bright, and he said in an impatient voice, "If you have something to say, then hurry up. And keep it short."

"Are you at Black Water City at the moment? I have a brilliant opportunity to present to you," Daoist Clear Bright said in a mysterious voice.

"Go ahead," Layman Bone Flame prompted in an indifferent voice.

"I presume you've also received the wanted notice from the Ubiquitous Pavilion, right?" Daoist Clear Bright asked.

"Why are you asking me that? Could it be that you have information on the wanted fugitive?" Layman Bone Flame asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's right! That man is currently in the Spirit Domain Realm!" Daoist Clear Bright replied.

Layman Bone Flame's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he confirmed with a cautious expression, "Really?"

"All you need to do to verify the authenticity of my claim is to contact your disciples in the Spirit Domain Realm," Daoist Clear Bright said.

Layman Bone Flame's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this. "Are you suggesting..."

"That's right. This is an unmissable opportunity for us. I suggest our two sects join forces to capture the fugitive, then split the reward from the Ubiquitous Pavilion evenly among us. What do you say?" Daoist Clear Bright proposed.

Chapter 61: Undercurrents

Layman Bone Flame pondered the proposal for a moment, then said in a calm manner, "The fact that this man is wanted by the Ubiquitous Pavilion indicates that he must be quite a formidable cultivator. Even if his powers will be suppressed in a lower realm, surely he's not someone that two or three Grand Ascension Stage beings can capture."

"There's no need to worry about that, Fellow Daoist. According to what I've heard, that man is currently severely injured and far from the peak of his powers, so he's only slightly more powerful than the average Grand Ascension Stage being," Daoist Clear Bright replied with a dismissive wave of his hand.

"Even so, it's still too risky to get our sects in the lower realm to deal with an immortal. I think it's much safer for us to wait until he leaves the Spirit Domain Realm, then capture him in person," Layman Bone Flame said after a brief silence.

"I feel like this is something that shouldn't be delayed. The fact that the Ubiquitous Pavilion is offering such a large reward for him indicates that he must be harboring some type of secret. Even if that isn't the case, the reward is still worth taking the risk for," Daoist Clear Bright said in a voice that was filled with temptation.

Layman Bone Flame fell silent upon hearing this, and it seemed that he really was tempted by the offer.

Only after some contemplation did he reply, "Alright, I will consider this. If everything is truly as you say, then I'm happy for our two sects to work together. As for the specific details, we'll establish everything once I return to Black Water City."

"I look forward to it," Daoist Clear Bright said with a smile.

……

Several days later, in a large hall deep within the Origin Realm Temple.

The hall was completely empty with the exception of a jade platform at the very center, upon which was a teleportation array that was over 100 feet in size.

The teleportation array was buzzing and glowing brightly with dazzling white light.

At this moment, Daoist Closed Mountain was standing in front of the array, watching it in an expressionless manner, seemingly waiting for something.

Moments later, the white light being released by the teleportation array swelled momentarily before shrinking, and circles of runes appeared within the array before releasing dazzling white radiance.

Once the light faded, two figures, one tall and one short, emerged.

The shorter of the two figures was a black-robed elderly man with a bald spot on his head. His hands were clasped behind his back, which was slightly hunched, and the top of his head wasn't even level with the shoulder of the person next to him. His face was as dark as unrefined iron, and he was giving off an extremely cold and sinister aura.

The other man was a refined black-robed figure, and it was none other than Duan Renli.

"Welcome, Fellow Daoist Tong, Fellow Daoist Duan. It is truly an honor for our Origin Realm Temple to be hosting both of you today. You two still look as fit as ever. In particular, I can sense that Fellow Daoist Tong has made significant strides in his cultivation base. This is truly worthy of celebration!" Daoist Closed Mountain said with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

The hunch-backed elderly man was the other Grand Ascension Stage being of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, Tong Ren'e. Not only did he possess the most advanced cultivation base in the Heavenly Ghost Sect, he was also arguably the number one cultivator in the entire Spirit Domain Realm.

However, he had a very reclusive personality and was normally always away from the sect. No one knew exactly where he stayed in seclusion.

The elderly man merely nodded in Daoist Closed Mountain as a greeting, while Duan Renli returned Daoist Closed Mountain's salute with a faint smile. "Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain."

"This is not the place to talk, Fellow Daoists. Let's go to the side hall," Daoist Closed Mountain as he made an inviting hand gesture before leading the way.

Moments later, the three of them arrived in a side hall before taking their seats.

"Where is that Han Li right now, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain?" Tong Ren'e immediately cut straight to the chase as soon as he sat down.

His voice was extremely coarse and piercing, like pieces of rusty metal scraping together, and it seemed as if he hadn't spoken with anyone in a long time.

"Truth be told, Han Li is currently on the Star Gathering Platform of our temple. He's already been here for half a year, and he hasn't left the platform even for a moment since his arrival," Daoist Closed Mountain replied.

"Why is an immortal like him using the Star Gathering Platform? Do you know the underlying reasons, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain?" Duan Renli asked with a cautious expression.

"I've thought about this myself, and I've watched him cultivate from afar on many a night. On top of that, I assigned a Body Integration cultivator of our sect to constantly remain at the platform to oversee proceedings. Judging from the state of his cultivation and the phenomena being triggered, he's most likely practicing some type of special body refinement cultivation art," Daoist Closed Mountain replied after a moment of contemplation.

"That man's physical body is already incredibly powerful, and he's also able to transform into the Giant Mountain Ape and Azure Luan Bird true spirits using some type of strange secret technique, yet he's still continuing to refine his physical body? Could it be that he's a Profound Immortal who fled into our Spirit Domain Realm?" Duan Renli speculated as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Perhaps. According to what I was told by Patriarch Clear Bright, he was severely wounded and lost his immortal body. Now that he's in a lower realm, his powers will also be greatly suppressed, so he can only be considered to be a Faux Immortal at the moment," Daoist Closed Mountain said.

"Even a Faux Immortal is still far beyond the average Grand Ascension Stage being. It's always best to err on the side of caution," Tong Ren'e said in a wary voice.

"I fully agree, Fellow Daoist Tong. This is an extremely important matter, and we need to devise a thorough strategy, which is why I've invited the two of you here today," Daoist Closed Mountain said with a serious nod.

"This is your territory, so I'm sure you've already considered what the best strategy is for this operation. Please go ahead and tell us what you think," Tong Ren'e said as he turned to Daoist Closed Mountain with a meaningful expression.

"Hehe, I do indeed have some ideas, but I'll be requiring your expert input," Daoist Closed Mountain chuckled in a modest manner.

……

That night.

Under the night sky, the entire Origin Realm Temple was enshrouded under a blanket of silence and darkness, but the pinnacle of the Nine Palace was still as bright as day.

Six enormous pillars of light were cascading down from the starry sky, and the white light was flashing incessantly before gradually disintegrating into specks of silver light.

A silver mist of light was permeating over the entire Star Gathering Platform.

On the top level of the platform, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed and his eyes closed. His entire body was brightly illuminated, and silver radiance was surging over his skin. His well-defined muscles were also giving off a metallic silver gleam, and it was as if every single fiber and sinew in his body had become as resolute as refined steel essence.

On his chest and abdomen were six specks of blue light that were particularly eye-catching, even amid all the silver and white radiance.

Right at this moment, six pillars of black light erupted out of the six existing pillars of light, then reverted back into six palm-sized black mirrors before flying into Han Li's body, vanishing in a flash.

A short while later, Han Li exhaled as he slowly opened his eyes.

With the assistance of the Star Gathering Platform and the Starmoon Mirrors, he had finally mastered the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

"I'm only one step away now," Han Li murmured to himself, then rose to his feet before taking a step forward, upon which a resounding boom suddenly rang out.

The entire Star Gathering Platform shuddered violently, and Han Li involuntarily stumbled forward. His foot had plunged straight into the stone platform, and half of his calf was embedded into its surface.

A mixture of amusement and exasperation appeared on his face. He had failed to anticipate just how significantly his body had been enhanced by the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

He had done nothing more than take a step, and his only mistake was that he had failed to tread lightly, yet this was the result.

Thankfully, the section of the platform that he had stomped into had no constellation arrays engraved onto it, so there weren't going to be any detrimental effects to the function of the platform. Otherwise, he would've been in a rather awkward situation.

With that in mind, he couldn't help but rub his own nose in a slightly sheepish manner.

The Origin Realm Temple elders around the platform all faltered slightly upon feeling the violent tremors, then turned in unison toward the Body Integration Stage brown-robed elderly man.

The elderly man briefly inspected the platform, then transmitted his voice to the other three brown-robed figures. "It's alright, everything is fine."

Ever since Han Li came here to cultivate, the Body Integration Stage elder had slowly become so accustomed to everything that Han Li did that he felt like nothing could surprise him anymore. This was a man who was able to cultivate under such vast starpower with incredible ease and poise, what could he possibly not be capable of?

The instruction that he had received from the supreme elder was only to keep a close eye on Han Li at all times, but to minimize interaction with him as much as possible.

On the Star Gathering Platform, Han Li took a deep breath, then flipped a hand over to produce a gray shield that was around two feet in length.

This was a shield that he had picked up during the rampage that he had gone on in the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and it belonged to one of the unlucky Spatial Tempering cultivators that he had swatted away like flies. The shield was entirely forged from Flowing Light Metal, and there were also some refined crystals thrown in the mix. There were many profound runes engraved on the surface of the shield, and it was clearly a treasure of quite a high caliber.

He injected some magic power into the shield, and spiritual light flashed on its surface. The bolstering restrictions within the shield were all activated, following which he grabbed onto the two sides of the shield before exerting some slight force through his hands.

The spiritual light on the surface of the shield was instantly snuffed out, following which the black shield was quickly massaged into a ball in Han Li's hands as if it were made from soft clay.

A hint of elation welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this.

By his estimates, his strength and physical resistance had almost doubled.

He raised his head to look up at the bright stars in the sky, and the excitement in his heart gradually subsided as he sat back down onto the Big Dipper constellation diagram, then closed his eyes to meditate.

Around two hours later, Han Li made a hand seal and began to chant the incantation for the seventh level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts.

The Big Dipper in the sky instantly began to glow brightly, but in contrast with all of the stars around it, it was giving off a bluish-silver radiance that was fluctuating erratically in brightness.

This time, seven incredibly thick pillars of silver light came crashing down from the night sky before striking the Star Gathering Platform.

All of the constellation diagrams engraved on the platform instantly began to glow with dazzling silver radiance.

From afar, it looked as if the entire platform had been doused in molten silver.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and the entire mountain peak shuddered violently.

A vast expanse of silver light swept over the area as a silver vortex of light that was over 10 times more powerful than the previous one appeared above the platform.

The protective light barrier that previously hung over the Star Gathering Platform was swept up by the incredibly violent starpower, and it was instantly torn to shreds before dissipating into specks of golden light.

The four elders guarding the platform were completely caught off guard and struck by the shockwaves released by the vortex, and the three Spatial Tempering Stage elders were instantly sent flying.

Thankfully, the Body Integration Stage elder was able to react very quickly, summoning several defensive treasures at once to just barely withstand the eruption of starpower. Even so, he was also blown back by over 1,000 feet, and after steadying himself, he immediately cast an astonished gaze toward the pinnacle of the Nine Palace Peak.

Chapter 62: Abnormality

At the same time, three figures were standing side by side on the peak of a certain mountain several hundred kilometers away. They were none other than the trio of Daoist Closed Mountain, Tong Ren'e, and Duan Renli, and they were all watching the phenomenon taking place on the Nine Palace Peak from afar.

All three of them were silent, and there was no sound to be heard aside from the gentle rustling of the wind and the flapping of their robes. The atmosphere was a little heavy.

A short while later, the silence was finally broken.

"So this is the plan that you propose? Let him cultivate in your sect and become even more powerful?" Duan Renli asked.

"This was an oversight from me. It seems like he's found a way to recover from his injuries," Daoist Closed Mountain sighed in a resigned manner.

"We can't delay this any longer," Tong Ren'e said in a cold voice.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Tong. The preparations were almost complete, and there were some finer details that I wanted to ponder, but it appears we really can't afford to wait any longer," Daoist Closed Mountain said in a grim voice.

"We should've done this a long time ago," Duan Renli harrumphed coldly as his hands clenched into tight fists in his sleeves, and an eager gleam appeared in his eyes.

……

The next morning.

There was a small tile courtyard concealed within the purple bamboo forest on the Holy Fire Peak of the Cold Flame Sect.

Sima Jingming was standing in front of a fragrant sandalwood table, looking at a three-foot-long portrait hanging on the wall, seemingly reporting something with a respectful expression.

A flash of light swept over the portrait, and a figure emerged from within. It was none other than Patriarch Cold Flame.

"So you're saying Han Li has already begun practicing the seventh level of the cultivation art?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked.

"Judging from the description that I received of the phenomenon that took place last night, that's almost certainly the case. Who exactly is this man, Patriarch? This rate of progress is completely unfathomable to me..." Sima Jingming replied.

"I don't know who he is, but I recently learned that a massive organization in the Immortal Realm is currently offering a reward for his capture. The reward is so handsome that even I'm slightly tempted.

“Normally, Daoist Clear Bright is constantly in seclusion, but he recently went to Black Water City to meet up with Layman Bone Flame. It looks like they're plotting something through the Heavenly Ghost Sect and the Origin Realm Temple," Patriarch Cold Flame said in an unhurried voice.

Sima Jingming's expression changed slightly upon hearing this. "In that case, should we also..."

"Are you suggesting that we also join the other two sects to get a share in the spoils?" Patriarch Cold Flame interjected.

Sima Jingming knew that he had spoken out of turn, and he immediately fell silent.

"Neither Daoist Clear Bright nor Layman Bone Flame has dealt with Fellow Daoist Han in person, but I've faced him in battle before, albeit only briefly, and it's clear to me that he's definitely no ordinary person.

“The fact that he was able to master the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts so quickly only serves to further confirm my suspicions. The reward is very tempting, but there's no point if you're not even alive to enjoy it," Patriarch Cold Flame said in a meaningful voice.

"Yes, Patriarch!" Sima Jingming hurriedly replied.

……

That night, on the top level of the Star Gathering Platform.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and his entire body was immersed within the silver vortex of light formed by the seven pillars of silver light around him.

Vast starpower was constantly surging into his body from all directions, refining him from the inside-out.

His body was completely still, but he was pondering some things in his mind.

The phenomena triggered during the cultivation of the Big Dipper Origin Arts were extremely spectacular, and the violent starpower sweeping down from the heavens had completely destroyed the protective restriction that once enshrouded the Star Gathering Platform.

After the four elders of the Origin Realm Temple were sent flying, they didn't reappear on the scene, and Daoist Closed Mountain also hadn't visited even once to see what was happening. It seemed that the supervision on him was a little too lax.

This wasn't a cause for alarm, but during the recent period of time, he had sensed all of the Origin Realm Temple cultivators within a radius of around 100 kilometers around the Star Gathering Platform leave their cave abodes one after another, and none of them had returned.

Initially, he didn't think much of this. After all, it was very commonplace for sect members to go out on long journeys or be sent out on missions for extended periods of time. However, once this situation continued for about half a month, it finally caught his attention, and a hint of wariness welled up in his heart.

Just now, for some reason, he had been struck by a sense of unease, and there was a hint of foreboding brewing in his heart.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li decided to withdraw his spiritual sense, which was guiding starpower toward himself from the heavens, then quickly scoured through the entire area in a radius of several hundred kilometers around him.

Right at this moment, the entire space above him suddenly blurred, following which an extremely thick and long white rift appeared. It was as if the entire sky had been torn in half, presenting an extremely peculiar sight to behold.

Countless silver runes surged out of the rift in a frenzy, and it seemed that there was no end to them in sight. As soon as the runes appeared, they immediately revolved on the spot before exploding into balls of silver light that filled virtually the entire sky.

The silver light blended into one another to form an enormous silver moon that was giving off dazzling radiance, completely outshining all of the surrounding stars and making them pale into insignificance.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and in the instant that the giant silver moon took shape, all of the starlight cascading down from the heavens completely vanished.

Han Li immediately flew back in retreat upon seeing this, leaving the Nine Palace Peak in the blink of an eye, then flying to over 10 kilometers away after just a few more flashes.

Right at this moment, a burst of loud rumbling rang out from a mountain that was several dozen kilometers away from the Nine Palace Peak. An enormous white rune that was over 1,000 feet in size appeared on the surface of the mountain, and a massive pillar of white light erupted directly up into the heavens.

Almost at the exact same moment, another mountain in another direction also trembled violently as it released a huge pillar of green light.

The same sequence took place a total of eight times, and a giant rune and an enormous pillar of light emerged from each of the eight completely unremarkable mountains around the Nine Palace Peak.

Each pillar of light was a different color from all the others, and countless runes were emerging around the pillars of light before rapidly connecting together, forming a gargantuan light barrier in the blink of an eye. The Nine Palace Peak stood at the center of the light barrier, which encompassed the entire area with a radius of over 50 kilometers around the peak.

Countless runes of different colors were surging incessantly over the light barrier, and even from extremely far away, one could still sense the astonishing spiritual power fluctuations being released by the light barrier.

Somewhere in the area encompassed within the light barrier, Han Li drew to a halt as a grim look appeared on his face.

He didn't know what the Origin Realm Temple was plotting, but it seemed that they had ultimately decided to turn on him.

He swept his gaze over his surroundings, and a layer of blue light appeared in his eyes, following which his brows furrowed slightly.

The giant restriction was far more profound than the array formed by the Heavenly Ghost Monarch Pillars in the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and even he was unable to immediately spot any weaknesses in it.

He immediately flew through the air without any hesitation, arriving in front of the light barrier in the blink of an eye. Six specks of blue light appeared on his chest and abdomen, following which he threw a vicious punch at the light barrier before him.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and the surface of the light barrier quivered and flashed violently.

An enormous fist indentation appeared, and countless five-colored runes converged toward the indentation from all directions, rapidly repairing the damage that had been inflicted at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Before the light barrier had a chance to completely recover, another punch landed on the same indentation, and the entire light barrier began to tremble violently, looking as if it were about to collapse.

However, right as Han Li raised his fist for a third time, the giant silver moon in the sky suddenly brightened significantly, raining down boundless silver radiance that was interspersed with countless silver runes. All of the silver runes then converged into one place, forming an enormous pillar of light that could encompass an area with a radius of dozens of kilometers.

Blinding silver radiance flashed in front of Han Li's eyes, and in the next instant, his vision was restored, but he found himself situated in a completely alien world.

This was a vast and barren desert, and it was completely devoid of life in all directions. The ground was littered with gray rocks, as well as some massive craters that looked as if they had been left behind by asteroids.

A dense layer of gray clouds was hanging in the sky at a very low altitude, looking as if it could come crashing down at any moment, presenting a rather oppressive and ominous sight to behold.

"Is this another domain treasure?" Han Li murmured to himself before immediately releasing his spiritual sense.

However, his spiritual sense was able to detect nothing aside from the barren land, the gray rocks, and the giant craters.

After a moment of contemplation, he directed his spiritual sense up toward the gray clouds.

However, as soon as his spiritual sense entered the gray clouds, progress became extremely difficult. Even with his Spirit Refinement Technique activated, he was only just barely able to extend his spiritual sense less than 200 feet into the clouds, where there were only more gray clouds waiting for him.

Even with his formidable spiritual sense, the gray clouds were somehow able to pose a stern obstacle.

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he withdrew his spiritual sense, yet right as he was planning to investigate the area through other means, the gray clouds overhead suddenly began to tumble and churn violently.

In the next instant, streaks of yellow light came falling out of the sky like rain before landing on the ground.

Each streak of yellow light expanded rapidly like a balloon upon landing, then transformed into a golden figure.

These figures were around the same size as the average person, with golden skin that was radiating golden radiance. They were wielding all types of different weapons, and even though they appeared to be very similar to normal people, they were completely devoid of life with wooden expressions on their faces as if they were puppets.

Within mere moments, close to 1,000 of these puppets had appeared in the surrounding area, trapping Han Li in a watertight encirclement.

Han Li was completely caught off guard by this abrupt turn of events.

Chapter 63: Raising An Army From Beans

The golden puppets were extremely agile, and they were wielding a diverse range of weapons, such as swords, spears, axes, and maces. As soon as they landed on the ground, some of them immediately leaped up into the air before gliding through the sky like huge golden birds, while others galloped over the ground, causing the earth to rumble and quake violently.

In the blink of an eye, countless golden puppets were charging toward Han Li from all directions, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

Han Li stood completely still on the spot as he calmly swept his gaze over his surroundings.

In the next instant, the first golden puppet reached him before thrusting its spear forward, unleashing a series of spear projections that screeched through the air as they hurtled directly toward Han Li.

Instead of retreating from the attack, he advanced toward the oncoming spear projections, then reached out with one hand like lightning to grab onto the spear.

A burst of enormous force surged through his arm, causing him to sway in a slightly unsteady manner, and even though he was able to instantly steady himself, he still couldn't help but be stunned by the strength of the golden warrior.

He pulled back on the spear with his arm, causing the spear-wielding golden puppet to stumble forward, then threw a punch with his other hand.

The spear slipped out of the golden puppet's grasp as it was sent flying back, crashing heavily into the army of golden puppets behind it, knocking down dozens of its comrades in a row before finally coming to a rest.

However, the golden puppet was able to immediately spring to its feet, but there was a very clear fist indentation on its chest.

After withstanding that blow, its movements had become slightly slower and more sluggish, but it continued to charge toward Han Li alongside all of the other golden puppets.

Han Li casually hurled the spear in his hand backward to send several of the golden puppets flying, then turned back just in time to see the fallen golden puppet spring back to its feet, and his pupils contracted slightly in alarm. He had used 50% of his strength in that punch, and it would've been capable of shattering an entire mountain, but it wasn't able to kill even a single one of these golden puppets.

At this point, all of the golden puppets had already swarmed around Han Li, and he gave a cold harrumph as he moved rapidly through the air, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake while lashing out with his fists.

Countless fist projections appeared before erupting in all directions, and the golden puppets were sent flying one after another.

All of the golden puppets that were struck received deep fist indentations on their chests before crashing into the puppets behind them, knocking dozens over at a time. As a result, the momentum of the attack was halted.

The puppets that were sent flying immediately sprang to their feet again after landing on the ground, and a cold look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he abruptly appeared in a wraith-like manner in front of one of the golden puppets that had just been flying, then threw another punch at the fist indentation on its chest.

The golden puppet shuddered as a series of cracks appeared over its body. Beams of yellow light filtered out of the cracks, following which the puppet exploded violently, disintegrating into a cloud of yellow mist.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon seeing this. These golden puppets possessed extremely resolute bodies, but they weren't indestructible.

The surrounding golden puppets continued to storm Han Li from all directions.

In response, Han Li took a deep breath, and six specks of blue light emerged on his chest and abdomen. His body abruptly swelled in size, and he began his retaliation.

A string of dull thumps rang out as seven or eight of the golden puppets closest to him were sent flying back before exploding.

Han Li's hands flashed through the air in a blur, unleashing countless fist projections that erupted through the air amid a string of resounding booms.

All of the golden puppets within close to 200 feet of him were sent flying before exploding into clouds of yellow mist.

With his strength enhanced by the Big Dipper Origin Arts, these golden puppets were no match for his fists.

……

There was a vast inky-black sea in the Immortal Realm.

Black mist permeated throughout the area, and gusts of Yin wind were howling incessantly over the surface of the sea, constantly raising massive waves that rose up to over 100 feet tall.

There was a massive black city situated in the area of the sea where the black mist was at its densest, floating atop the waves in a remarkably stable manner.

The city was over 1,000 feet tall and was over 100 kilometers in size. A plaque that bore the words "Black Water City" in large archaic characters was hanging above the northern city gate.

The walls of the city were constructed from giant rectangular black stones that reflected a crystalline gleam under the occasional ray of sunlight that managed to filter through the black mist. On the inside, the city appeared to be just like any other city, with rivers and farmland, streets and houses, everything that one would expect to see in the average city.

There were also many people roaming through the city, presenting a lively and bustling scene.

The terrain inside the city wasn't completely flat and steady. The closer one drew to the center of the city, the higher up they would find themselves, and the more closely packed the buildings became. The central area was also home to the most majestic palaces and pavilions in the city.

At the highest point of the entire city was a small inner city, which was clearly separated from all of the other buildings by a black river.

Inside the inner city were intricately constructed pavilions, soothing bodies of running water, and a series of fake mountains and well-maintained gardens. At the center of the inner city was a spacious platform, atop which stood a three-story pavilion that was entirely constructed from wood with intertwining arches and a glazed yellow tile roof. On top of the roof were beautiful dragon and phoenix statues that presented a display of remarkable craftsmanship.

On the top floor of the pavilion, all of the windows were opened, providing an extremely wide field of view. From this vantage point, not only could one see the entire inner city, there was even a clear view of the vast black sea outside of the giant city.

The furnishings inside the pavilion were very simple, with only a square table at the center, on either side of which was placed a round silken cushion.

On the table sat a dark red copper incense burner, protruding out of which were a few sticks of burning incense that were releasing fragrant smoke throughout the entire room.

On the cushion to the right of the table sat a thin elderly man with a purple lotus crown on his head. He was currently holding a beautiful teacup and carefully savoring its contents.

Inside the teacup was an elegant green tea that resembled translucent liquid jade, and its fragrance was extremely faint, somewhat overshadowed by the aroma of the incense smoke, but it was extremely pleasant on the tongue and rich in spiritual qi, providing a delightful drinking experience.

The elderly man slowly set down his teacup as he praised in an earnest manner, "This Black Water Spirit Tea truly lives up to all of the good things I've heard about it, Fellow Daoist Bone Flame."

Seated across from him was a black-robed man with a sickly yellow complexion, who replied in an indifferent voice, "You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Clear Bright. If you like it, you can take some back with you."

"In the past, we've rarely had any interactions due to the opposing nature of our sects in the lower realm, but here in the Immortal Realm, we should strive to work together more for mutual benefit," Daoist Clear Bright said with a warm smile.

Layman Bone Flame nodded in response. "If we can capture that Han Li, we'll most likely have to work together to uncover the potential secrets that he's harboring."

"Speaking of him, have you managed to find out anything about his history and origins?" Daoist Clear Bright asked as a serious look appeared on his face.

Layman Bone Flame shook his head in response. "I've done some investigation through certain avenues since you last contacted me, but I wasn't able to find any useful information. Have you made any discoveries on your end?"

"I'm afraid I was also unable to gather any useful information on him. The information that the Ubiquitous Pavilion is willing to divulge is very limited. All we know is that the client is a very powerful figure, but that's the extent of my knowledge on the matter for now," Daoist Clear Bright sighed.

"I'm even more interested in the secrets that this Han Li could potentially be harboring now. Looks like we'll have to interrogate him thoroughly after we capture him," Layman Bone Flame chuckled.

"You seem extremely confident, Brother Bone Flame. I presume you must've bestowed some powerful treasures upon your disciples, right?" Daoist Clear Bright asked.

"Are you saying you haven't done the same thing?" Layman Bone Flame countered as he took a glance at Daoist Clear Bright.

The latter gave a faint smile in response. "I naturally had to take some measures to ensure the success of this operation."

Daoist Clear Bright was clearly unwilling to divulge any specific details, so Layman Bone Flame didn't pry any further. Instead, he said in a nonchalant voice, "I managed to grow some Warrior Beans by chance a while ago, and only half a month ago was I able to successfully convert them into Dao Warriors. They're perfect for this cause, so I bestowed them upon my disciples."

Despite the nonchalance with which the statement had been made, Daoist Clear Bright seemed to be very surprised to hear this.

"You are incredibly fortunate to have been able to nurture Dao Warriors, Fellow Daoist Bone Flame."

"You flatter me, Fellow Daoist Clear Bright. The Dao Warriors that I managed to nurture are only Golden Dao Warriors, a type of lower third-grade Dao Warrior. That's hardly worthy of praise," Layman Bone Flame said with a dismissive sweep of his sleeve, but a hint of barely detectable pride flashed through his eyes as he spoke.

"Even so, those Dao Warriors will be far more powerful than most other treasures. With those Dao Warriors on our side, there's no way that Han Li would be able to slip out of our grasp," Daoist Clear Bright said with a clear hint of envy in his voice.

Layman Bone Flame merely smiled and offered no response.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Daoist Clear Bright, and he said, "By the way, that Han Li is technically a guest elder of the Cold Flame Sect. You don't think Cold Flame is going to get in our way, do you?"

"Unless he wants there to only be two top sects left in the Spirit Domain Realm, he would be wise not to get involved," Layman Bone Flame replied as a cold look appeared on his face.

Daoist Clear Bright nodded in response.

……

Inside a mysterious space, above a dense layer of gray clouds, three figures were standing in mid-air. They were none other than Tong Ren'e, Daoist Closed Mountain, and Duan Renli.

At this moment, Duan Renli was holding a yellow gourd while chanting an incantation.

The gourd was around half the size of an adult human, and there were circles of shimmering golden text on its surface. A series of golden runes that were similar to the text were drifting around the opening of the gourd, giving off an ethereal aura.

As his incantation rang out, a burst of golden light circled around the opening of the gourd, and a series of yellow bean-like objects flew out from within before descending out of the sky.

As soon as these beans came into contact with the gray clouds, a series of tiny vortexes instantly appeared in the clouds, swallowing up the yellow beans in a flash.

"Is this... the art of raising an army from beans? I didn't think your sect would be capable of unleashing such a legendary immortal art!" Daoist Closed Mountain exclaimed as he cast his gaze toward the yellow gourd in Duan Renli's hands with an envious expression.

"You're certainly very knowledgeable, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain. Truth be told, this immortal secret technique is far beyond anything that I can wield. I'm only able to summon these Dao Warriors using this immortal treasure bestowed upon me by our sect's patriarch," Tong Ren'e replied in an indifferent manner.

Chapter 64: Striking Together

"I see. Given how fearsome Han Li's physical body is, we won't be able to capture him through conventional means, but if we can wear him out with these Golden Dao Warriors first, then it'll undoubtedly make our job far easier," Daoist Closed Mountain praised with a nod of approval.

"It's all thanks to this domain treasure of yours that these Golden Dao Warriors can be put to good use. The first step of our plan has been successfully implemented, but we'll most likely have to strike together if we want to capture him," Tong Ren'e mused.

Right at this moment, Duan Renli's chanting suddenly ceased. "It's about time. Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain, can you show us what's happening down there?"

Daoist Closed Mountain nodded in response, then raised a hand to release a burst of silver light, within which was a silver bead around the size of an egg.

The bead circled around in the air for a moment before positioning itself in front of the trio, where it then exploded into a cloud of silver mist, which formed a silver mirror that was around 70 to 80 feet in size.

The surface of the mirror blurred momentarily, following which a clear image appeared.

The trio inspected the image with keen interest, but their expressions instantly changed drastically in response to the sight that they were greeted by.

In the image, one golden warrior after another was descending from the heavens before charging toward a tall and broad young man from all directions.

However, the young man was traversing through the hordes of golden warriors with ease while unleashing a relentless barrage of fist projections.

All of the golden warriors around him were immediately sent flying upon making contact with the fist projections, then exploded into bursts of yellow light, and none of them were even able to reach within 100 feet of the young man.

Within the span of just a few seconds, seven or eight of those golden warriors had already been destroyed.

The young man wore a calm expression, and his movements were fluid and languid, as if it wasn't taking him much effort at all to shatter these Dao Warriors.

Right at this moment, the surface of the silver mirror warped slightly before disintegrating into a large cloud of silver mist again.

"How is this possible?" Duan Renli exclaimed with an astonished expression.

"These Golden Dao Warriors don't know any secret techniques or cultivation arts, but all of them possess physical bodies comparable in power with high-grade body cultivators. Even if one of us were to be surrounded by such a large army of them, we'd be in a very difficult situation, yet he's able to deal with them with ease. It seems that we've still underestimated him," Tong Ren'e said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"Could it be that he's already recovered from his injuries?" Daoist Closed Mountain speculated in a concerned manner.

"If it were that easy for him to recover from his injuries, why would he have left the immortal realm and come to the Spirit Domain Realm? At this point, we have no choice but to forge ahead. As we planned in advance, we'll attack him together to finish this as quickly as possible," Tong Ren'e said in a cold voice.

……

Inside the domain.

Han Li swayed to the side to dodge the attacks from several golden warriors at once, then lashed out with his right arm to unleash seven or eight fist projections at once, each of which struck a golden warrior on the head with unerring accuracy.

The heads of those seven or eight golden warriors instantly exploded, and their bodies were sent flying before disintegrating into clouds of yellow mist.

The entire process was executed extremely cleanly and efficiently, and in the blink of an eye, close to 20 golden warriors were vanquished.

At this point, these golden warriors no longer posed a threat to Han Li, and he was killing them off faster than they could appear.

Once most of the golden warriors had been destroyed, blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes as he looked up at the layer of gray clouds overhead, trying to find an opening that he could exploit to see what was up there.

All of a sudden, the streaks of yellow light raining down from the heavens abruptly ceased. Immediately thereafter, a certain section of the gray clouds trembled violently, following which a rift that was over 100 feet wide was opened up.

Three streaks of light descended out of the rift, then faded to reveal a trio of figures.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he inspected the trio, and he discovered that aside from Daoist Closed Mountain and Duan Renli, there was also a short black-robed elderly man.

"It looks like you've joined forces with the Heavenly Ghost Sect, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain. How disappointing," Han Li mused with an indifferent expression.

"You can't blame me, Fellow Daoist Han. If you want to blame someone, then you can only blame yourself for making enemies out of people that you can't afford to oppose. I'm afraid that I had no choice in this matter," Daoist Closed Mountain replied.

A thought occurred to Han Li upon hearing this, and his expression remained unchanged as he cast his gaze toward Duan Renli. "I didn't think that you'd be able to recruit two other Grand Ascension Stage beings to your side, Fellow Daoist Duan."

"With your powers, you stand at the very pinnacle of the Spirit Domain Realm. If it were only for the sake of those 50 kilograms of Yin Dawn Stone, there's no way our Heavenly Ghost Sect would've chosen to come after you," the black-robed elderly man said with a serious expression.

"If I'm not mistaken, then you must be the number one cultivator of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, Fellow Daoist Tong, right? Who exactly have I made an enemy out of that warrants all three of you coming after me at once?" Han Li asked as he cast his gaze toward the elderly man.

"If you're trying to stall for time, then I'm afraid that you're going to be sorely disappointed, Fellow Daoist Han."

As soon as Tong Ren'e's voice trailed off, he immediately released an antiquated gray book out of his sleeve, then pointed a finger at it.

The book rustled audibly as its pages rapidly flipped past one after another while releasing bursts of gray light, which instantly transformed into a series of strange birds with ghostly heads, eagle bodies, and scorpion tails. Each of them was around 60 to 70 feet in size, and several dozens of them appeared in the blink of an eye before spreading their wings to circle around high up in the sky.

"Please pardon my intrusion, Fellow Daoist Han!" Daoist Closed Mountain said as he raised a hand to release a light blue plate treasure, which vanished into the gray clouds overhead in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, he extended a finger before pointing it up at the heavens, and the dense layer of clouds instantly began to churn while rumbling with deafening thunderclaps. Thick bolts of gray lightning began to flash through the clouds, presenting an extremely intimidating sight to behold.

Meanwhile, Duan Renli was chanting an incantation, and golden runes surged over the surface of the yellow gourd in his hands as hundreds of yellow beans flew out of its opening, then landed on the ground before transforming into more golden warriors.

The three of them had sprung into action in unison as if they had planned this in advance.

Han Li continued to unleash fist projections as his gaze fell upon the yellow gourd, and a hint of intrigue appeared in his eyes as he quickly realized that it was the source of all of the golden warriors.

As soon as he made this realization, he immediately unleashed a barrage of fist projections that swept through the air in all directions, sending all of the golden warriors in a radius of over 100 feet flying. Immediately thereafter, he sprang up into the air before flying toward Duan Renli.

The trio of Grand Ascension cultivators had gone out of their way to draw him into this domain, so they had to have more tricks up their sleeve than what was on display here. Hence, he had to seize the initiative and strike first.

Right at this moment, those strange birds in the sky circle around, and around a dozen of them swooped down toward Han Li.

At the same time, all of them thrust their scorpion tails in Han Li's direction, releasing countless thin black threads that rained down in a ferocious storm, encompassing a large area around Han Li.

Han Li flew diagonally through the air upon seeing this, leaving a trail of afterimages in his wake as he evaded all of the thin black threads.

However, right after he steadied himself before vanquishing a pair of nearby golden warriors, several more of those strange birds swooped down toward him from above.

Almost at the exact same moment, a deafening thunderclap rang out as a thick bolt of gray lightning came crashing down from the heavens with devastating might.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as golden light flashed from his body, and countless golden scales instantly appeared over his skin as he threw another punch upward.

A resounding boom rang out as the bolt of gray lightning exploded violently, and even though Han Li's fist remained completely unscathed, he was forced back a step by the impact.

Immediately thereafter, a string of loud clangs rang out as the thin black threads released by the scorpion tails of the strange birds fell upon his golden scales, but they were unable to leave even the faintest of marks.

After releasing a barrage of attacks, one of the strange birds was struck by a golden warrior that Han Li hurled upward before it could fly away, and it immediately felt a burst of tremendous force crash into its body, causing it to let loose an anguished cry before it disintegrated alongside the golden warrior.

Immediately thereafter, a string of deafening thunderclaps rang out as bolt after bolt of gray lightning came crashing down, tearing through the surrounding space with awe-inspiring might.

At the same time, the strange birds that were circling around in the sky were also attacking relentlessly.

Han Li was flashing through the air in an unpredictable manner, throwing punches to dispel the bolts of lightning that he was unable to evade while also occasionally felling a strange bird or two, and it seemed that he was able to hold his own quite easily.

However, as a result of this, he was unable to attack Duan Renli anytime soon.

More and more yellow beans were flying out of the gourd, and he was unable to vanquish them as quickly, seeing as he was distracted by all of these other attacks, so the number of golden warriors around him was constantly increasing.

Before he knew it, there were already around 3,000 to 4,000 golden warriors in the area.

What was even more concerning to him was that most of the golden warriors weren't in a hurry to attack him. Instead, they rushed away from him before abruptly coming to a halt, standing in what seemed to be a specific formation.

They're forming an array! Han Li thought to himself as his pupils contracted slightly.

Chapter 65: Yellow Rope

As soon as this thought occurred to him, Han Li immediately unclenched his fists, then spread his fingers open before picking up a nearby golden warrior and hurling it toward the golden warriors that were further away.

One of the golden warriors that was standing still on the spot was struck head-on, and the tremendous force of the impact caused both of them to disintegrate, releasing a powerful shockwave that toppled several more golden warriors in the surrounding area.

Han Li roamed through the area as he repeated the process, picking up one golden warrior after another as if they were sitting ducks before hurling them through the air to strike the golden warriors that were further away.

As for the gray lightning and the attacks from the strange birds that he was unable to dodge, he merely ignored them and allowed those attacks to strike his body.

After just a few seconds, the meticulous formation of the golden warriors had been plunged into complete chaos by Han Li's disruption.

Tong Ren'e's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he yelled, "We can't afford to delay any longer! Let's end this!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he immediately flipped a hand over to produce a rusty yellow badge, then made a strange seal with his other hand as he quickly chanted an incantation.

Dazzling yellow radiance instantly appeared on the surface of the badge, and Han Li's attention was immediately drawn to it.

He didn't know what this badge was, but a premonition of danger had welled up in his heart in the instant that it was summoned.

However, before he had a chance to do anything, the yellow badge flew out of Tong Ren'e's grasp, then transformed into a burst of scintillating yellow light that appeared in the sky above Han Li. The badge then began to revolve in mid-air as circles of strange spirit patterns lit up all around it.

All of a sudden, all of the thousands of golden warriors that were standing still on the spot raised their hands above their heads in unison before crossing their arms. Dazzling yellow light began to radiate from their bodies, then quickly converged to the point where their arms were crossed before erupting into the heavens.

All of the yellow light connected together in the sky before expanding in all directions to form a yellow light barrier, which instantly encompassed an area with a radius of over 10,000 feet around Han Li.

In the instant that the yellow light barrier appeared over him, Han Li immediately felt an incredible weight crashing down upon him, as if he were being crushed under a giant mountain, and his movements had become noticeably slower and more sluggish.

Right at this moment, plumes of yellow mist rose up from beneath the ground, then intertwined with one another to form lengths of yellow rope that flew toward him like a nest of spirit snakes.

The lengths of rope quickly wound themselves around his body, binding him tightly in the blink of an eye.

Before he knew it, his waist, arms, and legs had all been individually bound tightly to the ground, rendering him completely immobile.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly upon seeing this, and he activated his Big Dipper Origin Arts with all his might. The six specks of blue light on his chest and abdomen brightened considerably, further enhancing his already unfathomable strength as he twisted his body violently.

The lengths of yellow rope around him were instantly stretched taut, and the thinnest lengths of rope among them were trembling incessantly. Even though they were still binding him to the ground, they were no longer able to completely restrict his movements.

At the same time, the yellow gourd that Duan Renli was holding had already flown into the air above his head, where it was suspended in mid-air in a completely stationary manner.

Duan Renli opened his mouth to release several balls of blood essence onto the gourd, then began to chant an incantation.

Bright yellow light flashed from the surface of the gourd overhead, and it quickly swelled to the size of a house. The golden runes drifting around the opening of the gourd also expanded drastically while releasing dazzling golden radiance.

Countless yellow beans erupted out of the gourd in a frenzy, like a torrent of gushing water through a broken floodgate.

The newly emerged golden warriors all rushed over to certain positions before also raising their arms above their heads and crossing them, releasing bursts of dazzling yellow light that fused into the yellow light barrier up above.

Han Li clenched his fists tightly, and even though he was bound by the yellow rope, he was still able to throw several punches to destroy a few of the golden warriors and strange birds around him, but his movements were becoming slower and slower.

It seemed that with each additional golden warrior that appeared, the more substantial the light barrier overhead would become, and the more yellow mist that would rise up from the ground.

With the increased quantity of yellow mist rising up all around Han Li, the ropes that were binding him to the ground also became more and more resolute.

His body was feeling impossibly heavy, as if there were several mountains weighing down on his arms, making it more and more difficult to continue to unleash attacks. The yellow ropes were also constantly constricting with greater and greater force, restricting his movements further and further.

All of a sudden, golden light flashed over his body, and strands of golden fur sprouted out of his skin as he transformed into a giant golden ape in the blink of an eye, expanding drastically in size in the process.

He had unleashed his 12 Awakening Transformations once again to adopt his Giant Golden Ape form.

Tong Ren'e and Daoist Closed Mountain both faltered slightly at the sight of the giant ape that Han Li had suddenly transformed into.

Even though they had already learned from Duan Renli that Han Li possessed such a transformation secret technique, they were still stunned by the immense aura that Han Li was giving off in this form.

"What are you waiting for, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain?" Tong Ren'e yelled as he stowed away the antiquated book in front of him, then focused his attention fully on controlling the array down below.

Daoist Closed Mountain immediately returned to his senses, and a grim look appeared on his face as he chanted an incantation while making a rapid series of hand seals. Countless strange golden runes instantly surged out of his body in a frenzy, followed by a layer of dazzling golden light.

At this point, the number of golden warriors around Han Li had already exceeded 10,000.

Boundless yellow mist was surging out of the ground before flowing into the yellow ropes around Han Li to bolster them even further, and despite the tremendous strength of the Giant Mountain Ape, the ropes showed no signs of tearing.

A thunderous roar or fury rang out as a string of cracks and pops rang out from within the giant ape's body. All of its muscles then instantly swelled like balloons, while its golden fur turned as hard as steel needles before standing up on end. Following this process, the giant ape's body had doubled in size, expanding to over 300 feet.

However, the yellow ropes around his body also rapidly expanded amid flashes of yellow light, becoming even thicker and more resolute so he was still firmly bound, unable to escape.

Right at this moment, the giant ape's body rapidly shrank down to its original size of less than 200 feet, but the yellow ropes also shrank alongside it, refusing to let it escape.

No matter how the giant ape manipulated its own size, the yellow ropes were always able to keep up, as if they had been tailor-made for it, rendering its attempts to break free completely futile.

"He's still trying to break free! How delusional!" Duan Renli chortled upon seeing this.

"The time is now, Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain!" Tong Ren'e urged with tightly furrowed brows.

Daoist Closed Mountain offered no response, but he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, which flew into the air above the giant golden ape's head before revealing itself to be an antiquated azure scroll.

Daoist Closed Mountain pointed a finger at the scroll from afar, and a beam of golden radiance instantly erupted out of his finger before flying into the scroll.

Azure light flashed over the scroll, and it immediately unfurled itself in mid-air.

A burst of dazzling golden light appeared on the surface of the scroll, following which a golden nascent soul projection that was around five to six inches in size flew out from within.

The nascent soul bore the appearance of an elderly man wearing an ochre daoist robe and a purple lotus crown, and it was very similar in appearance to Daoist Clear Bright of the Origin Realm Temple.

At the same time, Daoist Closed Mountain began to chant an incantation, and golden light flashed incessantly from the already unfurled scroll as a series of ancient golden runes flew out incessantly from within before surging into the nascent soul projection.

The nascent soul was instantly enshrouded in golden light, and it gradually elongated before transforming into a giant golden sword that was over 100 feet in length.

Countless peculiar golden runes were engraved onto the blade of the sword, and there were also circles of runes revolving around the sword as it gave off bursts of terrifying fluctuations.

Tong Ren'e and Duan Renli couldn't help but exchange a glance in the instant that the giant golden sword appeared, and both of them could see their own astonishment mirrored in one another's eyes.

The giant golden ape immediately raised its head to look up at the massive sword overhead, and it clenched its fists tightly as six huge spots of blue light appeared on its chest and abdomen.

The muscles on its arms bulged as it tried to raise them with all its might to oppose the giant sword up above.

However, the golden ropes around his arms instantly began to glow brightly before exerting even greater restrictive force. Even so, they were still unable to completely bind him, and he was able to slowly drag his arms back toward his chest.

"Hurry!" Duan Renli yelled in an urgent voice.

Tong Ren'e's face was slightly pale, and his fingers were moving in a rapid blur as he released one incantation seal after another.

The yellow badge in the air instantly began to revolve at a far higher speed than before, and the bright yellow light also radiated from the bodies of all of the golden warriors down below, while more yellow mist rose up from the ground.

As a result, the yellow ropes around the giant golden ape constricted around it with even greater force.

The giant ape shuddered, and its arms were immediately snapped back to its sides again.

At this point, Daoist Closed Mountain finally completed his incantation, and with a triumphant roar, the giant golden sword in the sky came crashing down directly toward the golden ape's head as an enormous streak of golden light.

The giant sword rumbled through the air as it tore through the space beneath it, leaving countless thin gray rifts in its wake, all of which were releasing powerful spatial fluctuations.

The area encompassed under the sword began to shimmer and warp, becoming extremely blurry and indistinct. Even the clouds up above were being warped and displaced, and none of the strange birds circling around in the sky were able to get out of the way in time, letting loose anguished cries as their bodies instantly disintegrated into nothingness.

Meanwhile, the giant golden ape was completely bound by the yellow ropes around it, reducing it to nothing more than a massive sitting duck.

In this dire situation, the giant ape suddenly raised its head and let loose a thunderous roar. Scintillating golden radiance erupted out of its entire body, and countless golden scales emerged over its skin, while a single azure horn appeared on its head.

In the instant that the giant sword descended upon it, the golden ape tilted its head back slightly so that the horn was best positioned to oppose the giant sword.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the tip of the giant golden sword crashed heavily into the azure horn on the golden ape's head, upon which all of the golden light radiating from the sword instantly shattered before scattering through the air as boundless specks of golden light.

The entire surrounding space trembled violently as dozens of gray rifts appeared around the giant sword before fading in a flash. All of the golden warriors in a radius of close to 1,000 feet around the giant ape also exploded violently.

Amid the shower of resplendent golden light, the golden sword trembled violently before folding to an impossible angle, following which it was repelled back through the air.

As for the giant golden ape, it only shuddered slightly before returning to its original form, and it seemed to be completely unscathed.

"Impossible!" Daoist Closed Mountain exclaimed in an astonished voice.

Tong Ren'e and Duan Renli were also looking on with their mouths slightly agape in bewilderment.

Chapter 66: Spirit Nascent Sword Talisman

High up in the sky, golden light flashed erratically from the giant sword, and it was sent flying back for over 1,000 feet before coming to a halt.

Before Daoist Closed Mountain had a chance to do anything, the circles of runes on the surface of the sword began to glow brightly, radiating dazzling golden radiance as it came crashing down rapidly toward the giant ape once again, this time with even more power and ferocity than the last strike.

Due to the reduction in the number of golden warriors around it, the yellow ropes around the giant golden ape loosened ever so slightly, allowing it to twist around and directly face the giant sword. All of a sudden, it took a deep breath, and its chest swelled up like a balloon before it opened its cavernous mouth, letting loose an earth-shattering roar while blue light flashed within its eyes.

A burst of transparent soundwaves that were visible even to the naked eye erupted into the heavens out of the giant ape's mouth.

The space up above warped and twisted, and it instantly collapsed, caving in by over 100 feet like a crater left behind by an asteroid slamming into the ground, causing everything in the surrounding area to become blurry and unclear.

This was no ordinary roar. Instead, it was an ability known as the Vajra Roar, which Han Li was only able to unleash in his Giant Mountain Ape Form. It was an incredibly powerful soundwave attack, and unleashed by his current physical body, the attack was capable of shattering space itself.

Another resounding boom rang out as the giant golden sword plunged into the burst of transparent soundwaves with devastating force, only to be stopped cold in its tracks, unable to advance any further as it trembled violently.

As the soundwave attack continued, a string of loud cracks rang out, and the dazzling golden light being released by the sword was shattered like a mirror. A slight bulge appeared on the surface of the giant sword, out of which an elderly face that was identical to Daoist Clear Bright's emerged.

Immediately thereafter, a series of thin cracks began to appear on the surface of the sword, and before long, it was shattered into countless pieces before disintegrating into a vast expanse of golden light.

This was quite a lengthy process to describe, but in reality, everything had taken place in the blink of an eye.

Daoist Clear Bright's nascent soul projection re-emerged in mid-air amid a flash of golden light, and it seemed to have dimmed slightly.

There was an alarmed look on its face, and immediately flew toward the scroll that was hovering in the sky before vanishing into it in a flash.

Almost at the exact same moment, a long gash suddenly opened up on the giant golden ape's glabella, and a huge black demonic eye appeared. It was none other than the Law Destruction Eye, which was capable of piercing through space itself.

A black thread of light shot out of the black demonic eye, then vanished into thin air in a flash.

In the next instant, the black thread of light reappeared directly next to the antiquated scroll in the sky, then pierced viciously into the nascent soul projection that had already re-emerged.

The nascent soul projection instantly exploded into a ball of golden light amid an anguished wail, and immediately thereafter, the scroll burst into flames before being incinerated into ashes.

"That's... the Law Destruction Eye!" Tong Ren'e exclaimed as his expression changed drastically.

This was a treasure bestowed by the immortal patriarch of the Origin Realm Temple, yet not only had it been destroyed, the nascent soul projection residing within it had also been vanquished, and a grim look instantly appeared on Duan Renli's face upon seeing this.

A hint of fear immediately welled up in Daoist Closed Mountain's heart in the face of this development. He had no time to lament the loss of the treasure bestowed upon him by Patriarch Clear Bright as he was pondering whether it was time to flee the battle.

Right at this moment, an even more concerning development began to unfold.

All of a sudden, silver light flashed around the giant golden ape's body, and large bursts of silver flames erupted out of his fur, enveloping his entire body.

Plumes of yellow smoke began to rise up as the yellow ropes that were restricting the giant ape gradually melted and snapped in the face of the scorching silver flames.

After freeing itself from its bindings, the giant golden ape thumped its chest with its fists, then rolled over on the ground to snuff out the silver flames, but what took the place of those silver flames were countless arcs of silver lightning.

A giant silver bird that was over 100 feet in length spread its wings and flew out of the arcs of silver lightning. Its feathers looked as if they were forged from steel, and its talons resembled a set of hooks.

It was rather similar to the true spirit Kun Peng in appearance. This was another true spirit transformation of the 12 Awakening Transformations, the Lightning Bird.

An alarmed look appeared on Tong Ren'e's face as he accelerated his hand seals, and the yellow badge revolved frantically as yellow mist surged out of the ground in a frenzy to try and ensnare the Lightning Bird.

Duan Renli also immediately switched to a different hand seal, and the golden warriors formed by yellow beans that were gushing out of the giant yellow gourd in the sky converged toward the Lightning Bird rather than joining the array.

However, with just a casual flap of its wings, the Lightning Bird transformed into a gust of silver wind that abruptly vanished on the spot, evading the yellow ropes and golden warriors with ease.

Before the three Grand Ascension cultivators had a chance to react, a bolt of silver lightning suddenly flashed through the sky, and the Lightning Bird suddenly appeared directly above the giant yellow gourd before clutching it between its talons.

A burst of light flashed up above, and the Lightning Bird and the gourd shrank down in unison.

Moments later, Han Li reverted back to his human form, and he was holding a yellow gourd that was around a foot tall in his hands.

Daoist Closed Mountain's heart immediately sank upon seeing this, and he hurriedly said, "We're no match for him! We have to run!"

He then immediately sped away into the distance as a streak of golden light.

Tong Ren'e and Duan Renli also followed suit without any hesitation, fleeing the scene in such a hurry that they were leaving even the yellow badge in the air behind.

Han Li briefly inspected the gourd that he was holding, and a burst of azure light suddenly appeared over his palm before he rubbed his hand forcefully over the gourd's surface. The golden runes that were engraved onto the gourd instantly became blurry and unclear, and with one final wipe, they were completely erased.

At the same time, all of the golden warriors, regardless of whether they were standing in the array down below were charging toward Han Li, collapsed to the ground as if their souls had collectively left their bodies. Immediately thereafter, they reverted back to countless yellow beans amid flashes of yellow light.

The yellow array formed by the golden warriors naturally also instantly disintegrated.

Han Li flipped a hand over to stow the gourd away, then cast his gaze toward the fleeing trio in the distance as a cold smile appeared on his face. Silver lightning flashed over his body as he took on his Lightning Bird form again, and he instantly vanished from the spot with a flap of his wings.

At this moment, Duan Renli was frantically fleeing the scene, and he was feeling far from his peak condition.

Controlling the gourd and those Golden Dao Warriors had severely depleted his magic power, so he was flying far slower than Tong Ren'e and Daoist Closed Mountain, and as a result, he had already been left far behind by the two.

Right as he was lamenting his own ill-fortune, a burst of buzzing suddenly rang out beside him, and a thought immediately occurred to him, one that filled him with despair and horror.

Right at this moment, spatial fluctuations erupted no more than 1,000 feet above him, and a burst of silver lightning appeared, following which a pair of massive talons extended out of thin air.

Countless thin arcs of silver lightning were revolving around the claws of the talons, gradually forming a massive circular net of lightning that descended upon him.

Of course, as a Grand Ascension Stage being, Duan Renli was certainly no slouch. He was already prepared for such a scenario, and a vast expanse of crimson light instantly erupted out of his body as he opened his mouth to release a miniature crimson flag that was several inches tall.

As soon as the flag was released, it instantly swelled to around 10 feet in height, and crimson light surged over the flag as it released gusts of gorey wind and boundless blood mist, forming an enormous crimson cloud that encompassed Duan Renli's entire body.

However, before he had a chance to do anything else, silver light flashed above him, and the Lightning Bird emerged before folding its wings against the sides of its body, plunging down into the crimson cloud like an asteroid in free fall.

A burst of rumbling rang out as silver lightning flashed within the crimson cloud, and the entire cloud was torn into two before the Lightning Bird flew out the other side.

Clutched between its sharp talons was a humanoid figure who was struggling and writhing violently like a worm with a horrified look on its face. Black blood was gushing out of all of its seven orifices, presenting a ghastly sight to behold.

All of a sudden, the Lightning Bird said in a thunderous voice, "I spared you last time because I didn't want any trouble, but I didn't think you would be so foolish. It seems I have no choice but to put an end to your life here."

As soon as his voice trailed off, countless arcs of lightning converged toward the Lightning Bird's talons, and with one final blood-curdling cry, half of Duan Renli's body exploded amid a burst of crackling silver radiance.

Immediately thereafter, a dark red nascent soul flew out of his ruined body with a horrified look on its face, but before it had a chance to escape, it was struck by an arc of silver lightning that erased it out of existence in the blink of an eye.

Thus concluded the life of a Grand Ascension cultivator who had reigned supreme over the Spirit Domain Realm for tens of thousands of years. Not a single trace of him was left behind in this realm.

It had only taken a few seconds for Han Li to put an end to Duan Renli's life, and Tong Ren'e and Daoist Closed Mountain clearly had no intention of helping their companion. At this point, they were already far away.

……

In the inner city of Black Water City.

Daoist Clear Bright and Layman Bone Flame were still sipping tea while chatting with one another on the third floor of the pavilion, and their conversation gradually turned to matters related to cultivation experiences and insights.

Just as the two were having a spirited discussion, Daoist Clear Bright's face suddenly paled slightly, and he threw up a mouthful of blood without any warning.

"What happened, Fellow Daoist Clear Bright?" Layman Bone Flame hurriedly asked.

"The Spirit Nascent Sword Talisman that I sent to the Spirit Domain Realm has been destroyed," Daoist Clear Bright replied with a dark expression.

"How is that possible? That Spirit Nascent Sword Talisman contains enough power to rival an all-out attack from you! Even I wouldn't dare to directly oppose it. In addition to that, they had my Golden Dao Warriors on their side as well. How could they possibly have failed to kill that man?" Layman Bone Flame exclaimed with a stunned expression.

Daoist Clear Bright remained silent with a steely look on his face.

Chapter 67: Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost

Inside the gray space, Tong Ren'e and Daoist Closed Mountain were flying through the air as quickly as they could, covering vast distances in the blink of an eye.

In particular, after Duan Renli's aura was snuffed out, both of them frantically unleashed secret techniques at heavy costs to further enhance their speed.

Neither of them could even remember the last time that they had felt so horrified. In the entire Spirit Domain Realm, there were only a small handful of beings that were comparable to them in terms of cultivation base, and beings of their caliber very rarely entered battles against one another unless it was absolutely unavoidable.

"Fellow Daoist Closed Mountain, open up the spatial passageway right now! If we don't leave this domain, both of us are going to follow in Fellow Daoist Duan's footsteps!" Tong Ren'e urged as he took a fearful glance behind them.

Daoist Closed Mountain nodded in response, then flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized silver plate. Azure light then flashed from his other hand as he gently laid his palm down onto the round plate while chanting an incantation.

A burst of silver light instantly erupted from the plate, and the light gradually grew brighter and brighter as the chanting continued.

Countless silver runes began to emerge, and in the next instant, around a dozen beams of silver radiance erupted out of the silver light in unison, converging and intertwining in front of the two to form an indistinct silver diagram that was giving off spatial fluctuations.

Right at this moment, a muffled thunderclap rang out from behind the two, and their expressions changed drastically upon hearing this.

A speck of silver light appeared in the distance, and it was enlarging at an alarming rate, closing in on the duo at an incredible speed.

"How much longer do you need?" Tong Ren'e asked.

"10 seconds... No, eight!" Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly replied while continuing to make a rapid series of hand seals.

Tong Ren'e hesitated momentarily, then gritted his teeth as he said, "I'll hold him off as best as I can."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he began to chant an incantation, and at the same time, he tore off his black robe to expose his bare upper body.

There was a dark red image of a ghostly creature emblazoned onto his frail-looking chest, and it was giving off crimson light that was constantly fluctuating in brightness, as if it were a violent living creature that was constantly struggling.

There were several white objects on the ghostly creature's body that were giving off faint white light, suppressing the creature and keeping it subdued.

Tong Ren'e took a deep breath, then made a hand seal before pointing a finger at the white objects in rapid succession.

Bursts of dazzling white light erupted from the white objects, and a series of unintelligible white runes appeared. Immediately thereafter, the white objects sprang out of Tong Ren'e's chest, revealing themselves to be 13 white bone nails.

As soon the bone nails flew out of Tong Ren'e's body, the image of the ghostly creature instantly let loose a roar of excitement, as if it were a terrifying demon that had finally been freed.

Dazzling crimson light erupted out of Tong Ren'e's chest before enveloping his entire body, forming around a dozen incredibly thick pillars of crimson light. The pillars of light were giving off terrifying power, causing the surrounding space to churn and ripple incessantly.

Within the crimson light, Tong Ren'e gave a muffled groan as a pained look appeared on his face.

A string of cracks rang out from within his body, and his muscles squirmed as if they were living creatures as his body rapidly swelled in size.

In the blink of an eye, he transformed into a giant ghostly creature that was over 1,000 feet tall.

The ghostly creature was rather similar to the Blood Heavenly Ghost that Duan Renli had summoned. It was another heavenly ghost, but this one was even more terrifying.

Mysterious black and red patterns were running all over the heavenly ghost's entire body, and what was even more harrowing was that its chest, abdomen, arms, legs, and even the backs of its feet were riddled with eyes. In total, the heavenly ghost possessed in excess of 100 eyes, all of which were constantly blinking and radiating faint black light, striking the beholder with a bone-chilling sensation.

In particular, there was an especially massive vertical eye on his glabella that presented a harrowing sight to behold and forced the eyebrows of the eyes below it to the side.

However, that eye was tightly shut.

As soon as the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost appeared, Tong Ren'e's aura was elevated to unprecedented heights, causing the surrounding space to ripple and quiver.

Right at this moment, a silver Lightning Bird that was over 100 feet in size appeared in front of the two of them amid a flash of silver lightning, and a hint of surprise appeared in its eyes at the sight of the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost that Tong Ren'e had transformed into.

The Lightning Bird then spread its wings, and countless arcs of silver lightning appeared over its body amid a rumbling thunderclap as it abruptly made a forward-grabbing motion with one set of talons.

A set of terrifying lightning talons that were around an acre in size appeared out of thin air before grabbing toward the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost.

Even before the talons reached the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost, a burst of tremendous force came crashing down, causing the nearby space to constrict and tighten.

In the face of such an attack, the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost didn't display any fear. It immediately made a hand seal, and close to half of the eyes on its body lit up in unison before releasing bursts of black light.

Dozens of bursts of light intertwined to form a black net, which clashed with the giant lightning talons.

In the instant that the two came into contact with one another, a burst of faint law fluctuations erupted out of the black net, and the lightning talons abruptly vanished on the spot, then appeared several thousand feet away as if by instantaneous teleportation.

A burst of thunderous rumbling rang out as the lightning talons struck nothing but empty air, and countless arcs of silver lightning exploded through the air, causing the nearby space to churn and quiver violently.

A hint of surprise flashed through the Lightning Bird's eyes, and it flapped its wings vigorously to release two crescent arcs of silver lightning, one of which appeared on the heavenly ghost's left, while the other appeared on its right, and both of them converged to attack the heavenly ghost from both sides.

The eyes on the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost's body lit up once again, then released bursts of black light to oppose the two arcs of lightning.

Faint law fluctuations erupted once again, and the two arcs of lightning also vanished into thin air before appearing several thousand feet away, where they crashed into one another before exploding violently.

Daoist Closed Mountain was ecstatic to see this.

Two or three seconds had already passed, and through his wholehearted efforts, the silver diagram in the air was gradually becoming clearer and more substantial.

The Lightning Bird stopped attacking as it folded its wings against its sides, then completely disregarded what Daoist Closed Mountain was doing as it said to the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost, "I didn't think that I would encounter anyone capable of wielding spatial power here in the Spirit Domain Realm. You are truly worthy of your title as the number one Grand Ascension cultivator of this realm."

"There is no vendetta between us, Fellow Daoist Han. We only did this as we were instructed by our respective patriarchs in the Immortal Realm to capture you. Now that Duan Renli is already dead, I'm sure you've had a chance to vent your anger.

“I admit that your powers are far beyond ours, but those in the Immortal Realm won't just stand by and watch if you go too far and completely turn the Spirit Domain Realm on its head," the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost said, and even though it was delivering a threat, it was doing so in an imploring tone.

"As expected, this really does have something to do with the patriarchs of your sect. However, they're all far away in the Immortal Realm, so they won't be able to do anything about this," the Lightning Bird said in a cold voice.

The Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost faltered slightly upon hearing this. "You wouldn't dare..."

Before it had a chance to finish, the Lightning Bird suddenly raised its head before letting loose a sharp cry.

Arcs of silver lightning lit up around it once again, then converged toward its talons to form an enormous spherical net of lightning.

At the same time, a series of strange runes that were flashing with silver light flew out of its talons before vanishing into the net of lightning.

All of a sudden, the arcs of lightning on the silver net all disintegrated silently to release bursts of scintillating silver radiance, which then abruptly condensed to form two silver balls of lightning.

A layer of silver runes was distributed over the surface of each ball of lightning, and a burst of dull rumbling rang out as thin arcs of silver lightning erupted in all directions, releasing a terrifying aura that threatened to destroy everything in the path of the balls of lightning.

This was none other than Han Li's Lightningwield Technique! [1]

The balls of lightning were formed by the Lightning Bird's silver lightning, which was completely different from the Devil Vanquishing Divine Lightning he had used in the past. [2]

The Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost let loose a low roar, and all of the red and black patterns on its body lit up in unison, while all of its eyes sprang open at once.

The Lightning Bird raised its talons, and the two silver balls of lightning were instantly sent flying through the air, reaching the heavenly ghost at an incredible speed before exploding violently.

A pair of scintillating silver suns appeared in the sky before rapidly expanding outward as arcs of lightning flashed in all directions. Countless silver runes appeared on the surfaces of the silver suns as they came crashing down while releasing a devastating destructive aura.

Even though Tong Ren'e was already expecting a powerful onslaught from Han Li, he was still astonished by just how fearsome the attack was.

The Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost let loose a fierce roar as all of its eyes opened up wide, so much so that the corners of the eyes were tearing open slightly.

Bursts of black light that were close to twice as thick as the previous ones shot forth before intertwining to form a giant black net.

At the same time, the vertical eye on its forehead abruptly sprang open, revealing a huge eye that was as black as ink.

A thick pillar of black light shot out of the vertical eye before vanishing into the black net, which instantly transformed into a black light barrier that enshrouded the heavenly ghost from head to toe.

The two dazzling silver suns descended from the heavens before crashing into the black light barrier, and the light barrier immediately began to glow brightly while giving off powerful law fluctuations.

The light on close to half of the two silver suns instantly congealed as if it had frozen solid, but the other half remained completely unaffected as it continued to descend amid a burst of violent rumbling.

The black light barrier buzzed and trembled incessantly, and light was flashing erratically on its surface, but it refused to be destroyed.

Thus, an impasse ensued.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out from within the black light barrier, and the barrier abruptly swelled drastically in size as countless black runes appeared on its surface.

The pair of silver suns flashed before suddenly vanishing on the spot, then reappeared in the distance.

Immediately thereafter, the two silver suns exploded to form a pair of pillars of lightning, which erupted into the heavens to punch gargantuan holes through the gray clouds with ease. At the same time, a pair of bottomless holes were also blasted into the ground.

Enormous power fluctuations erupted from the giant lightning pillars, sweeping up gusts of fierce wind within several dozen kilometers of the explosion.

At the same time, the black light barrier also disintegrated to reveal the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost, and it appeared to be in terrible condition.

Not only was it panting heavily, all of its eyes were half closed, and the black light that they were giving off had become extremely faint. It was clear that they had been severely overexerted.

Daoist Closed Mountain was astonished by what he had just witnessed, but at the same time, the spatial passageway was about to take shape.

With one final string of incantation seals, the silver diagram in the sky began to glow brightly, then took on a clear and substantial form, revealing itself to be an image of a silver moon hanging in the sky.

[1]. For more information on the Lightningwield Technique, please refer to RMJI Chapter 1473: Lightningwield Technique.

[Back]

[2]. For more information on Devil Vanquishing Divine Lightning, please refer to RMJI Chapter 411: Cultivating Bamboo.

[Back]

Chapter 68: Pursuit

Daoist Closed Mountain was ecstatic to see this, and he switched to a different hand seal as he released a burst of blood essence out of his mouth, which fused into the silver moon image in a flash.

Inside the image, bursts of silver light were suddenly released by the silver moon that was concealed behind the mist, and the bursts of silver light intertwined with one another to form a shimmering silver vortex.

Bursts of spatial fluctuations erupted out of the vortex as a burst of dull rumbling that resembled a thunderclap rang out, and a speck of white light could be seen at the deepest point of the vortex.

In the instant that the spatial passageway was opened up, both the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost and the Lightning Bird turned to it in unison, and a hint of elation appeared on the former's face, while blue light flashed in the eyes of the latter.

Daoist Closed Mountain's gaze only settled on the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost for an instant before it was immediately directed toward the Lightning Bird, and he shuddered before turning around like a spooked hare and rushing into the silver vortex as quickly as he could.

Immediately thereafter, the silver vortex disintegrated into countless specks of silver light, disappearing in the blink of an eye.

In total, the spatial passageway was only open for less than a second, and all that remained of it were some faint spatial fluctuations.

Not only had Daoist Closed Mountain fled on his own, he had even closed the spatial passageway behind him, and the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost was furious to see this. "You bastard!"

Meanwhile, the blue light in the Lightning Bird's eyes faded, and a contemplative look appeared on its face.

During the brief instant before the passageway was closed, he had already captured all of the permutations of the spatial vortex.

"It's just you and me left now, Fellow Daoist Tong. It's time I settled my differences with your sect once and for all," the Lightning Bird said in a cold voice as it withdrew its gaze.

As soon as its voice trailed off, silver lightning flashed over its body, and it vanished on the spot amid a resounding thunderclap.

The Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost had no time to curse Daoist Closed Mountain for his betrayal as it frantically made a hand seal, and a vast expanse of viscous black qi surged out of its body, forming around a dozen thick tentacles that flailed wildly through the air around it.

Another thunderclap rang out, and the Lightning Bird appeared behind the heavenly ghost amid a flash of lightning, then lashed out with its talons at an incredible speed, leaving a trail of afterimages in their wake.

However, the black tentacles behind the heavenly ghost also reacted extremely quickly, wrapping themselves around the Lightning Bird in a flash.

A hint of surprise appeared in the Lightning Bird's eyes, following which arcs of silver lightning appeared all around its body, and countless silver runes also emerged from those arcs of lightning.

The runes exploded in rapid succession as countless thin threads of silver lightning sprang forth in all directions, tearing the black tentacles to shreds before reducing them to a cloud of black qi that was quickly eradicated.

The back of the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost was also struck by a thick arc of lightning, and the seven or eight eyes there were completely destroyed, causing black blood to gush down its back.

The Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost gave a muffled groan before frantically flying directly forward.

A burst of rumbling rang out from behind it as the Lightning Bird made a grabbing motion with its talons, and the arcs of silver lightning around it converged to form another pair of balls of lightning.

It then raised its talons up into the air, and the two balls of lightning flew up into the heavens before vanishing into the gray clouds up above.

A string of earth-shattering booms instantly rang out as the balls of lightning tore through the gray clouds, illuminating the landscape down below with scintillating silver light.

Two enormous pillars of lightning with countless silver runes surging around them abruptly shot out of the clouds, then came crashing down upon the fleeing Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost.

The heavenly ghost was greatly alarmed, and black light flashed from its body as it forced all of its eyes open again. Black light flashed within the pupils of its eyes as it prepared to unleash its spatial ability once again, but right at this moment, a bone-chilling harrumph rang out beside its ears.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of excruciating pain speared through its mind as if its brain had been viciously stabbed by a sharp knife, and it felt as if its soul were about to be torn apart at the seams.

The heavenly ghost threw its hands over its head as it let loose an agonized howl, and black blood began to flow out of all of its orifices.

The black light in the pupils of its eyes flashed erratically before fading, following which the two pillars of silver light struck its body amid a deafening thunderclap.

The Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost let loose a blood-curdling howl as two massive holes were instantly punched into its body by the pillars of lightning, and one of the holes was on its chest.

The heavenly ghost's body was almost torn into two, and black blood came gushing out as it plummeted out of the sky before crashing heavily down onto the ground.

A string of cracks and pops rang out as the Hundred-eye Heavenly Ghost's body rapidly shrank down, reverting back into a short elderly man in the blink of an eye. The elderly man was carrying extremely severe injuries with two large holes in his body, one on his chest and the other on his abdomen.

Blood was gushing incessantly out of Tong Ren'e's mouth as a horrified look appeared on his face.

However, in the next instant, a fierce look suddenly flashed through his eyes as he quickly made a hand seal.

Circles of black light instantly began to revolve around him, while his thin and frail body began to balloon up at an alarming rate.

"He's trying to self-detonate!" the Lightning Bird murmured to itself as it swept its talons through the air, releasing dazzling arcs of silver lightning that converged to form a ball of lightning in the blink of an eye.

The ball of lightning then came crashing down at an astonishing speed, but Tong Ren'e was able to self-detonate before it arrived, and the explosion released powerful shockwaves that tore through the nearby space.

Black light surged out of the spatial rifts, slowing down the ball of silver lightning in its descent.

A nascent soul that was several inches tall flew out of the black light before vanishing on the spot, then reappeared several hundred feet away in the blink of an eye. Protective spiritual light then flashed over its body as it attempted to flee the scene.

However, right at this moment, the silver ball of lightning exploded into an enormous silver sun, which rapidly expanded in all directions, engulfing Tong Ren'e's nascent soul in a flash.

An object shot out of the silver light before flying into the talons of the Lightning Bird.

Moments later, the silver sun slowly faded, revealing an enormous crater on the ground.

At this point, Tong Ren'e had already vanished without a trace.

The Lightning Bird vanished with a flash of silver lightning, and Han Li was revealed, holding a red bag that was giving off faint red light in one hand.

After that series of intense battles, he had reached the bottom of his magic power reserves, and his complexion had become quite pale.

He stowed the red bag away, then summoned a 1,000-year-old Cloud Crane Herb that he promptly devoured. After that, he raised his head to look up at the sky while chanting an incantation before sweeping a sleeve through the air.

Seven streaks of black light flew out before drawing to a halt in mid-air. These were none other than the seven Starmoon Mirrors that he had refined using Yin Dawn Stones, and they were arranged in accordance with the configuration of the Big Dipper's seven stars.

Han Li made a hand seal, casting streaks of light onto the seven mirrors, and they immediately began to revolve on the spot while radiating dazzling starlight.

Many black runes were also flying out of the mirrors before dancing in the starlight.

As Han Li cycled through a series of hand seals, the Starmoon Mirrors began to buzz incessantly, and the light that they were releasing became brighter and brighter, but they were trembling uncontrollably and becoming more and more unstable.

All of a sudden, Han Li made one final hand seal as he uttered the word "explode"!

The light radiating from the seven mirrors instantly reached peak brightness as they exploded into seven massive balls of light.

Han Li immediately began to make a rapid series of hand seals, and the seven balls of light quickly transformed into seven huge star projections that resembled a miniature replica of the Big Dipper at his behest.

Han Li instantly switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this, and light radiating from the seven star projections connected together to form a star array.

Han Li exhaled as he made a peculiar hand seal, and the star array instantly brightened, following which it split toward either side as if it were being torn apart by a pair of massive invisible hands.

Soon, an inky-black rift had appeared, and the rift seemed to be filled with boundless darkness, but there was a speck of light that could be seen at the deepest point in the darkness.

……

In the sky above the Origin Realm Temple's Star Gathering Platform, violent spatial fluctuations erupted from the giant silver moon as a spatial rift suddenly appeared down the middle, and Han Li flew out of the rift before hovering in mid-air.

The massive array that encompassed an enormous area around the Star Gathering Platform was still standing, and the bright silver light that was cascading down from the giant silver moon was intertwining with the radiance of the rainbow light barrier that encompassed the surrounding space, presenting a bizarre and ethereal display of lights.

At this point, Daoist Closed Mountain was already nowhere to be seen.

Han Li flew over to the light barrier in an unhurried manner, then threw three consecutive punches to smash a hole into the barrier before flying out from within.

The Origin Realm Temple outside was still standing peacefully in the night, and there didn't seem to be anything abnormal about it.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he released his spiritual sense and swept it through the surrounding area, following which he immediately cast a cold gaze toward the Heaven Stunning Peak in the distance.

In the next instant, he transformed into a streak of azure light and flew toward the peak like lightning.

Right at this moment, the earth around the Heaven Stunning Peak suddenly began to quake violently, and dozens of thick pillars of yellow light erupted out of the ground.

Each pillar of light was around 40 to 50 feet thick, and they reached all the way up into the clouds.

The pillars of light were riddled with earthy yellow spiritual patterns, which were giving off tremendous spiritual power fluctuations.

All of the pillars of light brightened in unison as they released bursts of yellow radiance, which connected together to form a thick yellow light barrier. From afar, it appeared as if a dense yellow cloud had appeared over the entire Heaven Stunning Peak.

Inside a hall on the Heaven Stunning Peak was a three-level platform that was entirely constructed from a type of yellow crystalline stone.

The platform was tapered from the bottom to the top, with the bottom level standing at over 100 feet in radius, while the top level was only around 20 to 30 feet.

The entire platform was riddled with yellow runes, and the dozens of earthy yellow pillars around the platform also had countless runes engraved upon them.

Daoist Closed Mountain was seated on the top level of the platform, and even though his expression was quite calm, the hint of panic in his eyes betrayed his true emotions.

He chanted an incantation while making a rapid series of hand seals, quickly releasing one incantation seal after another.

The platform and the dozens of pillars around it instantly began to flash incessantly with earthy yellow light, resonating with the array outside.

Seven or eight Body Integration cultivators of the Origin Realm Temple were seated with their legs crossed on the second level of the platform, and they were also chanting incessantly while injecting their magic power into the platform.

Outside the Heaven Stunning Peak, a streak of azure light arrived in front of the array before fading to reveal Han Li.

He took a glance at the yellow light barrier that enshrouded the entire mountain, and his eyes narrowed slightly as he took a deep breath. A string of cracks and pops rang out as his body rapidly swelled up like a balloon, while golden fur sprouted from his skin. In the blink of an eye, he had already transformed into a Giant Mountain Ape that was over 100 feet tall.

Chapter 69: Change in the Silver Moon

The giant golden ape thumped its chest with its fists, and a violent aura erupted out of its body, causing the yellow light barrier to sway and quiver.

Inside the hall on the Heaven Stunning Peak, Daoist Closed Mountain and the other cultivators of the Origin Realm Temple were all greatly alarmed by the sight of the terrifying giant ape outside the light barrier.

Sweat was beginning to bead up on Daoist Closed Mountain's forehead, and he sped up in his chanting as he pointed his fingers at the pillars around him in quick succession.

All of the pillars began to glow with yellow radiance, and the yellow light barrier encompassing the Heaven Stunning Peak became even thicker and denser.

The giant golden ape threw its head back and let loose a long roar, then swung a furry fist violently at the light barrier up ahead.

Dazzling golden light erupted from its massive fist as it sped through the air, sweeping up gusts of fierce golden wind before crashing into the yellow light barrier with ferocious might.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as dazzling golden and yellow light erupted forth in a blinding explosion of radiance.

The surface of the light barrier trembled violently, and the section that was struck caved in significantly amid a string of loud cracks. A series of fissures appeared on the light barrier around the giant golden fist before quickly spreading in all directions.

Inside the hall on the Heaven Stunning Peak, all of the pillars around the three-level platform trembled violently, and even the platform itself was displaying some signs of cracking as it flashed erratically.

The Body Integration cultivators situated around the platform all felt their dantians quiver violently alongside the platform, and they each threw up a mouthful of blood as astonished looks appeared on their faces.

The Divine Dense Earth Array encompassing the Heaven Stunning Peak was an array that had taken several array masters of the sect an entire century to construct under the guidance of Patriarch Clear Bright countless years ago, yet it had almost been destroyed by just a single punch!

A hint of panic flashed through Daoist Closed Mountain's eyes as he yelled, "Stabilize the array!"

He then gritted his teeth before opening his mouth to release a mouthful of blood essence, which transformed into a cloud of blood mist that fused into the nearby pillars. At the same time, he made a rapid series of hand seals as he injected his magic power into the platform in a frenzy.

The Body Integration cultivators around the platform hurriedly did the same upon seeing this.

Under their combined efforts, all of the pillars in the array lit up in unison, and the cracks that had been smashed into the yellow light barrier by the giant golden ape's fist quickly began to seal.

The giant golden ape harrumphed coldly upon seeing this, and its other arm also began to glow with radiant golden light before it unleashed another devastating strike.

The massive golden fist struck the exact same spot as before, and a series of golden shockwaves erupted from the fist, sweeping up gusts of fierce wind that blew through the air in all directions.

The entire array trembled and churned violently, and pillars of yellow qi rose up in a chaotic fashion in all directions.

As a result of the second strike, the indentation on the light barrier deepened by twofold, and the cracks began to spread over its surface again, with these ones even wider and deeper than the cracks from before.

Finally, the entire array completely shattered with a dull thump.

The hall on the Heaven Stunning Peak swayed violently while a massive crack appeared on the three-level platform, splitting it into two.

Seven or eight massive rifts also appeared on the ground in the hall, and all of the Body Integration cultivators shuddered uncontrollably as they almost fell off the platform.

At the same time, blood was gushing out of their mouths, and their auras were quickly waning.

Daoist Closed Mountain's complexion also paled significantly as he instantly rose to his feet.

However, before he had a chance to do anything, a resounding boom rang out, and countless cracks appeared on the roof of the hall before it collapsed forcefully, even though it was also bolstered by an array.

A golden fist projection the size of a house then came crashing down directly upon Daoist Closed Mountain.

A faint buzzing sound rang out as Daoist Closed Mountain flipped a hand over to produce a silver horsetail whisk, which he swept through the air to release countless silver threads.

He then made a seal with his other hand, and all of the silver threads instantly converged at his behest to form a silver Qilin projection, which clashed with the golden fist projection.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as golden and silver light intertwined, sweeping up a ferocious hurricane that erupted all the way up into the heavens before sweeping fiercely in all directions.

The entire hall was completely destroyed, and all of the Body Integration cultivators were sent flying by the ferocious gusts of wind. Thankfully, all of them reacted extremely quickly, frantically summoning all types of defensive treasures to protect themselves, so they remained relatively unharmed.

A portly figure shot back in retreat out of the fierce wind in an unsteady manner, and it was none other than Daoist Closed Mountain. He was holding a ruined horsetail whisk in one hand, and there was a look of horror and panic in his eyes as he hurriedly yelled, "Please wait, Fellow Daoist Han!"

Before he had a chance to say anything further, the giant golden ape appeared before him in a wraith-like manner amid a flash of golden light, then swung a massive golden palm down toward him.

The golden hand didn't appear to be moving very quickly, but in reality, it was rapidly descending and releasing a burst of terrifying power that threatened to flatten the very space itself.

Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly opened his mouth in a frantic manner to release a ball of white light, which contained an antiquated black inkstone.

There was a faint layer of light surging over the inkstone's surface, and it was clearly a treasure of quite a high caliber.

The inkstone revolved in mid-air as it rapidly expanded, and countless runes emerged on its surface. At the same time, it released a thick pillar of black light that managed to keep the giant golden palm at bay.

Daoist Closed Mountain immediately seized this opportunity to rush back in retreat while simultaneously flipping a hand over to produce a white jade pendant amid a flash of white light.

The giant golden ape let loose a low roar as it spread the fingers of the hand that was being kept at bay by the pillar of black light, and a series of golden spiritual patterns appeared on its palm.

The power that was being released by the hand was instantly enhanced by almost threefold, and it crushed the pillar of black light with ease before grabbing ahold of the black inkstone and tightening its grip.

The inkstone was completely pulverized with a dull thump, immediately following which the giant golden ape vanished on the spot before appearing not far behind Daoist Closed Mountain.

A furry golden hand reached out like lightning, and golden spiritual patterns instantly lit up on its surface as a burst of golden light swept forward with ferocious might.

Daoist Closed Mountain immediately turned around before sweeping an arm through the air, tossing the white jade pendant upward.

Red, yellow, and blue light surged over the jade pendant's surface, following which a burst of three-colored spirit flames erupted forth. The three-colored flames transformed into a three-colored phoenix that was over 100 feet in size in the blink of an eye, then flew directly toward the giant ape's oncoming fist.

Scintillating three-colored light radiated from the phoenix's body, illuminating the entire sky, causing everything around it to pale into insignificance in comparison.

An earth-shattering boom rang out in mid-air, instantly resounding throughout the entire Origin Realm Temple. All of the disciples in the temple instantly flew out of the buildings that they were in with alarmed expressions, then directed their gaze toward the Heaven Stunning Peak in the distance.

There, the entire sky had been split into two, with golden light dominating one side, while the other side was filled with scorching red, yellow, and blue flames. The two sides were locked in a fierce tug of war, and bursts of thunderous rumbling were ringing out incessantly.

The Heaven Stunning Peak and the entire area in a radius of hundreds of kilometers around it shuddered violently as gusts of destructive wind swept through the surrounding area.

All of the trees near the Heaven Stunning Peak were completely uprooted, and some of the giant rocks were also swept away by the ferocious wind, while everything else was razed to the ground.

The clash between the two bursts of terrifying power only raged on for a few seconds before the golden light quickly overwhelmed the three-colored flames, and the latter was completely crushed.

The three-colored phoenix let loose an anguished cry, and its body was also destroyed by the golden light.

Daoist Closed Mountain was sent flying back by the ferocious shockwaves, and the jade pendant in his hand was shattered with a dull thump.

He flew all the way back for several kilometers before crashing heavily into a mountain, then plummeted down onto the ground with countless rocks raining down all around him.

The giant golden ape also descended from the heavens, landing not far in front of Daoist Closed Mountain. The ground trembled violently, and rock fragments flew in all directions as a pair of huge craters were stomped into the ground by the ape's enormous feet.

The golden ape then lowered its head to look down at Daoist Closed Mountain with a cold look in its golden eyes.

Daoist Closed Mountain was absolutely horrified, but seeing as Han Li didn't immediately land the killing blow, a glimmer of hope welled up in his heart as he hurriedly said, "Fellow Daoist Han... No, Senior Han, please let me explain! It's not what you think!"

At this point, his heart was filled with nothing but remorse. If he had known that this was going to happen, he would've fled the Origin Realm Temple right away after leaving the domain. Perhaps he would've at least had a slim chance at survival then.

Right at this moment, a string of resounding booms suddenly rang out from the distance, and it was coming from the Star Gathering Platform's direction.

The giant golden ape raised an eyebrow as it turned toward the Star Gathering Platform, and Daoist Closed Mountain also hurriedly cast his gaze toward the same direction.

The eight mountains near the Star Gathering Platform were swaying in unison, and the peaks of the eight mountains exploded, while the eight pillars of light rising up from the mountains also vanished in a flash.

The massive light barrier overlooking the Star Gathering Platform then abruptly brightened before disintegrating.

However, the giant silver moon hanging over the Star Gathering Platform didn't fade. Not only that, but it had become even brighter than the sun and was trembling incessantly.

Bursts of invisible shockwaves erupted forth in all directions, and the surrounding space in a radius of several hundred kilometers was stirred up once again as trees were felled and mountains collapsed.

Immediately thereafter, all of the light radiating from the surface of the silver moon converged toward the center to form an enormous vortex. At the same time, lights of different colors appeared in the surrounding area, intertwining with one another as violent tremors ran through the nearby space.

All of the Origin Realm Temple disciples were staring at the scene unfolding in the sky in a slack-jawed silence.

The giant golden ape was watching the massive vortex in the sky with blue light flashing in its eyes, and it suddenly reached with one hand to make a grabbing motion, releasing a burst of immense suction force.

"Spare me!" Daoist Closed Mountain yelled as he tried to struggle frantically, but he was completely powerless to resist as the giant golden ape drew him into its grasp with ease.

The giant ape then opened its mouth to release the silver Essence Fire Raven, which transformed into a fiery silver rope in a flash before quickly winding itself around Daoist Closed Mountain's body several times.

With a casual swipe of the golden ape's hand, Daoist Closed Mountain was tossed away, following which the giant ape directed its gaze back to the spatial vortex in the sky with a grim look on its face.

Daoist Closed Mountain crashed heavily down onto the ground, and stars were dancing in front of his eyes.

His heart shuddered as he felt the terrifying power imbued within the fiery silver rope around him, and all he could do was lay obediently on the ground, not daring to move even a single inch for fear of irking Han Li.

Chapter 70: Extrarealm Flying Bean

In the sky above, the vortex on the surface of the giant silver moon had already expanded to over twice its original size.

A semi-transparent barrier could just barely be made out at the deepest point inside the vortex, and beyond that barrier seemed to be a completely foreign world.

All of a sudden, the semi-transparent barrier flashed as if something had crashed into it from the other side.

The giant silver moon trembled slightly, and a rift appeared on the surface of the semi-transparent barrier within the vortex.

A ball of piercing yellow light shot out from within, then began a rapid descent.

The semi-transparent barrier instantly sealed over again, following which the vortex suddenly began to shrink, and soon, the barrier could no longer be seen.

Blue light flashed through the giant golden ape's eyes, and it was instantly able to identify the object enveloped within the yellow light.

It was a bright yellow bean that was extremely similar to the beans that Duan Renli had released out of that yellow gourd earlier, but this bean was far larger, and there were countless profound runes engraved on its surface.

The large bean suddenly paused in its descent, then revolved in mid-air to release countless golden runes in a frenzy. The golden runes surged around the bean, releasing a vast expanse of golden light that basked the nearby area in a radius of over 100 feet in a golden glow that was rippling and warping incessantly, much like the disturbed surface of a golden pond.

Immediately thereafter, a crisp crack rang out, and the bean began to expand at an incredible rate while sprouting a head and four limbs.

In virtually the blink of an eye, the yellow bean that was originally no larger than a walnut had transformed into a golden giant that was over 2,000 feet tall, and its entire body was radiating golden light.

The golden giant was very similar in appearance to the golden warriors from before, with a completely bare upper body and bulging, vascular muscles on its legs and arms. It was as if its entire body were forged from steel essence, and its mere presence alone gave off a tremendous sense of pressure.

In the next instant, the surface of the silver moon shuddered once again, and countless yellow specks began to fly out from within. These were none other than the yellow beans that had been left in the domain treasure, and they were falling like rain.

Strangely enough, as soon as the yellow beans came into contact with the golden light that was radiating from the golden giant's body, they were immediately drawn to the giant by some type of suction force.

All of the beams that fell onto the giant's body were instantly sucked in, causing the golden giant to swell even further in size.

By the time all of the tens of thousands of yellow beans were drawn into the giant's body, it had swelled all the way to around 10,000 feet tall, standing like a pillar between heaven and earth, dwarfing even the nearby mountains.

An indescribably immense aura emanated from its body before sweeping in all directions.

"What the hell is that thing?"

"It's massive!"

"I don't like what's going on here! I think I just saw our supreme elder being defeated by that giant golden ape, and now, this thing has appeared out of nowhere!"

"Now's not the time to be chatting, we have to get out of here!"

All of the Origin Realm Temple disciples in the surrounding area were naturally horrified by this alarming sight, and many of them began to flee in all directions in a blind panic.

However, there were also quite a few disciples who were of the opinion that there was no danger in watching the unfolding situation from afar. Of course, these disciples consisted primarily of high-grade cultivators such as those who were at the Spatial Tempering Stage and the Body Integration Stage.

All of a sudden, the giant silver moon in the sky flashed a few times with silver light, then began to rapidly shrink. After just a short while, it had shrunk down to become a dull silver plate that was over 100 feet in size. Immediately thereafter, the silver plate came drifting down from the heavens, bursting into flames during its descent.

In the absence of the silver moon, the light of the stars that had previously been concealed was allowed to shine through again.

The giant golden ape completely ignored the changes taking place in the silver moon, and its gaze remained fixed firmly on the golden giant in the sky this entire time.

If it weren't mistaken, there was a very good chance that the yellow bean that had given rise to this golden giant had come from the Immortal Realm.

In fact, it was very likely that it was directly connected to the three immortal patriarchs of the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

Right as these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, the golden giant's face rippled slightly, and a projection of a human face with a sickly yellow complexion emerged. The golden giant cast a cold gaze toward the giant golden ape, then pounced directly toward it like a golden asteroid, reaching the giant ape in the blink of an eye before raising its right arm and throwing a vicious punch.

A yellow blast spread through the surrounding area like a turbulent wave, pulverizing all of the trees and mountains in its path.

The giant golden ape let loose a thunderous roar as its body quickly swelled to over 1,000 feet tall. At the same time, silver light flashed from both of its arms, and countless silver spiritual patterns emerged to form layers of complex arrays that spread over the entirety of the ape's arms, releasing a burst of terrifying power.

The golden ape then also retaliated with a punch of its own, and a silver hurricane swept forth from its arm.

The two fists of vastly contrasting sizes clashed violently with an earth-shattering boom and a vast eruption of golden and silver light, causing the nearby space to warp and buzz incessantly.

The giant golden ape's body shuddered violently, and the silver light on its arms was shattered as it was sent flying back like a giant cannonball. A string of loud thumps rang out as its body smashed its way through three or four small mountains in succession before finally crashing into a mountain that was over 10,000 feet tall, and only after plunging over 100 feet into the mountain did it finally come to a rest.

The huge mountain trembled violently as countless scattered rocks came clattering down, and it was almost toppled by the force of the impact. As for all of the buildings, cave abodes, and medicine gardens on the mountain, all of it was instantly reduced to piles of ruins and wreckage.

The giant golden ape flew out of the deep indentation in the mountain face before dusting itself off, and even though it was completely unscathed, there was a hint of astonishment in its eyes.

He was unable to express the full power of the Giant Mountain Ape due to his severely limited magic power reserves, but even so, this golden giant possessed truly unfathomable strength, so much so that even Han Li was feeling completely outmatched.

Close to 10 kilometers away, the golden giant paused in its flight, then landed heavily on the ground down below, causing the earth to quake and rumble beneath its feet.

It then bent its knees while leaning forward slightly, then pushed off against the ground forcefully with its feet.

An explosive bang rang out as ripples that were visible even to the naked eye spread through the air, and the golden giant rushed toward the giant golden ape like a shooting star, arriving directly above the ape in the blink of an eye before reaching down with its huge golden hands.

The giant ape was rather taken aback by the giant's speed and agility, but it remained calm and collected as a vast expanse of azure light surfaced over its body, and it rolled onto the ground before instantly transforming into a majestic azure bird that was around 400 to 500 feet in size.

This was none other than Han Li's Azure Luan Bird form, and the bird spread its wings before vanishing on the spot to avoid the golden giant's grab.

A deafening boom rang out as the golden giant grabbed onto the huge mountain that was standing behind where the giant ape was originally situated, and the top half of the mountain was forcibly removed.

The severed section of the mountain came tumbling down, crushing two other mountains behind it and sending violent tremors running through the ground once again.

An azure shadow flashed behind the golden giant, and the Azure Luan Bird appeared out of thin air before sinking its talons viciously into the giant's back.

Several long gashes were instantly torn into the golden giant's back, but they weren't very deep, and they were virtually negligible given how enormous the giant's body was.

The golden giant swatted a hand toward the Azure Luan Bird, unleashing a burst of tremendous power that caused a string of loud bangs to ring out in the air.

The Azure Luan Bird vanished yet again as an azure shadow, then appeared directly in front of the golden giant before giving its wings a vigorous flap.

Hundreds of feathers were instantly sent flying through the air before transforming into countless azure blades of wind, each of which was over 100 feet in length. The edges of every single blade of wind were giving off a sharp gleam, and they slashed into the golden giant's body at an incredible speed.

A series of gashes were sliced into the golden giant's chest and abdomen, causing it to fly into a thunderous rage. It immediately turned its head around before swinging an arm viciously through the air, but all it managed to do was strike an afterimage left behind by the Azure Luan Bird.

A glimmer of light flashed within the Azure Luan Bird's eyes as it began to fly around the golden giant, leaving a trail of afterimages in its wake as decoys as it searched for the next opportunity to strike.

To say that the golden giant's strength was remarkable was a severe understatement, but thankfully, its defenses weren't all that exceptional, and the Azure Luan Bird's attacks were capable of wounding it. The injuries appeared to be insignificant, but if enough of them were inflicted, the accumulating effect was undoubtedly going to culminate into something more debilitating.

Right at this moment, bursts of yellow light emerged from the golden giant's chest before quickly spreading over its entire body.

The wounds inflicted onto its back and chest rapidly healed within the yellow light, allowing it to fully recover in a matter of mere seconds.

The Azure Luan Bird couldn't help but falter slightly upon seeing this.

However, its eyes then narrowed slightly as it let loose a defiant cry, then elevated its speed to its maximal capacity as it flew around the golden giants while unleashing ferocious wind-attribute attacks.

The golden giant was incredibly strong, but its speed was far inferior to the Azure Luan Bird, which was renowned for its speed even among true spirit beings. As a result, it was flailing around wildly with its arms, but it was unable to even graze the Azure Luan Bird. However, the mountains in the area were not so fortunate, and the smaller mountains were completely pulverized, while the taller mountains were also toppled with ease.

The Azure Luan Bird continued to fly rapidly around the golden giant, the latter was quickly riddled with wounds.

However, yellow light continued to spread from the giant's chest, and regardless of what type of injury it sustained, it was always able to make a full recovery within a matter of seconds.

Not only that, but the golden giant's movements were gradually becoming more and more agile. It seemed to be familiarizing itself with the movements of the Azure Luan Bird, and it was slowly becoming more and more able to keep up with the bird's speed.

The two were constantly on the move as their battle raged on, destroying countless mountains and buildings in the Origin Realm Temple in the process.

Resounding booms rang out incessantly within the temple as widespread destruction ensued, and at this point, even the high-grade cultivators who had originally decided to stay and spectate had already fled the scene for self-preservation.

Daoist Closed Mountain was laying on the ground, watching helplessly as the sect fell into ruin, and he was desperate to do something.

If things were to continue like this, everything that had been built up over the course of the past 1,000,000 years would be destroyed!

However, as he raised his head to look up at the two deity-like titans locked in battle up above, he could only give a wry smile and lament his own ill-fortune.

Chapter 71: Holy Nirvana Physique

A deafening boom rang out as a giant golden palm that was several acres in size came descended from the sky, crashing down upon a blurry azure shadow with devastating might.

However, the azure shadow was extremely fast and was just barely able to evade the giant palm.

Having missed its target, the giant palm crashed down onto a mountain, causing the entire mountain to shatter and collapse with an earth-shattering boom.

The azure shadow instantly skirted around the massive palm to arrive behind the right arm of the golden giant that was connected to the palm, and bright azure light erupted from the crest on its head before spreading over its entire body. All of the azure light then converged toward its sharp talons, which were swept viciously through the air.

Dozens of azure talon projections came together to form a huge azure net that swept toward the golden giant's right arm, tearing through the space in its path with ease, creating a series of inky-black spatial rifts.

The golden giant raised its head in response, but it was still in the process of withdrawing its right arm, so there was no time for it to evade the attack.

A string of loud metallic clangs rang out as golden and azure light erupted between the azure net and the giant's right arm, but the explosion of light only lasted for an instant before the golden light was torn apart by the talon projections like paper.

In the face of the azure net, the golden giant's right arm was sliced off with ease as if it were made from tofu.

A hint of elation appeared in the Azure Luan Bird's eyes, but right at this moment, the golden spiritual patterns on the surface of the severed arm suddenly began to glow brightly, and it instantly exploded into an enormous cloud of yellow mist.

In the blink of an eye, the cloud of mist had already expanded to encompass an area that was dozens of acres in size.

The Azure Luan Bird immediately turned and fled the scene as soon as it realized that something was wrong, but the cloud was too massive to escape from.

All of a sudden, the Azure Luan Bird felt the air constrict around it, and its movements instantly became extremely slow and sluggish.

There were countless thin yellow threads dispersed throughout the cloud of yellow mist, and those threads had bound its entire body.

The Azure Luan Bird let loose an alarmed cry as it attempted to spread its wings and struggle free from its bindings, but the yellow threads around it instantly released a torrent of countless yellow runes in response.

The air around the Azure Luan Bird tightened even further, and it felt as if it were being crushed under a giant mountain, making it an immense struggle just to make even the slightest movement.

However, in the next instant, a vast expanse of silver flames erupted forth to envelop its entire body.

The thin yellow threads quickly melted and disintegrated within the silver flames, but there were countless more yellow threads converging from all directions to bind the Azure Luan Bird tightly once again.

Thus, a cycle ensued in which the thin threads around the Azure Luan Birds were constantly disintegrating and reforming, and during this process, it was able to regain some mobility.

Blue light flashed in its eyes as it attempted to find a way out, but right at this moment, the surrounding space suddenly dimmed, and at the same time, a burst of invisible force came crashing down upon it.

Immediately thereafter, an enormous hand appeared around the Azure Luan Bird, and the hand was so close that every single line on its enormous handprint was clearly visible.

As soon as the hand emerged, it immediately began to close around the Azure Luan Bird.

Han Li frantically adopted his Giant Mountain Ape form upon seeing this, and he was able to complete the transformation right as the giant hand closed around his body.

An agonized look appeared on the giant golden ape's face as bursts of tremendous force compressed toward its body from all directions, causing its bones to creak and shudder, but thankfully, its physical body was strong enough to withstand the crushing force of the giant's grip for now.

What was truly astonishing to Han Li was that his Flame of Essence was completely ineffective on the giant hand.

Right at this moment, the surrounding cloud of yellow mist swept back rapidly, revealing the enormous figure of the golden giant not far away. There was a sinister smile on the giant's sickly yellow face, and its left hand was closed tightly around the giant golden ape.

A speck of piercing yellow light flashed from the giant's chest, immediately following which all of the yellow mist converged toward the wound left behind by its severed right arm.

The mist quickly churned and intertwined to form a brand new arm, which the golden giant immediately clenched into a mountainous fist, then raised it up high before sending it crashing down toward the giant ape's head with devastating might.

Even before the fist arrived, the tremendous power imbued within it was already causing the surrounding space in a radius of close to 1,000 feet to warp and rumble violently.

A hint of despair welled up in the giant golden ape's heart upon seeing this.

Even with his immensely powerful physical body, being struck by such a fearsome blow would undoubtedly result in at least severe injuries, if not death.

With that in mind, Han Li was forced to make a decision, and he quickly made a hand seal as bright purple light erupted from his body.

The golden giant's fist came crashing down with devastating force, but in the next instant, a hint of surprise appeared on its face.

Contrary to its expectations, its fist wasn't able to smash through the giant ape's head. Instead, a dull thump rang out as a burst of purple light pierced through the back of its hand, and the fingers of its other hand were also folded back as if they had been snapped.

The purple light flew over to a short distance away, then faded to reveal a golden ape that was around 2,000 to 3,000 feet tall.

However, in contrast with before, this giant ape's entire body was covered in countless purplish-golden scales, and there was an azure horn on the top of its head. In addition to that, two more pairs of furry ape arms had grown out of its shoulders and ribs.

[1]

A serious look appeared on the golden giant's face as it cast its gaze toward the six-armed giant ape, and the injuries dealt to its two hands were instantly healed.

A layer of yellow light appeared over each of its two fists, and several massive golden runes flew out of the yellow light, then circled around before fusing into its fists in a flash. As a result, its fists swelled to around twice their original size, and a burst of terrifying power akin to a volcano on the brink of eruption was brewing within those fists. Even though the power hadn't been unleashed yet, the nearby space was already trembling and buzzing incessantly.

The six-armed giant ape let loose a long roar upon seeing this, and it took a huge stride forward, instantly covering a distance of thousands of feet as it arrived directly in front of the golden giant, then lashed out with its fists, which were glowing with radiant purplish-golden light.

The golden giant immediately responded in kind without any hesitation.

Two pairs of fists clashed violently with an earth-shattering boom, and the nearby space began to buzz loudly as destructive shockwaves swept through the surrounding area.

This time, the six-armed giant ape remained completely unmoved, while the golden giant was sent flying back through the air.

Not only that, but its fists had been reduced to nothing more than grotesque masses of mangled flesh, and its arms had also been completely snapped and bent to strange angles.

The golden giant's eyes were full of incredulity as it flew back for several thousand feet before crashing heavily into a mountain, which was instantly topped like a pile of frail sticks.

Even after plowing through the mountain, the golden giant didn't slow down in the slightest as it continued to fly back, and only after toppling several mountains in a row was it just barely able to arrest its momentum.

At this point, the six-armed giant ape had already caught up,

The golden giant was quite surprised by this sudden turn of events, but it remained calm and unflustered as yellow light surged out of its chest before quickly spreading to its snapped arms to repair the damage there. At the same time, it swept its right leg horizontally through the air like a giant blade, aiming a vicious kick at the giant ape's midsection.

Enormous power surged through the air, sweeping up a huge white blast for energy.

The six-armed giant ape suddenly crouched down, rolling over in an extremely ugly maneuver to evade the kick, then instantly sprang forward to crash into the golden giant's body with tremendous force. At the same time, it wound its bottom pair of arms tightly around the giant as it was sent flying back through the air.

An alarmed look appeared on the golden giant's face, and bright yellow light erupted out of its entire body as it raised its arms, which were still yet to be fully healed, in a frantic attempt to struggle free.

However, the giant golden ape then reached out with its middle pair of arms to latch onto the giant's arms in a vice-like grip before snapping them once again. At the same time, purplish-golden light flashed from its top pair of arms, and they began to release a metallic gleam as they were plunged viciously toward the giant's chest.

The pair of arms instantly pierced into the giant's body, then churned around forcefully. The golden giant's movements instantly ceased, and the light in its eyes rapidly faded, while the recovery of its arms also came to a grinding halt.

A furious look appeared on the projection of the sickly yellow face before it also quickly faded away.

Han Li then withdrew his arms from the golden giant's body, and one of his hands was holding a yellow bean that was giving off dazzling radiance.

The golden giant shuddered, and as Han Li's arms were withdrawn from its chest, all of the golden light emanating from its body completely faded. It reflexively stumbled back a few steps as countless cracks appeared on the surface of its massive body, and it quickly disintegrated into an enormous cloud of yellow mist that was scattered by the wind.

Almost at the exact same moment, the six-armed giant ape's aura plummeted drastically, and it reverted back into Han Li's human form amid a flash of purplish-golden light.

His face was extremely pale, and he hurriedly summoned a Cloud Crane Herb that he promptly devoured, and only then did his complexion improve slightly.

Looking at the gradually dissipating cloud of yellow mist, Han Li heaved a long sigh of relief as a hint of lingering fear flashed through his eyes.

The golden giant wasn't capable of using any cultivation arts or secret techniques, but its physical body and strength were no less powerful than a Profound Immortal's, and he was no match for it without unleashing his Holy Nirvana Physique.

However, not only did this ability have extremely steep physical requirements on the user, it also expended a vast amount of magic power, far more than what he was able to muster up with his current magic power reserves.

Originally, it would've required the absorption of a vast amount of the world's origin qi to recover the function of his Organ Refinement Origin Arts, but thankfully, after mastering the sixth level of the Big Dipper Origin Arts, he was able to recover some of the cultivation art's function, thereby allowing him to use his organs as vessels for magic power.

Even though doing so required the expenditure of dozens of times the amount of quintessential purple qi that was normally required, he had still devoured almost his entire supply of Cloud Crane Herbs without any hesitation as soon as he noticed the abnormal activity taking place in the Origin Realm Temple.

Even so, he was still only able to maintain his Holy Nirvana Physique for a few seconds, and it wasn't even at peak power during those few seconds.

Thankfully, the golden giant wasn't able to react sufficiently quickly to the situation. If it had immediately fled to buy just a little bit of time as soon as Han Li completed his transformation, the outcome of that battle would've been completely different.

As the medicinal power of the Cloud Crane Herb was converted into magic power, a hint of color quickly returned to Han Li's complexion, and he took a glance at the yellow bean in his hand, then raised an eyebrow before stowing it away.

[1]. For more information on the Holy Nirvana Physique, please refer to RMJI Chapter 2005: Holy Nirvana Physique.

[Back]

Chapter 72: Subjugating a Grand Ascension Cultivator

On a spacious rooftop somewhere in the inner city of Black Water City, Daoist Clear Bright and Layman Bone Flame were standing next to one another in silence.

The latter's brows were tightly furrowed, and he had a furious look on his face, looking as if he could snap at any moment.

The former's expression wasn't much more pleasant, and after a long while, he finally mused, "Who exactly is this man? Not only was my Spirit Nascent Sword Talisman unable to strike him down, even you..."

His voice trailed off there as he heaved a faint sigh, not wanting to speak any further on the matter.

A pained look appeared on Layman Bone Flame's face as he spat through gritted teeth, "That Golden Dao Warrior of mine was close to a Profound Immortal in power, how could it possibly have been defeated by a descended immortal?"

He had broken through the interrealm barrier at great cost to forcibly open up a spatial passageway and send down a primary bean, but only a short while later, his connection with the bean was completely severed, leaving him both furious and despondent by the loss.

"It seems like either the Ubiquitous Pavilion's information is inaccurate, or he must've encountered some especially fortunate circumstances that allowed him to return to full power. Now that we've failed to capture him, there's going to be trouble looming for our two sects in the Spirit Domain Realm. We have to find a way to address that as quickly as possible," Daoist Clear Bright said with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Layman Bone Flame's expression darkened even further upon hearing this. "He's not getting away with this!"

……

Meanwhile, in the Origin Realm Temple.

Daoist Closed Mountain looked on as Han Li approached him in an expressionless manner, and his flabby rolls began to tremble uncontrollably from fear.

If he hadn't been bound by the rope formed by the Flame of Essence, he would've already fled the scene even faster than the elders and disciples of the temple.

Han Li drew to a halt before him, then stared at him expressionlessly for a while before suddenly raising a hand and extending a finger toward his glabella.

"Spare me, Senior Han! I was only following orders! I had no choice!" Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly implored as his back instantly became drenched in cold sweat.

"Is that right? Whose orders were you acting on?" Han Li asked with a faint smile as he lowered his hand again.

"The orders were from the patriarch of our temple in the Immortal Realm. Otherwise, there's no way I would've dared to try and go against you, Senior Han," Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly replied.

"Why would the patriarch of your Origin Realm Temple issue an order to have me captured? Does he know me?" Han Li asked.

"According to our patriarch, a powerful organization in the Immortal Realm is offering a reward for your capture, and the reward is far loftier than what lower realm cultivators like myself can imagine. Patriarch Bone Flame of the Heavenly Ghost Sect received the bounty, and he coaxed our patriarch into joining forces with him. That's what led to this... this misunderstanding," Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly replied.

"Misunderstanding? You make it sound so trivial! So you're telling me that Patriarch Bone Flame received the bounty, but Patriarch Clear Bright of your Origin Realm Temple didn't?" Han Li asked with an unconvinced expression.

Daoist Closed Mountain's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and he carefully answered, "Perhaps the two patriarchs hatched the plan together. I'm only responsible for carrying out their orders, I don't know the exact details. I was extremely reluctant to oppose you, Senior Han, but I couldn't go against the orders of the patriarchs."

Han Li fell silent upon hearing this, and he began to ponder the information that he had just received, particularly the part pertaining to the reward being offered for his capture.

Daoist Closed Mountain was rather unnerved by Han Li's silence, and he thought that Han Li was hesitating about whether to take his life. Thus, the longer the silence continued, the more fearful he became, and finally, he gritted his teeth as he made a decision.

"Senior Han, your power is unmatched. From this day forth, I wish to follow you as my master. I can give you all of my pills and cultivation resources, and the entire Origin Realm Temple will also be yours to do with as you see fit."

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which he remarked with an amused expression, "You sure are adaptable."

Given Han Li's personality, he had no plans to spare Daoist Closed Mountain, but before he even had a chance to perform a soul search, Daoist Closed Mountain had already told him everything and had pledged his subordination to him, thereby saving him a lot of trouble.

After all, he had no intention of stirring up too much trouble in the Spirit Domain Realm.

Back in the Spirit Realm, he had encountered many Grand Ascension Stage beings, but never had he met one like Daoist Closed Mountain, and he couldn't help but think of a certain Sun Ergou. [1]

Daoist Closed Mountain could see that Han Li didn't seem opposed to the idea, and he immediately said in a respectful voice, "Thank you for sparing my life, Senior Han!"

"I have no interest in taking over your Origin Realm Temple. All you need to do is follow my orders and do some things for me. However, before that, I have to apply some restrictions onto you," Han Li said.

He raised a hand as he spoke, then chanted an incantation, and the tips of the five fingers on the hand lit up in unison. A series of thin translucent threads then emerged from his fingertips, swaying from side to side like seaweed in the current.

Han Li curled his fingers ever so slightly, and the translucent threads instantly became as straight as needles.

Daoist Closed Mountain shuddered slightly upon seeing this, and his face also turned quite pale, but he still displayed no intention of putting up any resistance.

A pleased look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and as he reached forward with his hand, the five translucent threads instantly shot into Daoist Closed Mountain's head.

In the instant that the translucent threads pierced into his body, Daoist Closed Mountain felt a sharp pain spear through his consciousness, and he couldn't help but let loose an agonized groan as his face paled even further.

However, he was still putting up no resistance whatsoever, allowing Han Li to do as he pleased.

Han Li swept a hand through the air to dispel the fiery silver rope around Daoist Closed Mountain's body, then said, "Those threads are formed by my spiritual sense, and they've already been planted deep into your soul. If you dare to go against me, I can destroy your soul from the inside with just a single thought, understood?"

"Yes, Senior Han. I'll be sure to serve you with the utmost loyalty and sincerity!" Daoist Closed Mountain replied with his head lowered in a respectful manner.

"There's no need to declare your loyalty to me. Instead, why don't you tell me where the array that you use to communicate with the Immortal Realm is?" Han Li asked.

"There are two such arrays, one on the Heaven Worship Peak, and the other on the Illustrious Mountain Peak. I'll take you to them right away, Senior Han," Daoist Closed Mountain replied without any hesitation.

Shortly thereafter, two streaks of light flew away into the distance.

At this point, peace and quiet had already returned to the Origin Realm Temple, but not long after that, two rumbling booms suddenly rang out one after another, separated by no more than 15 minutes.

Many of the elders and disciples who had only just returned to the temple were still feeling quite spooked, and they were greatly alarmed to hear this, but they were relieved to see that nothing more came out of the situation.

It had been an extremely tumultuous night, during which close to a third of the entire Origin Realm Temple had been reduced to ruins. In addition to that, the supreme elder was nowhere to be found, and everyone was wondering if the nightmare had truly ended.

Around an hour later, two figures flew over to a certain mountain deep in the Origin Realm Temple from afar, then entered a hall on the mountain.

At the very center of the hall was a white jade platform, upon which were engraved circles of complex runes to form a teleportation array.

"This is the teleportation array that leads to the Heavenly Ghost Sect?" Han Li asked as he inspected the array before him.

"That's right. This array is connected to the Heavenly Ghost Sect's Black Nether Peak, and even though it can't take us directly into the sect's core area, it'll allow us to bypass their sect's protective array," Daoist Closed Mountain immediately replied.

"Good. Come with me," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Yes, Senior Han!"

Thus, the two of them stepped into the array, and a burst of dazzling white light rose up from the ground to instantly engulf the two of them.

……

On the Serene Offering Peak of the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

On the main seat in a spacious hall sat a middle-aged man in a red silken robe. He had a pair of gentle eyes, and the lines and contours of his face were quite soft. There was also a slightly sickly white pallor to his skin, and overall, those traits culminated in a slightly feminine appearance.

At the moment, the man had an extremely grim look on his face, and he was gripping tightly onto the armrests of his chair as he said in a solemn voice, "Half a day ago, the soul badges of our sect's two supreme elders shattered in unison. Since then, we've tried to contact them using various secret techniques, but have received no response. What do you all think of this?"

There were around a dozen people seated on either side of the hall, all of whom were at the Body Integration Stage, and they were all silent with grim looks on their faces.

Thus, the entire hall fell into a tense and uncomfortable silence.

After a long while, a man with a thick beard was finally unable to bear the silence any longer, and he rose to his feet as he said, "Those soul badges must've malfunctioned somehow, Sect Master. Elder Tong is the number cultivator of the Spirit Domain Realm, who could possibly have killed him in this realm?"

"Exactly! Something must've gone wrong," someone in the hall immediately chimed in in agreement.

A beautiful woman in a red dress stood with tightly furrowed brows as she countered, "Soul badges are refined using a special secret technique with a cultivator's blood essence and a wisp of their soul acting as the medium. Has there ever been a case of a soul badge malfunctioning in the past?"

The bearded man opened his mouth to rebuke her, but he had no counterargument.

"There's no way the soul badges could've malfunctioned, but at the same time, it's extremely unlikely that our supreme elders could've both perished in such a short time. Is it possible that they've been trapped within some type of special array that's severed their connection to their soul badges?" another elder suggested.

A middle-aged man with a square face and a short purple beard rose to his feet as he said, "Regardless of what happened, the fact of the matter is that the two supreme elders went to the Origin Realm Temple, and now, we're unable to get into contact with them. What we should be doing is activating all of our sect's defensive arrays and contacting our patriarchs in the Immortal Realm as soon as possible."

The sect master was gently massaging his own glabella as he replied, "I agree. Elder Lu, you can take care of activating all of the arrays. As for contacting our patriarchs, I'll..."

Before he had a chance to finish, a burst of loud rumbling rang out, and the entire hall began to tremble violently.

"What's going on?"

Everyone immediately flew out of the hall at once, then arrived on the plaza outside.

There was a black light barrier hanging in the sky above the hall. The light barrier encompassed an area with a radius of several hundred kilometers, and it was none other than the Heavenly Ghost Sect's main protective array.

The dozens of mountains encompassed beneath the light barrier comprised the core area of the entire Heavenly Ghost Sect, and almost all of the sect's most important locations were situated on those mountains.

At this moment, the black light barrier was flashing incessantly with runes surging all over its surface, appearing to be in an extremely unstable state.

Outside the light barrier was a giant golden ape that was several hundred feet tall, and its arms were raised high above its head, seemingly preparing to land another blow on the already wavering black light barrier.

[1]. For more information on Sun Ergou, please refer to RMJI Chapter 100: Jia Yuan City.

[Back]

Chapter 73: Erasing a Sect

Two resounding booms rang out as the giant golden ape's fists came crashing down. The black light barrier ripped as two deep indentations appeared on the sections that were struck.

"Where did this thing come from? Its strength is incredible!"

"This thing seems to be rather similar to the legendary true spirit, the Giant Mountain Ape! Could it be..."

"In any case, we can't just allow this neanderthal to do as it pleases! We must capture it and execute it for challenging the authority of our sect!"

All of the Body Integration Stage elders initially faltered slightly at the sight of the giant golden ape, following which they briefly speculated about its origins, then summoned their treasures before flying up to oppose the giant ape.

Elder Lu was just about to join them when a hint of recognition flashed through his eyes, and he immediately stopped cold in his tracks. He wasn't the only one who was hanging behind. Aside from the sect master, there was also a hunch-backed elderly man, a beautiful woman, and a one-eyed man who were also refraining from joining the others.

These four were the same elders who had joined forces to attack Han Li in the Devilish Flame Valley during Han Li's previous visit to the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and all of them exchanged a glance with one another to find their own astonishment mirrored in each other's eyes.

At the same time, countless streaks of light emerged from all over the Heavenly Ghost Sect as virtually all of the elders and disciples flew out before landing on the nearby mountain peaks or plazas, then directed their attention upward with perplexed looks on their faces.

The giant golden ape paid no heed to the oncoming assailants, and not only did it not stop what it was doing, it let loose a thunderous roar instead as it rained a barrage of punches down upon the black light barrier.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, and the black light barrier trembled violently before warping significantly, then shattering into countless pieces.

The giant ape passed through the shattered section of the array before crashing down onto a mountain. At this point, the Body Integration Stage elders who had charged over from the Serene Offering Peak were already on the scene.

The elder charging at the forefront of the group let loose a loud roar as crimson mist surged out of his body, completely enveloping him in the blink of an eye, and he quickly transformed into a giant crimson-armored ghost that was around 500 to 600 feet tall.

The giant ghost was wielding a huge bloodstained ax, which it swung down toward the golden ape's head.

As the sharp edge of the giant ax descended through the air, a pair of crimson vortexes appeared out of thin air on either side of it, releasing bursts of powerful suction force that threatened to draw everything nearby into the path of the falling ax.

Close behind the giant crimson ax were several ghostly treasures of different forms and colors that were releasing clouds of black mist or rivers of blood, concealing the entire sky as they surged toward the giant golden ape with unstoppable might.

Gusts of Yin wind were howling ferociously through the sky like the shrieks and wails of countless ghosts, and the air temperature in the area was plummeting rapidly.

The giant golden ape gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and it didn't slow down in the slightest in its descent as it raised an arm up high before swatting an enormous palm at the river of blood and ghostly mist down below.

An indescribably powerful blast of energy immediately came crashing down like an impenetrable wall, descending with devastating force.

The crimson-armored giant was leading the way from the front, and the huge crimson ax crashed violently into the energy blast, only to be instantly shattered without being able to put up any resistance.

Immediately thereafter, half of the giant's body caved in as if it had crashed into a massive rock, following which its entire body exploded into a ball of crimson light.

As for the Yin clouds and blood mist behind the crimson giant, even before they came into contact with the energy blast, most of them were already dispelled by the tremendous force released by the energy blast. All of the treasures concealed within were instantly revealed, then exploded amid a string of loud bangs.

A string of agonized cries rang out as several figures threw up mouthfuls of blood as a result of suffering backlash from having their bonded treasures destroyed, then plummeted out of the sky.

Everyone else was greatly alarmed by this turn of events, and they hurriedly staged a retreat.

In the next instant, the giant golden ape came crashing heavily down onto a mountain like an asteroid, and the surrounding earth trembled violently as half of the mountain instantly collapsed, sending a huge cloud of dust and shrapnel flying up into the sky.

Cries of alarm rang out incessantly near the mountain as several hundred streaks of light rose up into the air before dispersing in all directions in a panicked frenzy.

Right at this moment, a nascent soul that was several inches tall suddenly emerged from the chaotic scene. The nascent soul was extremely similar in appearance to the elder who had transformed into the crimson-armored giant, and it wore a horrified expression as it turned to flee into the distance.

However, before it was able to get anywhere, a portly figure appeared silently beside it. It was none other than Daoist Closed Mountain.

He swung his palm down in an expressionless manner, and the nascent soul immediately felt the air constrict around it. Before it even had a chance to cry out, it had already exploded into a ball of crimson light.

On the Serene Offering Peak, the sect master of the Heavenly Ghost Sect was already astonished upon seeing the giant golden ape crushing all of the Body Integration Stage elders at once on its own, and his expression instantly darkened significantly at the sight of Daoist Closed Mountain's sudden arrival.

He forced himself to remain calm as he asked, "What is the meaning of this, Senior Closed Mountain?"

Daoist Closed Mountain cast his gaze toward the giant golden ape in the distance, then turned back before shaking his head as he replied, "Allow me to enlighten you, Sect Master Shi. Both of your sect's Grand Ascension Stage supreme elders have already fallen at the hands of Senior Han. It's over for the Heavenly Ghost Sect."

His voice wasn't very loud, but it was akin to a deafening thunderclap for the sect master and the Body Integration Stage elders of the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

In particular, the four elders who had teamed up against Han Li in the Devilish Flame Valley were completely distraught.

Earlier, they had already sensed a familiar aura from the giant golden ape, and now that they had received confirmation from Daoist Closed Mountain that the Giant Mountain Ape was indeed none other than Han Li, they knew that Daoist Closed Mountain was telling the truth about the demise of their sect's supreme elders.

Elder Lu took a deep breath, then communicated something to Sect Master Shi through voice transmission.

A conflicted look appeared on Sect Master Shi's face, but in the end, he gritted his teeth as he extended a respectful salute toward Daoist Closed Mountain, then said, "Senior Closed Mountain, if our Heavenly Ghost Sect is doomed to fall, then we would rather surrender and serve Senior Han from now on rather than throw away our lives for no good cause."

"Hehe, my Origin Realm Temple alone is sufficient to serve Senior Han and cater to his needs. As for all of you, I'm afraid you'll have to bear Senior Han's wrath," Daoist Closed Mountain chuckled as a cold look appeared on his face.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a sleeve through the air to release an antiquated peach wood sword, which rose up into the air before rapidly expanding, transforming into an enormous sword of light that was over 100 feet in length. Countless profound runes were surging over the surface of the sword, and it was also radiating dazzling golden light.

Immediately thereafter, the giant sword swept directly toward Sect Master Shi and his group.

The surrounding space shuddered as a long and pitch-black rift was sliced open.

Sect Master Shi and the others were greatly alarmed by this turn of events, and they all flew back in different directions while frantically taking defensive measures to protect themselves from the attack.

While this conversation was taking place, the giant golden ape leaped over to a huge mountain, then let loose a thunderous roar as it raised both of its fists up high before slamming them down onto the mountain with tremendous force.

Immediately thereafter, the entire mountain shuddered violently before collapsing in a gigantic heap, sending massive plumes of dust rising up into the sky.

Moments later, Han Li emerged from the dust before hovering in mid-air, having reverted back to his human form.

He quickly swept his gaze over the surrounding area to see countless streaks of light dispersing in all directions. Virtually all of the Heavenly Ghost Sect's elders and disciples were fleeing the scene.

Far away on the Serene Offering Peak, light was flashing incessantly amid strings of loud explosions, and it seemed that Daoist Closed Mountain was locked in a fierce battle against the sect master of the Heavenly Ghost Sect and several of its Body Integration Stage elders.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he quickly chanted an incantation, then abruptly opened his mouth to release a silver fireball, which instantly transformed into a silver fire raven that was around a foot in size.

He then made a hand seal before pointing a finger at the fire raven, which threw its head back and let loose a clear cry, following which its body began to swell rapidly at an incredible speed.

In the blink of an eye, it had swelled to the size of a small mountain, and it spread its wings before swooping down toward a dense cluster of buildings down below.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the giant fire raven crashed directly into the center of the cluster of buildings, then exploded into a sea of fire that engulfed everything.

Instead of lingering on the scene, Han Li suddenly turned and flew toward another mountain that was several hundred kilometers away.

He had already learned from Daoist Closed Mountain that the name of the mountain was the Serene Treasure Peak, and it was one of the most important places in the Heavenly Ghost Sect, home to its scripture library and pill and treasure storage facilities.

……

Several days later.

In a courtyard in the purple bamboo forest on the Holy Fire Peak.

Sima Jingming was holding a communication plate as he paced back and forth in the room with an elated look on his face.

Given the countless years he had spent cultivating and honing his mental state, he shouldn't have been displaying such clear emotions, but he was unable to suppress his joy.

All of a sudden, the scroll hanging on the wall in front of him suddenly lit up, and Patriarch Cold Flame emerged from within.

"Patriarch Cold Flame!" Sima Jingming hurriedly stopped in his tracks before extending a respectful bow.

"So? Has there been an outcome?" Patriarch Cold Flame asked in an indifferent voice.

"Yes, Patriarch, I have brilliant news to share with you!" Sima Jingming immediately replied with elation glowing in his eyes.

Patriarch Cold Flame's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and he didn't say anything in response.

Sima Jingming immediately realized that he had lost his composure, and he hurriedly apologized before continuing in a more self-restrained manner, "I was informed by Senior Han earlier today that the Heavenly Ghost Sect has already been wiped from the face of the Spirit Domain Realm, and he told me to take over some of the nations and sects previously controlled by the Heavenly Ghost Sect as compensation for the scriptures of our sect that he destroyed."

Patriarch Cold Flame's expression remained unchanged despite the good news. "He's only granting us some of the nations and sects previously under the Heavenly Ghost Sect's jurisdiction? What about the Origin Realm Temple?"

"Senior Han didn't mention anything about the Origin Realm Temple to me, but according to what I've heard, the Origin Realm Temple has been dealt a heavy blow, but it hasn't been completely eradicated like the Heavenly Ghost Sect," Sima Jingming replied.

Patriarch Cold Flame's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, and only after a long while did he heave a faint sigh. "I had thought that he would be able to inflict heavy damage onto both sects at the cost of his life, but I didn't think that he would be able to wipe out the Heavenly Ghost Sect and live to tell the tale. Looks like I've still managed to underestimate him."

"Patriarch Cold Flame, after all of this, our Cold Flame Sect will be sure to become the number one sect in the Spirit Domain Realm!" Sima Jingming said.

"Don't get complacent. Make sure to keep a close eye on the Origin Realm Temple. Also, I recall that Han Li has a younger sister who's staying in our sect. Make sure to look after her well and ensure her safety at all times. In addition to that, allocate extra resources to everyone in the sect who has any ties with him," Patriarch Cold Flame instructed.

Chapter 74: Bad News

In a cave abode on the Cloudrise Peak.

In the darkness of the night, the cold moonlight was spilling into a room through a window, shining upon a beautiful young woman in a palace dress with skin as fair as snow.

At this moment, she was seated on the edge of her bed in the room with a faint smile on her face, but there were tears flowing silently down her delicate cheeks.

"Father, Big Brothers, the Heavenly Ghost Sect has been eradicated by Senior... by Brother Han. The Prosperous Nation has also returned to the jurisdiction of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and our family has been avenged. Everyone is about to return to the Prosperous Nation and build a new life there. You can all rest easy in the heavens now," the young woman murmured as she wiped the tears from her face.

This young woman was naturally none other than Yu Menghan, and at this moment, she was crying tears of joy, but her heart was filled with countless emotions as the image of Han Li lingered stubbornly in her mind, refusing to be banished.

……

Close to half a month later, Han Li was standing on the Nine Palace Peak of the Origin Realm Temple, and he was in the process of inserting a final Starwash Stone into the ground.

A faint crack rang out, and the entire Star Gathering Platform instantly lit up.

A vast expanse of hazy silver light shone down from the heavens, enshrouding the entire platform like a fine mist.

In this instant, all of the star diagrams on the platform were illuminated.

Han Li raised his head to look up at the starry night sky, then slowly made his way up the staircase of the Star Gathering Platform with a calm expression.

……

In the Immortal Realm.

Next to a vast and nameless sea was a massive cliff that was over 10,000 feet tall, and it was hanging over the surface of the sea like the sharp beak of an eagle.

At the top of the cliff stood an enormous and majestic city.

The outer walls of the city were over 1,000 feet tall, and they were entirely constructed from some type of black rock material, allowing them to completely blend into the mountain.

The wall that was closest to the sea was riddled with marks and signs of erosion, which had been left behind by the countless waves that it had been struck by over the course of many years.

Inside the city were four straight and wide main roads, as well as many narrower roads that branched off these main roads, with countless shops and buildings interspersed throughout.

The city seemed to hold quite a large population, presenting a lively and bustling scene of activity.

In the southwestern area of the city was a narrow bluestone street that was complete with all types of shops, restaurants, and accommodation. The street was lined with different types of flags and bustling with activity, presenting a slightly noisy and rambunctious scene.

Beside a willow tree at the end of the bluestone street was a completely unremarkable-looking three-story building. It was an octagonal brick building with an azure flag hanging outside, bearing the word "medicine", and it could easily be missed on such a busy street.

Several employees were busy at work in the hall of the building, serving the customers who were there to purchase spirit medicines. Many of the customers were being led to the second floor by the shopkeeper.

At the top of the staircase on the second floor was an azure wooden door, sealing off the third floor.

There was a guest hall on the third floor, inside of which was a small rug. A purple tea table was placed on the rug, and the fragrance of sandalwood was wafting through the air from the tea table.

Two figures were seated on either side of the tea table across from one another, and each of them was holding a cup of tea.

One of the two was a handsome young man wearing a tight-fitting black robe with a set of defined facial features. It was none other than Fang Pan.

The other person was a slightly portly middle-aged man who appeared to be around 40 to 0 years of age. He was wearing a silken robe that was embroidered with golden threads, giving him the appearance of a wealthy merchant, and there was a benevolent smile on his face.

Fang Pan examined the room around him to find that there was a faint golden restriction light barrier enshrouding the surrounding area, and he remarked, "As the saying goes, the best place to hide something is in plain sight. It's an interesting idea for your Ubiquitous Pavilion to set up its branches in these cities inhabited by ordinary people."

"Our Ubiquitous Pavilion can't compare with all of those powerful sects out there. All we do is pass on information, so we naturally can't establish our branches in prestigious locations," the middle-aged man chuckled in response.

"You sent me a message earlier, telling me that you have news on that man. Is that true?" Fang Pan asked, quickly changing the subject.

"Of course. We asked you to come here for this sole purpose," the middle-aged man replied with a smile.

Fang Pan immediately flipped a hand over upon hearing this, producing a bulging azure storage bag that he placed onto the table.

The middle-aged man picked up the storage bag before briefly inspecting its contents with his spiritual sense, and the smile on his face grew even more pronounced as he revealed, "The man you are looking for is currently in the Spirit Domain Realm."

He swept a hand through the air as he spoke, and a round purplish-golden bowl that was filled with clear water appeared on the tea table.

He then reached out with a finger before gently tapping the edge of the bowl, and the water within the bowl instantly rippled as a burst of azure light flashed past.

Immediately thereafter, an image depicting a fierce battle between a massive ape and a golden giant appeared in the water.

Fang Pan's expression stiffened slightly at the sight of the mountainous golden ape, and a hint of ferocious killing intent appeared in his eyes.

The middle-aged man's expression remained completely unchanged upon seeing this, still maintaining a warm smile.

Moments later, he gently brushed a hand over the purplish-golden bowl, and the light within the bowl instantly faded, as did the image it was displaying.

"At the moment, that man is in a sect in the Spirit Domain Realm by the name of the Origin Realm Temple, and he most likely won't be leaving there anytime soon," the middle-aged man replied.

"Thank you for your efforts," Fang Pan replied in a rather absentminded manner, already pondering how he was going to travel to the Spirit Domain Realm.

"There's no need to thank me, I was simply providing a paid service. If you require my services at any later point, don't forget to visit again," the middle-aged man replied as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Right as Fang Pan was about to say something else, a burst of golden light suddenly appeared on his waist, and it was pulsing insistently.

The middle-aged man immediately rose to his feet upon seeing this, then said in a respectful voice, "The restrictions that we've set up here are definitely reliable, so you can take a rest here if you like. I'll leave you to yourself now."

He then extended a parting salute before exiting the room.

Following the middle-aged man's departure, Fang Pan brushed a hand over his waist, and an extremely beautiful golden badge appeared in his grasp.

He looked at the golden light flashing from the badge, and after a moment of hesitation, he closed his eyes before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

In the next instant, he found himself standing in a resplendent hall. There were barely any furnishings in the hall, but its walls were riddled with intricate engravings depicting all types of flora and fauna.

Directly in front of the hall stood a woman in a palace dress with a thin white veil over her face, and as soon as she caught sight of Fang Pan, she immediately said, "Recently, a tide of Veil Beasts of extremely massive proportions has erupted in the Driftcloud Realm. Hundreds of cities in the realm have already been slaughtered, and dozens of sects have been destroyed. You have been ordered to go to the Driftcloud Realm to take care of this matter."

Fang Pan's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and after a brief hesitation, he replied, "Esteemed Immortal Envoy, it's going to take at least several years to completely quell such a massive Veil Beast tide. I still have some urgent matters that I need to attend to right away. Would it be possible to have someone else carry out this mission instead?"

"Everyone else is currently busy with other missions. You are the only one who hasn't accepted a new mission after completing your previous one," the woman in white replied with a shake of her head.

"But..."

Fang Pan still wanted to say something, but he was immediately cut off by the woman. "Fang Pan, have you forgotten your duties and the rules of the Immortal Palace?"

"I wouldn't dare. I accept this mission," Fang Pan replied in a resigned manner despite his extreme reluctance to do so.

After withdrawing his spiritual sense from the badge, a dark look appeared on his face as he spat through gritted teeth, "Lucky bastard! Looks like you'll get to live a few more years."

……

Three years later, at the Origin Realm Temple.

It was nighttime, but the Nine Palace Peak was illuminated by such radiant silver light that it was as bright as day.

The entire Star Gathering Platform was enshrouded within seven extraordinarily thick pillars of silver light, and a massive tornado formed by starpower was raging around the pillars of light, forming what appeared to be an impregnable fortress.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed at the center of the platform, and his entire body seemed to have been filled with starlight, making him so bright that appeared to almost be transparent.

Six dazzling specks of blue light were glowing on his chest and abdomen, giving off scintillating radiance. The seventh speck of blue light at the tip of his spine was still a little hazy, but it was also clearly visible.

Right at this moment, Han Li's eyelashes fluttered slightly, and his eyes suddenly sprang open as he withdrew his hand seal. The seven pillars of light around the Star Gathering Platform instantly dimmed before gradually fading away.

Seven streaks of black light then descended from the sky, reverting back into seven Starmoon Mirrors before falling into Han Li's grasp.

He had detonated the original set of mirrors in order to escape from the domain that he had been trapped in, but he was able to refine a new set of seven Starmoon Mirrors after acquiring a large quantity of Yin Dawn Stones from the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he murmured to himself, "I'm finally about to manifest my seventh profound aperture."

In reality, he didn't have much of a concept of Profound Immortals in the past. However, his battle against the golden giant three years ago and the insights that he had gleaned from cultivating the Big Dipper Origin Arts had given him a clearer understanding of the concept.

He was confident that once he attained a True Extreme Body, he wouldn't have to use his Holy Nirvana Physique against the likes of the golden giant. Instead, he would be able to defeat an opponent of that caliber with the power of his physical body alone.

With that in mind, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he flipped a hand over to produce a walnut-sized yellow bean.

It was the exact same bean that he had pulled out of the golden giant's chest.

Ever since learning about the reward being offered for his capture in the Immortal Realm, he had been busy at work, cultivating to enhance his own powers, so he had never had the chance to examine the bean closely.

He held the bean in the palm of his hand, and after some careful examination, he discovered that there was nothing remarkable about it aside from the fact that it was several times larger than the soybean.

However, as he injected his spiritual sense into the bean, he was immediately stunned by what he felt.

The bean was filled with a burst of rich azure light, and if Han Li didn't know any better, he would think that he had been teleported into a vast forest that was filled with stunning exuberance and vitality.

"It's extraordinary that a bean of this size could hold such enormous life energy," Han Li couldn't help but praise after opening his eyes.

He had only seen this bean be used to give rise to the golden giant, but he had no idea how to use it. However, looking at the vitality imbued within the bean, perhaps it was going to come in very useful in the future.

After a moment of contemplation, he stowed the bean away with a flick of his wrist, then rose to his feet before making his way down the stone staircase on the side of the Star Gathering Platform.

Right at this moment, a large streak of light suddenly appeared in the night sky, then rapidly approached Han Li before landing beside him.

Daoist Closed Mountain was revealed from the streak of light with an urgent look on his face, and he hurriedly extended a respectful salute toward Han Li, then said, "Senior Han, I have bad news!"

Chapter 75: Inquiry

"What happened?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

"I just received news from Fellow Daoist Sima of the Cold Flame Sect that... that Young Mistress Liu was abducted," Daoist Closed Mountain stuttered.

"Tell me what happened," Han Li urged as his expression darkened slightly.

Daoist Closed Mountain hurriedly explained, "Last night, a woman in white suddenly broke through the restrictions around the Spirit Flame Mountain Range, then went straight to the Cloudrise Peak before taking Young Mistress Liu away."

"And the Cold Flame Sect just allowed it to happen without doing anything?" Han Li asked.

"Fellow Daoist Sima claims that he tried to step in, but his attacks were dispelled by the woman with ease, and all it took was a casual sweep of her sleeve to send him flying, so he was completely powerless to stop her. However, the woman seemed to have no intention of harming anyone. She said that she belonged to the same race as Young Mistress Liu, then took her away," Daoist Closed Mountain replied as he extended a respectful bow.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this. "You're telling me that she sent Sima Jingming flying with just a sweep of her sleeve?"

"That's what I was told by Fellow Daoist Sima. Would you like me to send out some disciples of our Origin Realm Temple to search for Young Mistress Liu? When it comes to searching for people, our Origin Realm Temple is..."

Before Daoist Closed Mountain had a chance to finish, Han Li cut him off as he asked, "Do you know of anyone in this realm capable of sending a Grand Ascension cultivator flying with just a sweep of their hand?"

"N... No," Daoist Closed Mountain replied in an uneasy voice.

"Alright, you can go now," Han Li replied.

Daoist Closed Mountain extended another respectful bow, then departed from the Star Gathering Platform.

Han Li looked on as Daoist Closed Mountain flew away into the distance, then suddenly swept a hand through the air after a brief silence to conjure up a silver light barrier that enshrouded the entire Star Gathering Platform.

……

The next morning.

Daoist Closed Mountain's portly figure appeared in front of the Nine Palace Peak once again, and he extended a respectful bow toward the Star Gathering Platform as he declared, "Junior Closed Mountain pays his respects to Senior Han."

During the past three years, he showed up at this time every single day without fail to report all of the noteworthy pieces of news that had arisen in the Spirit Domain Realm to Han Li. Occasionally, he would also act as a messenger bird between Han Li and the Cold Flame Sect, and his diligence to the task was truly commendable.

Most of the time, Han Li was cultivating in seclusion, in which case Daoist Closed Mountain would respectfully announce his arrival, then wait patiently for around two hours before departing after respectfully taking his leave. He displayed no agitation or impatience throughout this entire process, and his attitude was impeccable.

As a result, during the past three years, all of the disciples of the Origin Realm Temple gradually came to realize that their Grand Ascension Stage supreme elder, who was normally extremely rarely seen, had become a relatively common sight in the temple. Even though they could only see him from afar, this was already enough to fill many of the disciples with giddy excitement.

Of course, all of the Body Integration and some of the Spatial Tempering Stage elders of the temple were naturally aware of the circumstances involved. However, they all chose to refrain from speaking on the matter, as if there were some type of unspoken agreement between them.

Daoist Closed Mountain stood in mid-air around 1,000 feet away from the Nine Palace Peak with a respectful look on his face, but he was feeling a little perplexed as he looked at the silver light barrier around the Star Gathering Platform.

Normally, during Han Li's cultivation, the entire surrounding area would be teeming with turbulent starpower, but there was no sign of that at all on this day.

Despite his befuddlement, he didn't dare to intrude. Perhaps Han Li was undergoing some other type of cultivation. With that in mind, he continued to wait obediently off to the side, then took his leave once again two hours later.

Time passed by one day after another, and he still made his routine daily visits, but there still seemed to be nothing happening on the Star Gathering Platform.

Close to three months flew by in the blink of an eye, and Daoist Closed Mountain was gradually running out of patience.

On this day, he waited for half a day, but there was still no change whatsoever on the Star Gathering Platform.

He took a deep breath, then declared, "Senior Han, I've found some more leads pertaining to Young Mistress Liu's abduction. Would you happen to have some time to speak to me?"

There was no response at all.

"Senior Han!" Daoist Closed Mountain called out once again, but yet again, there was no response.

"Could it be..." His expression changed slightly as a thought occurred to him, and he swept a hand through the air, releasing a burst of golden light that fell upon the silver light barrier.

The silver light barrier was instantly shattered, revealing a completely deserted Star Gathering Platform.

However, there was a white jade slip sitting on the center of the platform.

Daoist Closed Mountain picked up the jade slip before injecting his spiritual sense into it, following which an excited look appeared on his face, and his flabby rolls began to tremble with elation.

The jade slip contained the method to remove the restriction that Han Li had placed in his body.

"Thank you, Senior Han!"

He withdrew his gaze before turning toward the distant sky, and he didn't know if Han Li could hear him, but he still loudly expressed his gratitude.

……

In the Spirit Flame Mountain Range.

Inside a certain hall, Sima Jingming was holding a discussion with the sect master and several Body Integration Stage elders of the sect. Following their discussion, everyone departed, leaving only Sima Jingming remaining in the hall.

He let out a long breath, and he was looking rather weary.

In the blink of an eye, the former number one sect of the Spirit Domain Realm, the Heavenly Ghost Sect, had been erased from existence, and all of the other major powers had been constantly competing with one another for the former territory of the Heavenly Ghost Sect during the past few years. As the only one of the former three top sects to have emerged completely unscathed from the incident, the Cold Flame Sect had been particularly busy.

As a result, he was constantly having to attend to different duties and matters and had no time for cultivation.

For a very long time, he had been focused solely on secluded cultivation and very rarely addressed the matters of the sect, so this was a very jarring change for him.

Of course, another reason why he was doing this was because of the current state of the Origin Realm Temple. He had thought that the Origin Realm Temple had been dealt a heavy blow, but not only was that not the case, it had also benefited immensely from the fall of the Heavenly Ghost Sect.

As for why this was the case, he was naturally aware of the underlying reasons, but he didn't dare to say anything.

However, Patriarch Cold Flame had been extremely pleased with the expansion of the Cold Flame Sect, and had already sent down several rewards.

With these rewards, Sima Jingming was confident that he would be able to take another stride in his cultivation once everything settled down and he had a chance to go into seclusion.

At this rate, the prospect of ascending into the Immortal Realm no longer seemed to be completely out of reach.

With that in mind, Sima Jingming was feeling very pleased, and he rose to his feet, yet right as he was about to depart from the hall, a familiar voice suddenly rang out.

"Fellow Daoist Sima."

Sima Jingming's expression changed slightly upon hearing this voice, and in the next instant, Han Li appeared in the hall amid a flash of azure light.

In one of his hands, which was concealed up his sleeve, he was holding a purple talisman that was flashing with silver light.

Sima Jingming's pupils contracted slightly at the sight of Han Li, and he instantly put on a warm smile as he cupped his fist in a salute. "Long time no see, Senior Han. You've become even more powerful since we last met several years ago! Congratulations!"

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Sima," Han Li replied in a rather aloof voice.

"Please take a seat, Senior Han."

Sima Jingming's heart jolted slightly at the sight of Han Li's cold demeanor, and he hurriedly invited Han Li to take a seat before sitting down beside him.

"I came here today to inquire about Sister Liu. Is it true that she was abducted from the Cold Flame Sect?" Han Li immediately asked after taking a seat.

"It's true. I was unable to protect her, but her abductor was someone truly formidable, and..." Sima Jingming replied in an uneasy manner.

Han Li cut him off in an expressionless manner as he asked, "Do you have any leads on her abductor, Fellow Daoist Sima? Did she say anything to you that day?"

"The person who abducted Liu Le'er was a young woman in white, and she claimed to be from the same race as her. She asked me to thank you for looking after Le'er. I'm certain that I've never seen this woman before, and since the incident, I've sent out many of our sect's disciples to investigate her, but to no avail. Hence, I've developed a theory about her origins..." Sima Jingming's voice trailed off at the end, and a slightly hesitant look appeared on his face.

"Go on," Han Li prompted as he raised an eyebrow.

"My theory is that she isn't from the Spirit Domain Realm. She was so powerful that I was unable to withstand even a single attack from her, which leads me to believe that she's a True Immortal from the Immortal Realm."

Han Li had already guessed this to be the case, so he wasn't surprised to hear this theory being proposed by Sima Jingming. Instead, his brows furrowed slightly in contemplation.

According to his knowledge, the Cloud Fox Race that Liu Le'er belonged to was a branch of the Fox Race that had fallen well into decline. Otherwise, they wouldn't have been wiped out by the Blood Sword Sect. With that in mind, he couldn't help but wonder how such a race had managed to produce a True Immortal.

Perhaps an ancestor of the race had ascended to the Immortal Realm many years ago and just so happened to have returned to the Spirit Domain Realm recently, or perhaps Liu Le'er had been keeping some secrets from him...

"You've already done everything in your power, so I can't blame you for this. Fortunately, Le'er seems to have been taken by one of her brethren, so she shouldn't be in any danger," Han Li sighed.

Sima Jingming heaved an internal sigh of relief upon hearing this, and only then did he realize that his back was already drenched in cold sweat.

"By the way, I came here because there was another thing that I wanted you to enlighten me on, Fellow Daoist Sima," Han Li suddenly continued after a brief silence.

"I wouldn't dare to claim to be able to enlighten you, Senior Han! Please, ask me anything, and I'll tell you everything that I know," Sima Jingming hurriedly replied.

"Has Fellow Daoist Cold Flame ever spoken to you about his ascension to the Immortal Realm? Also, is there anything I have to be mindful of if I wish to attempt an ascension into the Immortal Realm from the Spirit Domain Realm?" Han Li asked.

Sima Jingming faltered slightly upon hearing this, and he took a deep breath, then replied in a respectful manner, "Senior Han, seeing as you're pursuing the path of body cultivation, once you attain a True Extreme Body, your physical body will automatically be rejected by the power of this realm. If you wish to ascend, then you'll have to break through the interrealm barrier with your physical strength."

"I see," Han Li replied with an enlightened expression.

It was no wonder that the closer he came to fully mastering the Big Dipper Origin Arts, the more he felt suppressed by some type of inexplicable force, to the point that even his flight was slightly hampered.

"The Spirit Domain Realm is very close to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, so ascending to the Immortal Realm from here will take you to a random Ascension Platform in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

“Due to how sparse spiritual power in the lower realms is compared to in the Immortal Realm, all those who can successfully ascend possess exceptional aptitude and resolute wills, so they'll be generally held in very high regard in the Immortal Realm," Sima Jingming replied, revealing everything that he knew.

Han Li's expression remained completely unchanged, but he was quickly processing the information that he had just been given.

The Immortal Realm's attitude toward ascended immortals had always been the same, regardless of whether it was in the Spirit Domain Realm or back in the Spirit Realm. It was clear that he was currently being targeted by a certain power or person in the Immortal Realm, and the last thing that he wanted was to attract attention to himself.

Chapter 76: Legend

After a period of silence, a thought suddenly occurred to Sima Jingming, and he added, "By the way, aside from the Ascension Platforms I just mentioned, there's another type of smuggling method in our Spirit Domain Realm that can allow one to ascend to the Immortal Realm in secret and avoid the Ascension Platforms altogether."

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, but he feigned a nonchalant expression as he prompted, "Oh? Tell me about that."

"The concept of this method is quite simple. All that needs to be done is to find a brittle spatial node between the Spirit Domain Realm and the Immortal Realm, then forcibly break through it using spatial-attribute arrays or some other method, thereby taking one into the space between the two realms, which they can then travel through to reach the Immortal Realm," Sima Jingming explained.

"That sounds like it would be a lot more difficult to accomplish than the legitimate method of ascension," Han Li said.

This was the exact same method that he had employed to ascend from the Human Realm to the Spirit Realm.

It was likely the case that this type of method could only be used in realms like the Spirit Domain Realm, which were very close to the Immortal Realm.

"Indeed, Senior Han. This is an extremely risky method. The space between realms is extremely perilous, and even if one manages to complete the journey, there's a very good chance that they'll arrive in a very dangerous location in the Immortal Realm. After all, generally speaking, most places in the Immortal Realm where space is quite brittle are not good places to be.

“In addition to that, using this method of ascension will prevent one from being able to enjoy the various benefits of ascending through legitimate avenues, such as getting to refine one's physical body in an immortal pond or receiving an immortal badge for identification purposes. As a result, it's very likely that one would find themselves in some trouble even if they manage to get to the Immortal Realm," Sima Jingming explained.

Han Li nodded in response, and his expression remained unchanged, but he was feeling quite excited.

Ascending to the Immortal Realm had always been quite a troublesome predicament in his mind, but he had finally found a solution.

As for the dangers that Sima Jingming spoke of, with his current powers, those dangers most likely weren't going to be a concern as long as he was sufficiently prepared, so he wasn't particularly concerned.

"Thank you, Fellow Daoist Sima," Han Li said with a grateful nod.

"Please don't thank me, Senior Han. You've singlehanded elevated our sect to unprecedented heights. Patriarch Cold Flame told me to offer you his sincerest gratitude on his behalf," Sima Jingming replied in an earnest voice.

"Is that so? I didn't think that Fellow Daoist Cold Flame would still remember me," Han Li said as a meaningful look appeared on his face.

Sima Jingming's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, and he hurriedly said, "Surely you jest, Senior Han. Patriarch..."

"I'll be taking my leave now, Fellow Daoist Sima." Before he had a chance to finish, Han Li abruptly cut him off, then flew out of the hall as a streak of azure light.

Sima Jingming looked on as the streak of azure light vanished into the distant sky, and he couldn't help but heave a long sigh of relief.

……

Following Han Li's departure from the Cold Flame Sect, he made no further appearances in the Spirit Domain Realm, and it was as if he had disappeared from the face of the realm.

However, some exaggerated accounts of his feats gradually began to spread throughout the realm, painting him into an almighty yet enigmatic legend.

The cultivation world of the Spirit Domain Realm had already reached a certain equilibrium, but that equilibrium had been completely shattered in just a few years due to his arrival.

Some said that he was an almighty figure who was always in seclusion and isolated himself from the rest of the realm, while others proclaimed that he was actually a descended immortal. There were even some who speculated that he was a descendant of a true spirit who had lived for countless years.

Everyone's opinion of him also varied drastically over a wide spectrum. Some saw him as a bloodthirsty fiend who killed without discrimination, while others regarded him as a saint who had eradicated the largest menace in the realm in the form of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, thereby restoring peace to the Spirit Domain Realm.

In any case, there were all types of things being said about him.

The chaos that arose in the wake of the fall of the Heavenly Ghost Sect lasted several centuries. After countless battles between all of the major sects and powers and the demise of countless cultivators, a new landscape began to arise before gradually reaching stability, but of course, that was a story for another time.

On a bright and sunny day several months after the disappearance of Liu Le'er.

There was a certain vast sea located in the northern region of the Spirit Domain Realm. Dense black mist that completely concealed the heavens would often rise up from the sea, and as a result, it was named the Black Mist Sea.

The spiritual power in this area of the sea was quite abundant, so there were many sea beasts dwelling here. In addition to that, there were also several types of precious spirit ingredients that could only be found here and nowhere else, so the area was rife with cultivators who were on adventures to seek out treasures and slay sea beasts.

Near a deserted island deep in the Black Mist Sea, a burst of rumbling rang out, sweeping up turbulent waves on the surface of the sea within a radius of several dozen kilometers. The waves rose up to several dozen feet in height before sweeping in all directions, and even the dense black mist above the sea began to revolve under the influence of some type of invisible force, forming a gigantic vortex.

At the center of the vortex was a green-robed young woman, a black-robed elderly man, and a middle-aged daoist priest, all of whom were locked in a fierce battle against a manatee-like sea beast.

All three of them were at the early-Deity Transformation Stage, and even though they were all using different cultivation arts, it was clear from their seamless teamwork that this wasn't their first time working together.

Their treasures were connected together to form a large circle that surrounded the sea beast, delivering one wave of ferocious attacks after another.

The sea beast was entirely blue in color with two black stripes on its back, extending all the way from its forehead to the tip of its tail, presenting a rather peculiar sight to behold.

The sea beast was roaring incessantly as blue light flashed over its body, and a series of balls of blue lightning appeared around it to ward off the oncoming barrages of attacks. At the same time, it was releasing a series of thick pillars of blue light out of its mouth to retaliate against its three assailants.

Its cultivation base was at the mid-Deity Transformation Stage, so it was slightly superior to its three assailants in that regard, but its offensive repertoire was very limited, and it was gradually being suppressed by the trio of cultivators.

The battle raged on for almost another hour before the protective spiritual light around the sea beast was finally broken, and a large hole was punched into its head by a burst of rapidly revolving black swordlight that had been unleashed by the black-robed elderly man.

The sea beast let loose an agonized wail, then thrashed violently a few times before quickly falling still.

"Your Soul Devouring Heart Drilling Sword is still as formidable as ever, Fellow Daoist Qin. Adult Black-striped Blue Manatees are renowned for their defensive prowess, yet even it couldn't withstand a single blow from your sword," the middle-aged daoist priest praised.

"You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist Dead Wood."

A hint of pride flashed through the black-robed elderly man's eyes as he drew the burst of black swordlight back to himself, revealing it to be a strange-looking longsword that resembled a pair of vipers intertwined together. The sword was giving off a cold black light, and the elderly man carefully stowed it away, clearly holding it in very high regard.

He had spent the majority of his life's savings to craft this treasure, and its powers were comparable to the average spirit treasure. In addition to that, it possessed certain armor-piercing properties that made it the perfect weapon against defensively adept sea beasts.

The three of them quickly dissected the carcass of the sea beast, and all of them received appreciable returns.

"If you ask me, even if the three of us encounter a late-Deity Transformation Stage sea beast, we should be able to at least ensure a safe retreat even if we can't defeat it, so how about we advance a little further?" the green-robed young woman suggested as she cast her gaze toward the sea up ahead.

The middle-aged daoist priest's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he seemed to also be tempted by this proposal.

"That would be a terrible idea. The two of you have only recently arrived in the Black Mist Sea, so allow me to enlighten you. Not far ahead of this point is the extremely dreaded core region of the Black Mist Sea. There are many formidable sea beasts residing in that area, including even Spatial Tempering and Body Integration Stage sea beasts!

“In fact, there are even stories claiming that a Grand Ascension Stage Five-clawed Black Dragon is residing in the deepest part of the core region. Those sea beasts generally only stay in the core region and very rarely venture out of it, but no one dares to enter the core region unless they're at least at the Body Integration Stage.

“Truth be told, we've already taken a huge risk by pursuing that Black-striped Blue Manatee all the way to this point. If you ask me, the best course of action would be to retreat as quickly as possible," the black-robed elderly man hurriedly said with a grim expression.

"A Grand Ascension Stage sea beast? How is that possible?" The middle-aged daoist priest was astonished to hear this.

An incredulous look had also appeared on the green-robed young woman's face.

"That's only a legend. Apparently, that Five-clawed Black Dragon has already been residing here for over 100,000 years, and the last time it appeared was several thousand years ago. At the time, it was already at the peak of the Body Integration Stage.

“Perhaps it's already reached the end of its lifespan since then, but even so, this is an extremely dangerous place, and it would be wise to leave this area as soon as possible," the black-robed elderly man said in a slightly urgent voice.

The middle-aged daoist priest and the green-robed young woman hurriedly nodded in response, yet right as they were about to depart, an earth-shattering boom suddenly rang out up ahead.

The sound was coming from somewhere extremely far away, but it was still able to reach them with startling clarity, and it was accompanied by a burst of violent tremors that ran through the entire area.

The expressions of the trio changed slightly upon hearing this, yet before they had a chance to do anything, another burst of violent rumbling rang out up ahead.

At the same time, a burst of enormous yet chaotic spiritual pressure came sweeping violently toward them, sending gusts of incredibly ferocious wind blowing their way.

The trio was extremely alarmed, and they immediately turned to flee, but it was already too late. Before they were able to get away from the area, they were swept up by the gusts of fierce wind and were blown around unsteadily like a trio of leaves in a stiff gale.

Thankfully, the gusts of wind began to wane after traveling for a short distance, and the three of them hurriedly stabilized themselves, but by then, their faces were already deathly pale with fear.

Right at this moment, another earth-shattering boom rang out, and the surface of the sea dozens of kilometers up ahead abruptly erupted.

A gargantuan black figure flew out from within, and after flying for some distance, it crashed down heavily onto that deserted island not far away from the trio of cultivators. The entire island trembled violently, and the shockwaves released by the impact swept up a series of massive waves in the surrounding sea.

The black figure was an enormous black wyrm that was around 2,000 to 3,000 feet in length. Its entire body was covered in gleaming, inky-black scales, and there were a pair of translucent, coral-like long horns on its head.

The gigantic wyrm had two pairs of massive claws, and every single claw had five toes that resembled giant black swords that were giving off a cold, menacing light.

An indescribably enormous aura was emanating from the black wyrm's body, and at this point, the trio of cultivators was already on the verge of passing out from fear.

Among them, the black-robed elderly man was particularly petrified. He wasn't a vagrant cultivator. Instead, he was an inner court disciple of a large sect, which was overseen by a Body Integration Stage patriarch.

However, the aura being released by this black wyrm was far beyond that of the Body Integration Stage patriarch of his sect!

Could it be that the legends are all true stories?

An astonishing thought occurred to the elderly man as his heart jolted violently.

The gargantuan black wyrm flipped itself over violently, causing the island to tremble and quake once again.

The trio of cultivators were extremely alarmed, and they hurriedly retreated to over 1,000 feet away. Upon refocusing their gaze on the black wyrm, they discovered that there was a massive hole on its chest, out of which blood was pouring incessantly, quickly staining most of the island red.

All of a sudden, an azure humanoid figure flew out of the sea. The figure was so fast that it was impossible to track with the naked eye, and it flew past the black wyrm like a dazzling harbinger of death.

The black wyrm's entire body stiffened, following which its gigantic head suddenly flew up into the sky, accompanied by an incredibly thick fountain of blood. It was as if a storm of blood were falling upon the entire island, and a nauseating odor was permeating through the air.

The enormous wyrm collapsed to the ground with a violent thump, then spasmed a few times before falling still.

Right at this moment, a streak of black light flew out of the giant wyrm's head. Inside the streak of black light was a miniature black wyrm that was only several inches in size, and it immediately tried to flee into the distance in a panicked manner.

However, the azure figure was already prepared, and he appeared in front of the miniature black wyrm in a flash, then opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light to envelop it before casually stuffing it into a jade vial.

The trio of cultivators was completely rooted to the spot upon seeing this, with their jaws dropping straight onto the ocean floor down below.

At this point, the azure figure had already been revealed to be an azure-robed young man who appeared to be around 25 to 26 years of age, with a set of unremarkable facial features and a slightly dark complexion.

Chapter 77: Two Powerful Treasures

The azure-robed young man completely ignored the trio as he calmly made his way over to the massive head of the black wyrm, then reached out with one hand to make a grabbing motion.

A certain part of the wyrm's head instantly exploded, following which a translucent black core flew out from within. The object was riddled with a series of profound black patterns, and it was none other than the black wyrm's demon core.

The young man examined the demon core momentarily in an expressionless manner, then stowed it away.

After that, he raised a hand before making a downward chopping motion, and the four giant claws of the black wyrm were all severed amid a string of loud cracks.

The young man stowed the claws away, then directed his gaze toward the neck of the giant wyrm.

His gaze settled on a light silver scale that was close to 10 feet in size, which was completely different in appearance from all of the black scales around it. There were also several light silver bone spikes around the scale that were giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations.

The scale and the bone spikes were also riddled with patterns that were similar to the ones on the demon core.

The young man carefully extracted the silver scale and the bone spikes, then took several more parts of the black wyrm's body, and only then did he cast his gaze toward the nearby trio of cultivators.

Even though there was no animosity in his eyes, the trio still immediately tensed up, at a complete loss for what to do as they sweated profusely.

Thankfully for them, the azure-robed young man quickly withdrew his gaze before flying away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

Only after he had completely disappeared into the distance did the trio dare to heave a collective sigh of relief.

"Could that wyrm have been the Five-clawed Black Dragon that we were just talking about?" the middle-aged daoist priest asked as he looked down at the carcass of the black wyrm.

The black-robed elderly man took a moment to compose himself, then nodded in response. "It looks like it. Judging from what we just saw, there's a very good chance that this wyrm had already reached the Grand Ascension Stage!"

Both the green-robed young woman and the middle-aged daoist priest drew a sharp breath upon hearing this.

The green-robed young woman still had some lingering fear in her heart, and she mused with a perplexed expression, "Not only was that senior able to slay that wyrm without using any treasures, it didn't seem to have taken him much effort at all.

“Could it be that he was also a Grand Ascension cultivator? I've seen portraits of both Senior Sima of the Cold Flame Sect and Senior Closed Mountain of the Origin Realm Temple, but he didn't seem to be either of them."

"Could it be that that was one of them in disguise?" the middle-aged daoist priest speculated.

"I don't think so. Judging from the wounds sustained by the black wyrm, it seems that that senior from just now is a pure body cultivator, so I don't think he's one of those two seniors," the black-robed elderly man said with a shake of his head.

"If it's not those two, then are there other Grand Ascension Stage beings in the Spirit Domain Realm?" the green-robed young woman asked as her brows furrowed slightly.

"There's one more... Have you forgotten that Senior Han Li, who destroyed the Heavenly Ghost Sect in one night? He was precisely a body cultivator!" the black-robed elderly man exclaimed.

The green-robed young woman's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this. "Ah, now that you mention it, that Senior Han was purported to have an extremely youthful appearance. Was that really him just now?"

"Apparently, Senior Han is a descended immortal from the Immortal Realm, so he's an actual immortal!" The middle-aged daoist priest was also getting quite excited.

While the three of them were conversing with one another, their attention quickly turned to the carcass of the Five-clawed Black Dragon, and the excitement in their eyes only became more pronounced.

Han Li had abandoned the carcass, but for a trio of Deity Transformation cultivators like them, if they could take back even a small piece of the wyrm's flesh, that would be enough to create a massive stir.

After all, this was the flesh of a Grand Ascension Stage demon beast!

……

The Heavenly Crystal Sect was a sect that had a history of 200,000 to 300,000 years. It couldn't compare with the superpower sects like the Cold Flame Sect and the Origin Realm Temple, but it had several Body Integration cultivators among its ranks, and it was certainly not to be looked down on.

However, the sect had always kept a low profile, so it wasn't very renowned in the Spirit Domain Realm.

At this moment, a burst of blinding golden light was erupting on a drill ground in the sect, and it was accompanied by a thunderous boom.

A silver-robed elderly man was sent flying like a ragdoll before crashing into the restriction around the drill ground, upon which he threw up a mouthful of blood before tumbling to the ground.

A light golden bowl also clattered onto the ground not far away from him, and the spiritual light radiating from its surface had dimmed significantly.

Standing in mid-air across from the elderly man was an azure-robed cultivator whose face was concealed behind a film of azure light, and he was in the process of slowly retracting his extended right hand.

There were three other Body Integration cultivators gathered around the drill ground, and they were stunned by what they saw. They hurriedly withdrew the restriction around the drill ground, then rushed over to the silver-robed elderly man's side before turning to the azure-robed cultivator with wary expressions.

"Are you alright, Supreme Elder?"

"I'm fine. That fellow daoist held back at the last moment," the silver-robed elderly man replied as he pulled out a yellow pill before taking it, and only then did his complexion gradually begin to improve.

The other three Body Integration cultivators were stunned to hear this.

"Your powers are truly extraordinary, Fellow Daoist. I am ashamed to concede that I'm unable to take even a single attack from you," the silver-robed elderly man said with a wry smile as he cupped his fist in a salute toward the azure-robed cultivator.

"If you concede, then according to our agreement, it's time for you to hand over your Exquisite Eight Treasures Jade," the azure-robed cultivator said in an indifferent voice, and he sounded quite young.

The silver-robed elderly man turned to a burly man next to him with a resigned expression before issuing an instruction, and despite his reluctance, the burly man still did as he was told.

Shortly thereafter, he returned with a white jade box that was several feet long and around half a foot wide in his hands, then handed it over to the silver-robed elderly man.

The elderly man stroked the jade box with a wistful expression, then tossed it toward the azure-robed cultivator, where it hovered in front of him, enveloped within a ball of golden light.

The azure-robed cultivator caught the jade box, then tapped it with a fingertip that was glowing with azure light.

A faint crack rang out, and the white jade box slowly opened on its own, revealing several pieces of white jade of different sizes. They appeared to be quite unremarkable, but there was eight-colored spiritual light surging incessantly over their surfaces, presenting quite a mesmerizing sight to behold.

The azure-robed cultivator nodded with a pleased expression, then placed the lid back onto the box before stowing it away.

"It's taken us tens of thousands of years to accumulate these pieces of premium Exquisite Eight Treasures Jade from our sect's jade mines. I hope you can put them to good use," the silver-robed elderly man sighed.

"Rest assured, I won't let these precious treasures go to waste," the azure-robed cultivator promised, then swept a hand through the air to send a burst of white light containing a storage bracelet flying over to the silver-robed elderly man.

"I won't take these pieces of jade for free. The items in that storage bracelet should be sufficient compensation," the azure-robed cultivator said in an indifferent voice, then flew away as a streak of azure light, disappearing into the distant sky in the blink of an eye.

The silver-robed elderly man injected his spiritual sense into the storage bracelet, and a stunned look immediately appeared on his face.

The bracelet contained a vast number of spirit stones, as well as some extremely precious spirit medicines and demon beast ingredients.

In terms of overall value, these items were indeed not inferior to the Exquisite Eight Treasures Jade. In fact, they were of an even superior value.

……

Within the span of just a few short months, a string of strange events took place in the Spirit Domain Realm one after another.

Many sects had their precious materials, or secret techniques, cultivation arts, or scriptures taken away by a mysterious figure.

No one knew who this person was, but he was extremely powerful. However, he was also quite a reasonable man, and all of the sects that had had their treasures taken received handsome compensation. As a result, there was no public outrage arising from these events. Instead, this became a hot topic of discussion for many vagrant cultivators and disciples of other sects.

After several months of activity, the mysterious figure suddenly vanished, and no one ever saw him again.

Close to a year passed by in the blink of an eye.

There was an enormous crimson mountain range in the southeastern region of the Spirit Domain Realm. The mountain range was known as the Fire Cloud Mountain Range, and it extended for hundreds of thousands of kilometers.

The mountain range was filled with countless connected volcanoes that were constantly spewing scorching lava up into the air, filling the entire area with incredible heat and the acrid stench of sulfur.

All of the mountains in this mountain range were a dark red color, resembling red-hot rocks, and even the clouds above the mountain range were always tinted with a crimson hue, thereby giving the mountain range its name.

This was the largest fire spiritual area in the Spirit Domain Realm and also one of the most perilous regions in the entire realm. Even among advanced cultivators, very few had the courage to venture deep into this mountain range.

Deep in the Fire Cloud Mountain Range was an enormous abyss, at the deepest part of which was a river of molten lava, which rumbled loudly as it flowed incessantly.

The river was glowing with red light, as if there were countless flames burning on its surface.

The temperatures here were so high that the air was extremely warped, severely impacting visibility.

On a cliff face no more than 1,000 feet away from the river of lava, a massive cave had been hollowed out, and there were lights of all types of different colors flashing within it, accompanied by occasional loud noises.

On this day, a draconic roar rang out from within the cave, following which an incredibly thick pillar of white light erupted out from within before hurtling directly up toward the heavens.

Within the pillar of light, projections of two wyrms and a massive suit of bone armor could be seen, and those projections lingered in the air for a long time before slowly fading away.

Inside the cave was an azure-robed man seated with his legs crossed.

It was none other than Han Li, and there was an elated look on his face.

There were two treasures that were shimmering with spiritual light hovering in front of him, one of which was a suit of white bone armor with a rather antiquated design. Its surface was riddled with engravings of different images depicting items such as shields and umbrellas.

The other treasure was a pair of silver gloves with a series of silver bone spikes on them, giving them the appearance of a pair of wyrm heads.

Both of the treasures were giving off astonishing spiritual power fluctuations, and a pleased look flashed through Han Li's eyes as his gaze roamed over the pair of treasures.

The suit of bone armor was known as the Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor, while the gloves were known as the Heaven Piercing Gauntlets.

He had found the refinement methods for both of these treasures in the scriptures of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and these treasures were perfect for him as they required the user to possess extremely formidable physical strength in order to unleash their full potential.

Sima Jingming had told him that this alternative method of ascension was very dangerous, so as a safety precaution, he had gone out of his way to gather countless precious materials in order to refine these two treasures.

Han Li opened his mouth to release a burst of azure light that stowed the pair of treasures away, then flipped a hand over to produce an azure jade slip, which contained a detailed map of the Spirit Domain Realm.

There were several locations that had already been annotated on the map, and they marked the brittle spatial nodes that he had found from the scriptures that he had read in various sects, but he hadn't yet verified those spatial nodes in person.

After a brief moment of contemplation, his gaze fell upon an annotated point on the southeastern part of the map, and a thoughtful look appeared in his eyes.

Moments later, a streak of azure light flew out of the valley before hurtling away into the distance.

Chapter 78: Big Dipper Phenomenon

On a giant snowy mountain that was over 100,000 feet tall in the Spirit Domain Realm.

There was a layer of extremely dense dark clouds in the sky, within which thunderclaps were rumbling incessantly, and the occasional flash of dark blue lightning could also be seen.

Down below, gusts of fierce wind were howling incessantly, stirring the countless snowflakes in the sky into a frenzy.

Close to 100 kilometers away from this mountain was a peaceful area with clear skies and a bright moon, creating a stark contrast with the snowy mountain.

The peak of the snowy mountain had already been sliced off, turning it into an enormous plateau that was over 1,000 feet in size.

On the plateau were dozens of black stone pillars that were each over 100 feet tall. The pillars seemed to have been arranged in a random and haphazard manner, but in reality, they were positioned in a way that they formed a giant ring-shaped formation that consisted of two circles, one outside the other.

There were a series of complex spirit patterns engraved onto the ground at the center of the array, while pieces of spirit stones with extremely abundant spiritual power were embedded onto the tops of the surrounding stone pillars.

At this moment, there was a tall figure seated with his legs crossed at the center of the array amid the wind and the snow.

He was wearing a thin azure robe, and he had a set of unremarkable yet well-defined facial features. His eyes were as bright as stars, and it was none other than Han Li.

He gently closed his eyes while making a rapid series of hand seals and chanting an incantation in a low voice, activating his Big Dipper Origin Arts.

All of a sudden, a burst of dazzling light appeared on the mountain peak.

Boundless silver starlight pierced through the dark clouds, projecting down from the heavens, forming seven incredibly thick pillars of silver light that enshrouded the entire mountain.

All of the swirling snow that fell into the pillars of silver light instantly vanished, having been evaporated into vapor.

Han Li continued to make a series of hand seals while raising his hands up to the sky, and a burst of black light flashed from his waist, following which the seven Starmoon Mirrors flew out, with each of them flying into one of the pillars of light before giving off dazzling radiance.

At the same time, a strange vortex suddenly appeared above Han Li, drawing the seven mirrors toward itself.

As the vortex grew larger and larger, the suction force that it was releasing also became more and more pronounced, and all seven of the mirrors began to converge involuntarily toward its center.

The seven massive pillars of light were also influenced, beginning to tilt and angle themselves toward the center of the vortex.

A rumbling boom akin to a thunderclap rang out, and the seven pillars of silver light finally fused as one, forming a gigantic pillar of light that was over 1,000 feet in diameter.

The pillar of light seemed to be connecting heaven and earth and encompassed the entire mountain.

At the same time, a startling change was also taking place in the Big Dipper constellation in the sky.

The seven stars of the Big Dipper began to glow with purplish-silver light one after another, and at the same time, they were also shifting in position, first forming a straight line, then arranging themselves into a circle.

Immediately thereafter, an incredibly thick pillar of purplish-silver light surged out of the ring, piercing through the night sky before shining down directly upon Han Li.

In the instant the purplish-silver light came into contact with Han Li, his clothes were instantly incinerated into ashes.

At the same time, his body turned completely transparent and took on a bright silver hue.

It could even be seen through his skin that changes were beginning to take place in the muscles and bones in his body. In the past, they had only been enveloped by a layer of faint silver light, but now, it was as if they had been encased by liquid silver.

A burst of loud buzzing rang out on the snowy mountain as countless fragments of silver light fell from the sky, replacing the falling snow.

The fragments of light formed an enormous spherical light barrier that encompassed the entire mountain, and there were extremely fearsome spiritual powerful fluctuations emanating from within it.

As these fluctuations became stronger and stronger, the entire mountain began to sway and tremble violently, and soon, the entire mountain range was plunged into a state of unrest.

The ground in a radius of close to 1,000 kilometers was quaking incessantly, and countless long and winding fissures had opened up. Some of them were even causing shifts in the nearby riverbeds, resulting in a restructuring of the rivers.

Plumes of dust began to rise up from all over the lush primitive forest nearby, and countless wild beasts were galloping through the forest while roaring in panic.

In the sky above the forest, countless birds and flying beasts were soaring through the air, forming a dark blanket that concealed most of the sky.

Several hundred kilometers away, a tall volcano that had already laid dormant for over 10,000 years erupted once again under the effects of these violent and persistent tremors.

Large volumes of dark red lava were spewing out of the volcano amid plumes of dense black smoke, rising up high into the sky.

Countless rocks that had been scorched bright red were hurled up into the air, then came crashing back down like a meteor shower, leaving long fiery tails behind them in the night sky. The falling rocks passed through the permeating layers of volcanic ash, then crashed down onto the forest below.

Large sections of the forest were instantly set alight, illuminating the night sky in a bright red hue amid the dense smoke.

Immediately thereafter, around a dozen streaks of light flew out of different parts of the mountain range, and all of them drew to a halt in the air dozens of kilometers away from the silver ball of light.

There were people of all types of descriptions gathered at the scene, and most of them were alone, with only a few rare groups interspersed among their ranks.

They were all vagrant cultivators who were lurking in this mountain range, and their cultivation bases varied drastically, with the weakest ones only at the late-Core Formation Stage, while the strongest ones were at the mid-Spatial Tempering Stage.

Aside from them, there were also some strange-looking humanoid figures. Some of them had horns growing on their heads, some had vibrant stripes on their bodies, some were covered in a coat of fur, and some even had beastly heads rather than human heads. It was clear that these were demonic cultivators.

However, regardless of what race these cultivators belonged to, all of them were currently looking up toward the top of the snowy mountain with stunned and fearful expressions, and not a single one of them dared to approach the scene to investigate.

"Could it be that there's a Grand Ascension cultivator about to transcend an ascension tribulation here?" a white-robed young man asked in a bewildered voice as he stared at the phenomena unfolding on the snowy mountain.

The young man was accompanied by a thin elderly man, who shook his head as he said, "I don't think so. There's no sign of any tribulation lightning falling. Instead, it seems more like someone is practicing an extremely profound cultivation art, and these phenomena are a sign that they're about to reach full mastery of that cultivation art."

"This is all because someone's practicing a cultivation art? How is that possible?"

The white-robed young man drew a sharp breath upon hearing this, unable to wrap his head around such a staggering concept.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar erupted from the mountain peak, and an incredibly powerful energy blast swept through the air in all directions from the mountaintop.

Everyone was already quite far away from the mountain peak, but they still immediately flew back in retreat as streaks of light. One of the weaker demonic cultivators wasn't able to get sufficiently far away in time, and they were struck by the energy blast. As a result, they instantly sustained extremely severe injuries and came within a hair's breadth of being killed on the spot.

Only after retreating a further 100 kilometers or so did everyone draw to a halt before turning back to the mountain peak with lingering fear in their eyes.

The spherical light barrier encompassing the entire snowy mountain had expanded to about twice its original size, thereby encompassing an even larger area. As a result, the entire snowy mountain was reduced to a blur, and only an extremely faint outline could just barely be made out.

……

At the same time.

On the Nine Palace Peak of the Origin Realm Temple, Daoist Closed Mountain was standing on the Star Gathering Platform, looking up at the altered Big Dipper constellation in the night sky with a complex look on his face.

He had been pressured by Han Li into destroying the arrays that facilitated communication between the temple and the Immortal Realm, so he had completely betrayed Daoist Clear Bright.

Now that Han Li seemed to be about to leave, Daoist Closed Mountain was considering what he was going to do if Daoist Clear Bright decided to try and punish him for this transgression.

In addition to that, the Cold Flame Sect had been developing rapidly these past few years, absorbing many smaller powers and sects, and at this point, the Cold Flame Sect and the Origin Realm Temple were roughly evenly matched. With Han Li's departure, the Spirit Domain Realm was most likely going to be plunged into conflict and unrest.

With that in mind, Daoist Closed Mountain couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh.

……

On a plaza at the top of the Cold Flame Sect's Holy Fire Peak.

Sima Jingming was clutching the white jade railing before him with both hands, and he was also looking up at the night sky with a complex look in his eyes.

After some time, he heaved a long sigh, then murmured to himself in a relieved voice, "You're finally leaving, Senior Han..."

Even though the Cold Flame Sect had become significantly more powerful in the wake of the Heavenly Ghost Sect's demise, Han Li's existence had constantly been weighing on his heart like a mountain.

Even though the Cold Flame Sect was on rather good terms with Han Li, that still didn't change the fact Han Li was someone who was capable of wiping out the entire Cold Flame Sect on a whim if he so pleased. Hence, his very existence posed a constant threat to what was otherwise supposed to be a dominant powerhouse of the Spirit Domain Realm, so it was no wonder that Sima Jingming was feeling so apprehensive.

……

Meanwhile, in a secluded cave abode on the Cloudrise Peak.

Gu Yunyue and Yu Menghan were seated beside the stone table in the courtyard of the cave abode.

The latter had her chin resting in her hands as she looked up at the ring-shaped Big Dipper in the sky, as well as that pillar of purplish-silver light, and her eyes were a little out of focus.

A gentle smile appeared on Gu Yunyue's face at the sight of her forlorn display, and she said in a slightly teasing voice, "I must say, Elder Han has been very good to you. Not only has he left this cave abode to you, he also left you so many treasures and pills. In total, these resources rival what one would expect to find in an entire small sect, and they'll be more than enough to support you to the Deity Transformation Stage."

Yu Menghan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then replied, "Elder Han is most likely only giving me this preferential treatment because I was the one who took him and Sister Le'er back to our Yu Manor. Come to think of it, he's already repaid that favor long ago. I owe him far more than he owes me."

Gu Yunyue smiled and offered no response to this.

Thus, both of them fell silent, and peace and quiet returned to the courtyard.

……

In a cave abode halfway up the Cloudrise Peak, Daoist White Stone was seated with his legs crossed in a secret chamber.

Placed in front of him was an old book that was slightly yellow with age, and its cover bore the title "Profound Water Cultivation Journal" in bold and primitive text.

This was a top-tier ghostly cultivation art of the Heavenly Ghost Sect, and in the past, it was an extremely important resource that would've never been given to anyone outside of the sect, which was why Daoist White Stone had been astonished when Han Li suddenly paid him a visit and bestowed this cultivation art upon him.

As soon as he obtained the cultivation art, he immediately began to study it in earnest, and at this point, he had already reached the second level. As a result, the early-Core Formation Stage bottleneck that had stumped him for years was finally beginning to loosen a little.

This was naturally an extremely encouraging turn of events, and not only was Daoist White Stone elated by this progress, he was also feeling extremely fortunate that he had been able to follow Han Li, albeit only for a short time.

Chapter 79: Shattering Space

In the dark night sky, the stars were looking strangely dim, with the exception of the ring-shaped Big Dipper, which was glowing radiantly like a purplish-silver sun.

All of a sudden, the enormous pillar of purplish-silver light that it was projecting downward vanished without any warning.

A burst of rumbling rang out, and the spherical light barrier that encompassed the entire mountain exploded violently, scattering into countless specks of silver light that danced through the air like a sparkle of fireflies.

From afar, it looked as if a beautiful galaxy of stars were descending into this world.

However, this glorious scenery didn't linger for very long before the silver specks of light abruptly converged rapidly toward the peak of the snowy mountain as if they had been summoned there, then vanished into the body of a young man, whose entire body was radiating bright silver light.

The young man was none other than Han Li, and even though waves upon waves of silver light were surging into his body in a frenzy, he remained completely still with his eyes tightly shut.

After an indeterminate period of time, his eyelashes fluttered slightly, and his eyes abruptly sprang open. Blue light was flashing within his eyes, which were incredibly clear and reflecting all of the stars in the sky like a pair of mirrors.

In the next instant, he let loose a low cry, and a cloud of glowing silver mist surged out of his mouth, then gradually faded into the night.

Seven specks of blue light were glowing radiantly from his chest and his abdomen.

He had finally manifested the seventh profound aperture!

The silver light radiating from his body was also gradually fading, but a thin, semi-transparent film was taking shape over his skin, and there were wisps of silver light flowing incessantly over the surface of the thin film.

"This is a True Extreme Membrane, the sign of a True Extreme Body! As expected, full mastery of the Big Dipper Origin Arts really does instantly result in the attainment of a True Extreme Body!"

Han Li was ecstatic as he raised his arm to examine the thin film that enveloped his entire body. He discovered that the film required no magic power expenditure to maintain, and that it was slightly cold to the touch. In addition to that, it didn't feel foreign at all, as if it were a part of his body.

With a single thought, he was able to compress the film so that it adhered to his skin, then vanished into his body after a flash of starry light.

He then summoned the film again, and it instantly appeared over his body at his behest.

After experimenting with this sequence a few times, Han Li's elation only continued to grow. Not only was he honing his mastery over the True Extreme Membrane, he also discovered during the process that his spiritual sense had made a full recovery.

In terms of spiritual sense alone, he was already far ahead of the average True Immortal, and that was undoubtedly a piece of fantastic news for Han Li, who was about to return to the Immortal Realm.

Only at this point did the phenomena taking place in the area gradually subside, and even the erupting volcano slowly settled down again.

However, it was going to take some more time before the fire sweeping through the forest burned itself out.

Hundreds of kilometers away, all of the vagrant cultivators hovering in mid-air were looking up with awe-struck expressions, at a complete loss for what to do.

The white-robed young man's back was already drenched in cold sweat, and he murmured in a bewildered voice, "Is... Is it over?"

"Perhaps..." the thin elderly man replied with a rather hesitant expression.

Standing atop the snowy mountain, there was no hint of elation on Han Li's face. Instead, he wore a rather solemn expression, as if he were preparing for an ordeal.

Only he knew that the true test had only just begun.

In the instant that he had attained a True Extreme Body, the rejection from this realm had already begun to act upon him, applying immense pressure to try and banish him from this realm.

At this moment, he felt as if even the air circulation around him had become extremely sluggish, and even his breathing was slightly hampered, as if he had fallen into a swamp.

This force of rejection wasn't unfamiliar to him. Back when he was ascending to the Immortal Realm in the Spirit Realm, he had briefly felt the same thing, but at the time, he was too busy dealing with the lightning tribulation to bask in the sensation.

He took a deep breath as he made a hand seal, then began to chant an incantation.

A faint buzzing sound rang out as dozens of bursts of light appeared around him in unison. Bursts of rich spiritual power surged out of the spirit stones embedded into the tops of the surrounding stone pillars, then flowed into the array along the patterns on the pillars.

The runes that were engraved onto the ground and the stone pillars instantly lit up, quickly forming an extremely intricate and complex array that was glowing with silver radiance.

This array was known as the Spatial Spirit Pattern Array, and it was a spatial array that he had found in an ancient array tome in the Origin Realm Temple's scripture library.

Even though the array wasn't capable of directly shattering space, it could clear away part of the spatial resistance that he was going to encounter, and that was going to be very helpful to him.

Dozens of pillars of silver light erupted into the heavens from the snowy mountain in unison, piercing straight into the dark clouds up above.

In the instant that the pillars of light erupted into the dark clouds, they instantly transformed into a giant vortex that revolved rapidly around the pillars of light, and the surrounding wind and snow were also swept up into a frenzy.

Thick bolts of lightning began to twist and churn incessantly around the pillars of light like a series of dark blue wyrms while releasing bursts of dull rumbling.

The vagrant cultivators who were watching from afar were greatly alarmed to see this, and they immediately retreated even further away for fear of any further perilous phenomena arising from the scene that they were witnessing. This time, they retreated all the way back to close to 1,000 kilometers away, and only then did they draw to a halt.

Right at this moment, Han Li stood up within the array, then released dozens of streaks of black light out of his sleeve with a flick of his wrist. This was a batch of close to 100 Starmoon Mirrors, and all of them flew toward the surrounding pillars of light.

These Starmoon Mirrors possessed spatial power, and in order to refine them, not only had he exhausted the Heavenly Ghost Sect's entire supply of Yin Dawn Stones, he had even used up all of the Yin Dawn Stones that he had acquired from Tong Ren'e's storage bag.

Upon flying into the pillars of light, the Starmoon Mirrors rose directly upward before vanishing into the dark clouds.

Han Li made a string of hand seals while chanting an incantation, and all of a sudden, blue light flashed within his eyes as he let loose an explosive cry.

A string of earth-shattering booms instantly rang out in rapid succession, and boundless silver starlight exploded in the heavens, forming a silver screen of light that opened up a vast area of silver radiance within the vortex of dark clouds.

Right at this moment, Han Li's entire body began to glow, and he sprang up into the air, flying directly upward toward that glowing silver area.

Inside the vortex was a vast expanse of chaos, and gray mist filled the entire area. Thousands of gray spatial rifts of different shapes and lengths were scattered haphazardly throughout the glowing silver area, presenting an extremely unstable sight to behold.

Han Li swept his gaze over the area to find that small blades of gray light would occasionally fly out of these spatial rifts.

As soon as the surrounding dark clouds came into contact with these blades of light, they would be instantly shredded, and even a bolt of lightning that was struck by one of the blades of light was instantly sliced into two.

As more and more of these blades of gray light appeared, the glowing silver area that had been opened up by boundless starlight was also being eroded, and it was shrinking rapidly at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

The dark clouds were beginning to swallow up the vast expanse of silver radiance, and Han Li didn't hesitate any longer upon seeing this. He immediately let loose a low roar, and dazzling golden light erupted from his body as he rapidly swelled in size, transforming into a giant golden ape that was several hundred feet tall in the blink of an eye.

The giant ape took a deep breath, and a gash appeared on its glabella, out of which a cloud of black qi surged forth, and an inky-black eye abruptly appeared.

Black light flashed deep within the pupil of the eye, and a thin thread of black light was released.

As soon as the thread of black light emerged, it immediately transformed into a thick pillar of black light, which vanished into thin air in a flash.

However, in the next instant, a burst of rumbling suddenly rang out from deep within the vortex of dark clouds.

Immediately thereafter, the entire sky suddenly fell still. It was as if this entire space had been frozen in time, and even the swirling dark clouds and the surrounding wind and snow had become completely stationary.

Deep within the vortex, an indistinct wall of gray light that was around 100 feet in size and extremely irregular in shape emerged within the dark clouds.

Blue light flashed within the giant ape's eyes, and it raised its arms, upon which two bursts of dazzling silver light appeared on its enormous fists. A pair of gauntlets that were tipped with a series of white bone spikes emerged, enveloping both of its fists.

The giant ape then let loose a thunderous roar before drawing upon its reserves of magic power, and countless threads of golden light instantly emerged from its body before flowing into the silver gauntlets along its arms.

The gauntlets instantly began to glow with bright silver light, and they expanded to around twice their original size.

At the same time, seven radiant balls of blue light appeared on the giant ape's chest and abdomen, and the muscles all over its entire body bulged even further, while its arms abruptly thickened considerably.

Immediately thereafter, it raised a fist before throwing a vicious punch at the gray wall of light.

A burst of silver light erupted out of its fist, then rapidly expanded as it surged through the air, transforming into a projection of a silver wyrm's head that was around the size of a house before plunging deep into the vortex.

A resounding boom rang out, and the entire sky trembled violently. A string of loud cracks akin to the sound of a shattering mirror rang out from the gray wall of light deep within the vortex, and a series of cracks appeared at its center before quickly spreading over its entire surface.

Even so, the gray wall of light still didn't shatter. Instead, the glowing gray area that was being supported by starlight crumbled amid the violent tremors.

The dark clouds that had fallen still began to churn ferociously once again, and the countless gray spatial rifts gradually expanded as they converged toward the giant ape.

The giant ape immediately picked up the pace upon seeing this, rushing over to the gray wall of light after just a few flashes in a wraith-like manner.

It then drew upon its magic power once again, and golden light surged over its arms as a layer of golden scales emerged from beneath its fur. At the same time, its muscles quickly bulged even further, and the seven profound apertures on its chest and abdomen also began to glow brightly, as did its Heaven Piercing Gauntlets.

A silver dragon's head projection appeared on the gauntlet, and it was accompanied by a low draconic roar.

The giant golden ape let loose a thunderous roar as it slammed its fist into the gray wall of light, and a resounding boom rang out as the bone spikes on its right gauntlets instantly shattered upon impact, while the projection of the draconic head and the gauntlet itself exploded in unison.

A scintillating silver sun abruptly appeared in the night sky, releasing blinding light that engulfed virtually the entire wall of gray light.

Immediately thereafter, a crisp crack rang out, and an opening that was around 10 feet in length finally appeared on the wall of gray light, revealing a murky gray space beyond it.

At the same time, the rift released a burst of extraordinarily powerful spatial fluctuations, the ferocity of which Han Li had never felt before.

Golden light flashed over the giant ape's body as it quickly reverted back into its human form, then flew into the opening in a flash.

As soon as Han Li entered through the opening, the dozen or so spatial rifts and the dark clouds behind him devoured the wall of gray light.

Several seconds later, the silver pillars of light on the snowy mountain peak gradually faded, and the vortex of dark clouds in the sky also dissipated, while the spatial rifts that had been left behind slowly sealed over again.

The storm of wind and snow resumed, and aside from the howling of the wind, everything was peaceful and quiet again.

Chapter 80: Strange Bubbles

Streams of light of different colors were surging throughout the area in a violent and chaotic fashion, forming enormous waves that were constantly crashing into one another amid deafening booms.

Occasionally, a series of white spatial rifts would emerge within the waves of light, releasing astonishing suction force and a high-pitched droning sound.

Even almighty Grand Ascension cultivators or high-grade demon beasts with near indestructible physical bodies had to exercise the utmost caution when traversing through this space. Even the slightest lapse in concentration could result complete destruction of one's body and soul, not only putting an end to one's life, but also robbing them of a chance at reincarnation.

This was the interrealm gap!

At this moment, Han Li was like a non-swimmer who had suddenly been thrown into a raging and turbulent sea.

He had already anticipated that the interrealm gap was going to be an extremely perilous place that would be exceedingly difficult to traverse through, but this was still quite an astonishing sight to him.

The spatial storm that was raging throughout the surrounding area was countless times more powerful than the one he had endured during his ascension from the Human Realm to the Spirit Realm.

If it weren't for the fact that he had already attained a True Extreme Body and taken countless pills, as well as practiced countless cultivation arts that enhanced his physical constitution, he would've most likely been completely pulverized in the instant that he entered this space.

His entire body was already encased within a suit of antiquated white bone armor. It was the Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor that he had refined using countless precious treasures from the Spirit Domain Realm, but even so, he was swaying unsteadily under the influence of the enormous suction force acting upon him from all directions.

He took a deep breath, and dazzling white light erupted from the suit of bone armor as all of the umbrellas, shields, and other images on its surface lit up in unison. At the same time, a sharp screeching sound rang out, and all of the images projected themselves before revolving around Han Li.

These projections revolved around him momentarily before fusing as one to form an extremely substantial protective barrier that encompassed his entire body. The protective barrier was giving off radiant white light, and it was keeping out some of the violent spatial fluctuations in the surrounding area.

Only then was Han Li able to steady himself, and he gave a pleased nod as he inspected his suit of bone armor.

This suit of Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor had been refined specifically to deal with the spatial storm in the interrealm gap, and he had carefully selected all of the materials used. Several of the main materials, such as the Exquisite Eight Treasures Jade, all possessed spatial attributes, and the suit of armor was certainly living up to his expectations thus far.

Blue light flashed several times within his eyes, following which he proceeded forward as a streak of light.

The surrounding spatial storm surged toward him in waves, only to be kept out by the suit of Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor.

However, around 15 minutes later, his brows furrowed slightly with concern once again.

Even though he was well protected by the suit of bone armor, the progress that he was making through the spatial storm was agonizingly slow. At this point, he estimated that he had only advanced around 50 kilometers.

Under normal circumstances, this wouldn't have been a cause for concern in itself. After all, this was a brittle spatial node between the two realms, and even if progress were slow, he would eventually reach the Immortal Realm so long as he continued to advance. However, he could clearly sense that the spiritual power imbued within the suit of bone armor was being rapidly exhausted as it withstood the spatial storm.

"I wanted to save some energy to deal with any potential unforeseen circumstances, but it looks like I can't hold back any longer," Han Li murmured to himself after a moment of contemplation.

In the next instant, dazzling rainbow light that was as bright as the sun erupted from his entire body.

A clear phoenix cry rose directly up into the heavens as he transformed into a giant bird that was several hundred feet in length.

This was none other than the Heavenly Phoenix form in his 12 Awakening Transformations.

The Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor disassembled itself, transforming into a series of bone plates that adhered to various parts of the Heavenly Phoenix's body, but the white light barrier wasn't affected at all.

The Heavenly Phoenix spread its wings and transformed into a rainbow-colored shadow that sped directly forward at a speed that was countless times faster than before.

The spatial storm continued to converge from all directions, but as soon as it came into contact with the Heavenly Phoenix, a burst of rainbow light would instantly erupt from its body to divert the spatial storm away.

The Heavenly Phoenix possessed the ability to manipulate space, so it was like a fish in water in this spatial storm.

A hint of excitement appeared in the Heavenly Phoenix's eyes, and it let loose a long cry before accelerating even further, traversing rapidly through the boundless spatial storm up ahead.

Time slowly passed by. There were no days or nights in the interrealm gap, but by Han Li's estimates, roughly a day had already passed by.

During this day, he had encountered many close calls, and it felt longer and more arduous than even an entire year.

Not only were there spatial storms in the interrealm gap, there were also other unforeseen dangers lurking in the shadows, including even a type of strange living being that inhabited the area and had attacked him on several occasions.

Thankfully, he was able to spot these dangers in advance with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, and that, coupled with the spatial manipulation abilities of the Heavenly Phoenix, allowed him to escape unscathed every time.

At this point, the rainbow light around the Heavenly Phoenix's body had already become significantly dimmer than before, and there was also a hint of weariness in its eyes.

Maintaining this form for an extended period of time was very physically taxing for Han Li, but what was even more concerning to him was the suit of bone armor that he was wearing.

A series of cracks had already appeared on the armor's surface, and all that remained of the white protective barrier around him was only a thin layer that was less than a third as potent as it had been at its peak.

"If I had known this would happen, I would've spent some more time to refine another treasure," Han Li murmured to himself with a wry smile, but he quickly banished that thought from his mind.

At this point, it was already too late to turn back, so there was no point in crying over spilled milk.

He took a deep breath, and the rainbow light around his body brightened as he accelerated once again.

Shortly thereafter, his eyes suddenly lit up as he caught sight of a speck of white light amid the spatial storm up ahead.

It was only a very faint speck of light, but it stood like an unyielding beacon amid a storm of chaos and murky grayness.

Could it be...

A possibility sprang into Han Li's mind, and he reflexively accelerated even further, flying rapidly toward the speck of white light.

The more he advanced, the brighter the speck of white light became, and an inexplicable yet regal aura was emanating from within, as if an extremely sacred place laid beyond it.

This was an aura that Han Li had felt before. It was the aura of the Immortal Realm!

"Finally..." Han Li heaved a long sigh of relief and excitement.

Thankfully, his luck wasn't too terrible. Otherwise, if this suit of Exquisite Eight Treasures Bone Armor were to be shattered, he wouldn't have been able to withstand the spatial storms within the interrealm gap with his physical body alone.

Even though he was already feeling quite exhausted, he was reinvigorated by the sight that greeted him up ahead.

As long as he could return to the Immortal Realm, he would be able to find the organization that was offering a reward for his capture, and it would only be a matter of time before he uncovered the events that led to his amnesia and the severe injuries that he had sustained.

After flying forward for a while longer, Han Li suddenly began to slow down as a befuddled look appeared in his eyes.

A massive yellow object that was several hundred kilometers in size was hovering amid the spatial turbulence not far up ahead, and it bore the appearance of an enormous bubble.

The turbulent spatial storm was instantly repelled as soon as it came into contact with the giant bubble, unable to harm it in the slightest.

Furthermore, Han Li could just barely make out something residing within the mysterious bubble, and a layer of blue light emerged within his eyes as he focused his gaze on the bubble, but his brows then quickly furrowed slightly.

There was some type of peculiar force that was obstructing his view, and even his Brightsight Spirit Eyes were unable to see through the bubble.

A hint of curiosity welled up in Han Li's heart, but he immediately shook his head.

The bubble was a very strange entity, and he was far from peak condition right now, so it was best to stay out of trouble as much as possible and prioritize getting to the Immortal Realm.

With that in mind, the Heavenly Phoenix spread its wings, then altered its flight trajectory so that it could skirt around the yellow bubble.

Right at this moment, the spatial storm around him began to churn violently.

All of a sudden, a burst of enormous force sprang out of the spatial storm before crashing viciously into the Heavenly Phoenix.

What was that?

The power imbued within the burst of force was not inferior to that of an all-out attack from him.

The Heavenly Phoenix was instantly sent careening to the side before crashing involuntarily into the yellow bubble.

The yellow bubble was able to repel the surrounding spatial storm with ease, but not only was the Heavenly Phoenix not repelled, it sank into the bubble without any resistance.

Han Li felt as if the world were spinning all around him, and only after flapping his wings vigorously several times was he able to just barely steady himself.

The burst of force that had crashed into him had been extremely powerful, but it wasn't enough to harm him in his current state.

After stabilizing himself, he quickly inspected his surroundings, and he was quite surprised by what he saw.

This was an extremely peaceful yellow world. The violent spatial turbulence outside had completely vanished, and yellow light was permeating through the air. Down below was a landmass that was several hundred kilometers in size, resembling an island.

The world's origin qi within this yellow space was extremely abundant, hundreds of times more so than even the best spirit regions in the Spirit Domain Realm. The island was riddled with lush forestry, and all of the trees growing on the island looked to be at least 1,000 years old.

There were also many spirit ingredients interspersed throughout the forest, all of which were at least several thousand years old. There were also many spirit medicines that were in excess of 10,000 years of age, and most of them were species that he didn't recognize.

This was an island that was riddled with treasures!

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li returned to his human form amid a flash of rainbow light, then flipped a hand to summon a blue pill that he promptly swallowed.

This pill was called the Heavenly Star Pill, and it was a secret pill of the Origin Realm Temple that was refined using several types of spirit medicines capable of absorbing starpower. For someone like him, who had cultivated the Big Dipper Origin Arts, it was the ideal recovery pill.

The Heavenly Star Pill quickly dissolved into a surge of warmth that flowed throughout his entire body, filling his exhausted body with a burst of vitality that facilitated rapid recovery.

Instead of immediately descending to the ground, Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes and began to carefully inspect his surroundings.

He couldn't shake the feeling that someone or something had intentionally launched that burst of force at him to propel him into the yellow bubble.

Right at this moment, an earth-shattering roar rang out from down below.

The entire island trembled violently as a gargantuan yellow cloud rose up from the forest before flying toward Han Li like lightning, reaching him in the blink of an eye.

A massive figure that seemed to belong to a giant could just barely be made out within the yellow cloud.

An enormous yellow fist was launched out of the yellow cloud. The skin on the fist was yellow and withered like extremely coarse tree roots.

As soon as the fist emerged, it crashed directly toward Han Li with incredibly fearsome power, and even before the fist reached Han Li, the space around him was already beginning to ripple violently.

Han Li's pupils contracted slightly as he let loose a low roar, and seven specks of blue light emerged on his chest and abdomen as he activated his Big Dipper Origin Arts to its fullest extent.

Faint starlight began to emanate from his entire body, and seven thick bands of starlight wrapped themselves around him as he retaliated with a punch of his own.

The surrounding space exploded violently, sending shockwaves that were visible to the naked eye surging through the air.

After achieving full mastery of the Big Dipper Origin Arts, this punch from Han Li was able to rival the golden giant in power even without taking on his Giant Mountain Ape form.

The two fists collided with an earth-shattering boom, and the surrounding space warped violently as bursts of devastating shockwaves swept through the air, proliferating outward as gusts of ferocious wind.

Han Li was sent flying back by the impact and flew all the way back for several thousand feet before just barely managing to steady himself.

Inside the yellow cloud, the giant was also stopped cold in its tracks and forced to stumble back a couple of steps to absorb the force of the impact.

Immediately thereafter, the yellow cloud around the giant was blown apart by the gusts of fierce wind, thereby revealing the creature inside.